Like I said, that was just a taste of Book 2.
To  watch  it  uncensored,  just  click  on  the  first  link  here  in
the  pinned  comment.
I'll see you on the other side in a few seconds.
Remember, just click on the first link down here in the comments.
And Book 2, complete.
With  no  ads  or  interruptions,  we'll  already  be  available  for
you.
It's very simple.
Book 2 is something I'm loving making, and you're loving it too.
So I promise there will be more.
It's where you find increasingly spicy stories,
a true dark romance,
and precisely because this version is getting more and more heated,
the video isn't well accepted publicly on YouTube.
This closed environment is where I can actually share my essence,
and where I feel free to do my best work for you.
More news coming soon.
I'll be waiting for you on the other side.