I've heard stories, but I never imagined it would be like this.
This place holds secrets.
I know it.
She only needed one interview.
Jago  Quint  was  the  billionaire  no  one  could  reach,  and  that
story  could  save  her  career.
So  she  accepted  the  most  dangerous  deal  of  her  life,  pretending
to  be  his  girlfriend  for  one
night.
It was supposed to be simple.
Walk  into  the  ball  convinces  family  and  walk  out  with  the  answers  she
needed,  but  when
Jago's  mother  demanded  proof  of  love  in  front  of  everyone,  she
did  exactly  what  she
shouldn't have.
She kissed Jago.
And  that  kiss,  which  was  only  supposed  to  be  a  lie,
started  to  feel  far  too  real.
Hi, I'm Rowan.
A  special  shout  out  to  those  of  you  watching  Book  One  for  free  here  on  the
My  Stories  platform,
completely ad-free and uninterrupted.
Chapter 1.
The Impossible Interview.
His  room  smelled  of  reheated  coffee  and  old  paper,  and
Rowina  Pike  had  already  drunk  three
cups before nine in the morning.
The gray light coming through the window gave every face there the same shade of exhaustion.
The kind of fatigue that doesn't come from one bad night's sleep, but from months piled
one on top of another.
She knew, hers was no different.
She held her folder against her chest, and crossed the narrow aisle between the desks,
greeting with a Kurt Nord anyone who looked up.
Hollis Vaughn was waiting for her with his elbows planted on the desk, glasses pushed
to the tip of his nose.
The editor had a peculiar way of looking at people, as if he were checking whether they were
worth their own salary.
Rowina shut the door behind her, ignored the chair he didn't offer, and sat down without
waiting for an invitation.
I need the interview Pike.
Hollis didn't waste time on introductions, and I need something else too.
If you're about to tell me you need a photo of Quint without his jacket, I'm walking
out of this room right now.
I need a file.
The sentence landed in the middle of the desk, like something too heavy for the furniture.
Rowina raised an eyebrow, waiting for him to refraise to apologise to turn it into a joke.
Hollis did none of that.
He simply laced his fingers, and kept looking at her, as if he were collecting on an old
debt.
Proof, he added, that that empire is hiding something it shouldn't be hiding.
Everyone hides something Pike.
You just need to find out what?
You want me to get inside the home of the most closed off family in the south.
Land the interview no one's managed to land in 10 years, and still walk out of there with
compromising material.
I'm telling you that your job here depends on it.
She didn't answer right away.
She sat staring at the coffee stain on the rim of his mug.
Calculating how much of next month's salary was already committed to rent, how much was
still owed on her mother's bill.
The window behind Hollis let in the muffled noise of the street.
A horn, a quick step.
The city running nonstop while she sat there deciding how far she was willing to go.
Then she nodded once, short, like someone signing a contract they haven't yet read.
Malo Trent intercepted her in the hallway with two fresh coffees, and a smile that was
already a question.
Malo was a copy editor, a colleague of three years, and the only person in the newsroom
who understood when Rowine needed silence, and when she needed noise, you look like someone
who just sold her soul.
Malo remarked, handing over the hotter cup.
Was it for much?
It was for next month's rent.
Malo laughed, a short laugh, cut off halfway by the awareness that the joke was worth
more to herself than to Rowine.
She leaned her shoulder against Rowine as they walked down the hallway, and for a moment,
Rowine felt like dropping everything right there, walking out the front door and never
coming back.
She didn't.
She drank the coffee until it burned her tongue.
After noon came quickly, and with it a note left at the front desk.
No sender, just her name on the front of the envelope, written in black pen and handwriting
that wasn't a friend, slanted controlled letters, each one in its exact place.
Rowine had turned the envelope over twice before opening it, inside just an address and
a time.
Nothing more.
The office it pointed to was three blocks away, in a discreet building she had never noticed,
despite having walked past it hundreds of times.
The sign at the entrance simply read Ashford and Associates, in letters too small to
draw attention.
Rowine aclimed the steps with her folder still pressed against her chest, and greeted
the receptionist with the name that was on the note.
The man who received her was younger than she expected.
Tall, navy, suit, no tie, with that kind of discretion only old money teachers.
He extended his hand and introduced himself as Silas Ashford, the Quint family's lawyer,
a friend of Jago's since their boarding school days.
The information came without fanfare, the way someone hands over a business card.
Have a seat, Miss Pike.
His voice had the same tone as the handwriting on the envelope.
I'll be brief because the proposal is brief.
I'm curious.
Mr. Quint agrees to grant a two-hour interview to your publication.
No restrictions on subject matter.
Except one.
Silas made a minimal pause.
The kind of pause lawyers used to let the client swallow the next piece of information.
In return, you would attend the family's Gallaboll in Savannah as his companion on Friday.
One night, just one.
Rowine elapsed before her brain authorized her mouth.
Companion.
That's the word he preferred.
And what word didn't he prefer?
The corner of Silas's mouth moved half a millimeter, almost the beginning of a smile,
but nothing followed through.
He slid a black envelope across the desk, sealed, with her name written on the front,
in the same slanted, controlled handwriting as the first note.
Letters she now recognized without effort,
and which definitely did not belong to Silas.
The rules are in there.
One read is enough.
The expects an answer today.
Rowine looked at the black envelope for too long.
She thought about the rent.
She thought about the look on Holasis face.
She thought about the old photograph of the reclusive billionaire
that had circulated through the papers forever.
Always the same profile of a clenched jaw.
Always the same gaze that didn't invite anyone to stay.
She tucked the envelope into her folder without opening it.
Tell him I'll be in Savannah on Friday.
Silas nodded like someone who already knew the answer before the question.
He rose, shook her hand again, and walked her to the door with practice courtesy.
Before closing the handle, he said almost without voice.
He's not what the press writes, that's all.
Rowine didn't ask what he meant.
She preferred not to know yet.
Marla was waiting for her on the street with a cigarette that pretended to be lit.
The kind of theatre she used as an excuse to loiter on corners.
Rowine handed over the black envelope without ceremony.
A friend turned the object over in her hand,
studied the seal with more attention than necessary, and gave it back.
Don't open it now, Marla said, open it on the train.
It's prettier that way.
Pretty ya.
Do you want to be someone else's story or make history?
If it's the second, you open it on the train alone,
and you cry if you need to cry without anyone seeing.
It's the least you deserve.
Rowine laughed and the laugh pulled some of the weight off her back.
She rested her forehead on Marla's shoulder for a short second.
Just enough to remember she still had a friend in that grey city,
and then she went home to pack.
The station was too crowded for her taste.
Rowine had dragged her luggage between hurried bodies,
bought a sandwich she wasn't going to eat, and settled by the window of the car.
The seats smelled of dust and warm synthetic leather.
That smell of a place where many people have passed without leaving a trace.
She sat staring at the tracks for a while,
before taking the black envelope out of the inner pocket of her bag.
The seal gave way with a dry sound.
Inside, three folded sheets.
The first two carried instructions written with almost legal precision.
Times, names she should memorize,
clothes that would be delivered to the hotel.
What to say if anyone asked how long they had known each other,
Rowine erred them with the same attention she gave to story contracts,
mentally noting every detail, every gap between the lines.
The third sheet was smaller, a single line written by hand, unsigned.
Don't smile at anyone like you believe it.
Only smile when I'm looking.
She read it three times.
She put it away again.
She looked out the window as the train picked up speed and the city opened into suburb,
then countryside.
There nothing.
And she couldn't decide whether that was an order, a warning, or a request.
The train arrived in Savannah in the late afternoon.
The air changed before she even stepped onto the platform.
Warmer, denser,
laden with a sweet perfume she couldn't yet name.
Magnolia maybe.
Or something that grew near water.
Rowine across the station with her folder under her arm,
looking for the driver who would be waiting with her name on a sign.
She found the dark car outside, a man in a suit opening the back door without ceremony.
Before getting in, she looked one last time at the city's skyline and saw in the distance.
The high roof of the quint mansion cut against the sky that was beginning to turn orange.
Too big, too old.
The kind of house that doesn't invite you in.
It absorbs you.
Rowine sat on the leather seat,
rested her head against the cold glass,
and pressed the black envelope against her lap,
like someone clutching a boarding pass to another country.
She took the sheet out one more time.
Only smile when I'm looking.
She re-read it, folded it, put it away.
The car started up,
and the streets of Savannah began to pass by outside like a borrowed set,
with the moss heavy trees and the old houses that each guarded their own version of a secret.
And for the first time since Holly's Vaughn had added the word file,
Rowine a pike wondered,
whether she could go home as the same person who had boarded the train.
Chapter 2, a three second kiss.
Who tell sweet was bigger than her entire apartment,
with a soft smell of jasmine that seemed built into the walls.
Rowine looked at herself in the oval mirror for a long time,
adjusting the wine-colored silk dress they had left hanging behind the door.
The fabric fell effortlessly.
The kind of piece that only existed when someone paid for it without thinking twice.
The driver knocked at the door at the exact time indicated in the envelope.
Rowine went down,
crossed the lobby under stairs she pretended not to notice,
and found the car waiting at the curb.
The back door opened before she touched the handle,
and the first thing she saw inside was the impeccable crease of dark trousers,
running down to a pair of polished black shoes.
Jago Quint was seated on the other side of the seat,
with one knee slightly apart from the other,
hands resting on his own thighs.
He didn't stand, didn't extend his hand.
He merely tilted his chin and inch toward the empty spot beside him,
and waited.
Rowine got in, adjusted her skirt with a quick gesture,
and shut the door with more force than necessary.
He noticed.
She saw that he noticed.
Neither of them commented.
Good evening, Miss Pike.
His voice was lower than she had imagined from any interview she'd ever read.
A voice that didn't rise because it didn't need to.
Rowine returned her face and looked at him full on for the first time,
and had the displeasure of confirming that the portraits published over the years did
him no justice.
In person, he was a sculpture of a straight jaw,
dark hair combed back with calculated carelessness,
and eyes that decided the temperature of the room before saying anything at all.
Good evening, Mr. Quint.
Jago will do.
Then Rowine will do.
He nodded almost imperceptibly,
the car started up, and for a while the two of them sat in silence.
Rowine noticed his hands resting on his knees,
long fingers, a silver watch with no visible brand.
She also noticed that the seat between them held a thin leather folder,
closed, with one corner leaning against the glass.
Details.
She collected details.
Are the rules clear?
He asked without turning his face.
Crystal.
Any questions?
One.
Rowine awaited until he finally turned his gaze to her.
How long do you intend for this night to last?
As long as necessary, that's not an answer.
It's the only one I have.
He looked forward again and Rowine accepted defeat in that round without arguing.
She kept watching his profile against the dark window.
The hard line of his jaw, the way his thumb pressed against his own knee in a steady rhythm,
like someone counting something inside himself.
She stored the gesture in her memory, and said nothing.
The Quint mentioned appeared at the end of the avenue of tall trees,
lit from outside like a theatre set.
Rowine drew a deep breath before the car stopped.
Jago got out first.
Went around the vehicle and opened her door with a courtesy that sounded more rehearsed than
sincere.
He offered his arm.
She accepted.
His palm brushed briefly against her hand as he helped her position herself,
and the temperature changed.
Don't smile at anyone like you believe it, he murmured.
Barely moving his lips as they climb the steps.
You already warned me in writing.
I'm reinforcing it.
The main hall swallowed them the moment the door opened.
Rowine has smelled it before she saw anything.
Magnolia and old money.
Exactly as Silas had said in the instruction note.
The white walls rose high to a ceiling of worked stucco,
and everywhere there were antique chandeliers spreading a honey-colored light over the guests.
Long dresses, emerald chocas, men in black tuxedoes,
greeting each other without enthusiasm.
Jago introduced her to three couples in a row,
always with the same assembled sentence.
My companion for the evening, Rowine a pike.
No complicated surnames.
No deer.
No love.
Rowine a smile in just the right measure.
Answered questions in just the right measure.
And noticed everything.
She noticed that he avoided the terrace.
Twice a waiter passed offering to take guests out to the outdoor area.
And both times Jago declined,
with a minimal gesture of his chin,
without even looking at the glass door.
She also noticed that his gaze had one point,
tripped over an empty chair near the window.
A chair upholstered in dark green velvet,
slightly set apart from the rest of the arrangement,
as if it belonged to someone who used to sit there and hadn't arrived yet.
He looked away quickly.
Rowineerstorted.
What an unlikely evening.
The voice came from behind her sweetest syrup heated too much.
Rowine returned and found a woman with red hair pinned in a low bun,
an emerald green dress,
a smile that didn't reach her eyes.
Jago stiffened beside her.
Odeit, he greeted her without warmth.
Jago.
Odeitmachand extended her hand to Rowine,
palm down,
the gesture of someone expecting reverence,
and the companion.
How interesting.
What do you do, dear?
I write.
Ah.
Odeit seemed to decide something in silence.
How brave of him to bring you here.
Brave of me to agree to come.
Odeit laughed.
A short note that contained nothing of laughter.
Then she moved off with a wave of her fingers,
leaving behind a trail of expensive perfume.
Jago rested his hand at the small of Rowine's back
for just a second,
a gesture of ownership that wasn't affection.
Then he withdrew it.
You didn't need to provoke her.
He remarked.
Low.
I did, actually.
He didn't answer.
But the corner of his mouth moved a millimeter,
and Rowine arrested it as if it were the headline of the month.
It wasn't a smile yet.
It was close.
The silence in the hall changed texture
before she understood why.
It was as if the air had drawn back a few inches,
and everybody there in Unison had turned their heads in the same direction.
Rowine followed the others gaze,
and saw you door a quint entering through the main door.
The matriarch didn't need to announce herself.
A long black dress, a pearl necklace that fell to the middle of her chest,
gray hair pinned with a rigidity that allowed no discussion.
She crossed the hall without greeting anyone,
and stopped before her son and his companion,
with the expression of someone appraising merchandise.
Good evening, mother, said Jago.
You'dora didn't answer her son.
She turned her pale eyes to Rowina,
and examined her from shoes to hairstyle,
with a surgical calm.
Then she stepped half a step closer,
and the voice that came out of her was low,
but sharp enough to cut the entire hall.
I don't see love here, my son.
The silence closed around the three of them.
Rowina felt Jago's body stiffened beside her,
his shoulders rising half an inch.
Yudora stayed put, chin raised waiting.
Proof said the matriarch.
If it's true, prove it.
The entire hall turned, heads lifted from champagne glasses,
conversations ceased,
waiters stopped where they stood.
Rowina felt the weight of the whole hall falling on her and Jago at the same time.
He locked up.
She saw that he locked up.
His thumb stopped counting on his own hip,
his jaw hardened,
and for a whole second, no decision came out of his body.
Rowina decided for him.
She raised her hand took his face by the side and pulled.
His mouth met hers with a hesitation of someone who hadn't rehearsed this scene,
and for an instant, Rowina thought he wouldn't respond.
Then his breath faltered.
She felt the falter,
felt the air caught halfway up his chest,
felt his hand rise by reflex to her back and settle between her shoulder blades,
with a pressure that didn't belong to the charade.
The kiss was supposed to last a second.
It lasted three.
Maybe more.
Rowina lost count somewhere between the moment he tilted his head a little to the side,
and the moment she herself forgot there was a hall around them.
When they pulled apart, she opened her eyes first.
He took half a second longer,
and what Rowina saw on his face when he finally looked back,
was the same thing she felt inside,
and which she wasn't prepared to name yet.
Udora stepped back half a step.
She adjusted her pearl necklace with a calculated carelessness,
and the corner of her mouth drew a line that wasn't a smile but pretended to be.
Good.
Mermaid the matriarch.
I hope to see you again many times.
Many.
She turned on her heels and moved off.
The hall little by little began to breathe again.
Conversations returned like a discreet murmur.
Waters moved.
Someone laughed in the distance at something that wasn't funny.
Rowina kept looking at Jago.
His hand was still on her back forgotten there,
in no hurry to leave.
He took his time pulling it back.
When he did, his fingers passed slowly over the silk of the dress,
like someone memorizing a path they might need to retrace later.
Across the hall Odec-Marshon watched them with a glass in her hand,
and her smile was now a different one.
Rowina registered it.
She already knew, without needing a warning,
that that woman would want payback.
Jago leaned in very slightly,
and spoke close to her ear so low that only she could hear.
You owe me an explanation.
For the kiss?
For the length of the kiss.
Rowina didn't answer.
She didn't know the answer yet.
She took the glass away to her,
drank a sip she didn't even feel go down,
and looked again at the empty chair near the window.
Someone, at some point, had sat in it.
Someone who now was no longer there,
and Rowina Pike, who had collected details since childhood,
understood that the most important story of that night,
had nothing to do with the reason Hollis Vaughan had sent her there.
Chapter 3, Coffee with No Recorder.
The morning after the ball arrived without ceremony,
the Savannah Sun came through the gaps in the curtain of the guest room,
at the Quint Mansion with an almost impolite insistence,
and Rowina Pike opened her eyes before she remembered exactly where she was.
It took a whole instant for the high ceiling,
the carved footboard, and the thick silence of the house to organize themselves in her head.
Only then did the kiss come back.
It came back first through her lip.
Then through the nape of her neck,
then through her stomach.
Three seconds that now carried the weight of biography.
She sat on the edge of the bed and looked at her own hands.
They were cold.
Someone had left a coffee tray on the sideboard beside the door,
during the night probably,
because the cup was no longer steaming.
Beside it a short note, written by hand in a hand writing she recognized at once,
garden, whenever you can.
Jay Rowina re-read the note twice just to prove to herself that it hadn't unsettled her.
It didn't stick.
The garden was at the back of the house, far from the main hall.
She noticed that as a small paleide housekeeper,
let her down a corridor of portraits.
The woman introduced herself as neve,
lightly squeezed Rowina's arm and said,
in an accent from rural Georgia,
that Mr. Jego was already waiting.
There was warmth in her voice but also scrutiny.
Rowina smiled with her mouth closed and asked nothing.
Jego Quint was standing near an old rose bush with his back to the house.
White shirt sleeves folded to the elbow,
hair still wet from his shower.
He turned when he heard the gravel and for a second,
just one, his eyes met hers unguarded,
without their usual controlled gleam.
Then his jaw firmed up again.
Did you sleep?
As much as I could, she answered,
the house makes noises.
It does. He pointed with his chin toward a cast iron bench.
Sit with me.
We need to work out what comes next.
Rowina obeyed, but chose to sit in profile knees turned outward.
A small defense he noticed.
He said nothing.
You have the interview, Jego began,
his voice low and chosen word by word.
That's still standing,
but last night raised an issue I didn't foresee.
My mother didn't believe it until the kiss.
Maybe she believed it afterward.
If you disappear tomorrow,
she'll get suspicious again.
And I'll have three candidates on the table by Sunday.
You're asking me for more days.
I'm asking for weeks.
Rowina swallowed the small shock and breathed through her mouth before answering.
Weeks of what?
Appearances.
A dinner here and event there.
Enough for Savannah to believe you're the woman who finally got into this house.
He paused.
Same payment, same interview.
Just a longer timeline.
There was logic in the proposal.
And there was a trap.
She knew both.
And if I refuse,
you get the interview anyway.
He said without hesitating.
We agreed on something and I don't undo what's agreed.
That was what disarmed her.
Not the proposal.
The resolution of the proposal.
Rowina bit the inside of her cheek.
Looked at the nearest rose counted to three and said yes.
He didn't smile.
He just nodded slightly, like someone closing her claws.
But when she stood up to go back into the house,
his hand brushed her back for half a second,
had a spot below her shoulder blade.
And lingered an instant longer than any contract required.
She stored the gesture alongside the others.
She was already collecting.
The following weeks arrived slowly,
and without a truce.
Rowina began to split herself between the newsroom
where Marlo covered her shifts with increasingly irritated humour,
and the streets of Savannah,
where she learned there were neighborhoods where the air smelled of wet
Jasmine and others where it only smelled of hoarded money.
Jego always sent for her at the station,
with the same driver and always in the same car.
He waited for her inside, in the back seat,
shoulder leaning against the opposite door.
One Tuesday, he took her to an antique's fair under the oaks of the old
Rowina stopped in front of a tray of loose pendants,
and picked up one shaped like a crooked owl.
Half green with age, set with ridiculous red stones.
It's ugly, she said, smiling at the object as if it were an accomplice.
It is, Jego agreed.
She put the pendant back on the tray.
She didn't ask for it.
Didn't haggle.
Didn't look at it again.
Half an hour later, when they were heading back to the car,
he passed the dark velvet box into her hand without any ceremony,
and Rowina stood in the middle of the sidewalk,
holding the crooked owl as if it were a live animal.
You didn't haggle, she remarked.
No, he opened the car door for her.
I knew what it was worth to you.
It was that day that Rowina didn't turn on the recorder for the entire afternoon.
She sat with Jego in his office on the 13th floor of a glass building in downtown savanna,
and they talked about things no interview called for.
A cousin he had never saw.
A book she had read 12 times in her teams.
A specific smell of the coffee her mother used to make.
Jego poured her coffee that afternoon in a way she hadn't taught him.
Half a spoon of sugar, a splash of milk.
Very hot.
Rowina looked at the cup, looked at him, and didn't ask how he knew.
Neeve let the answer slip a week later in the mansions kitchen,
while drying a crystal glass with the attention of someone handling something bigger than a glass.
He's been sleeping better since you've been coming.
The housekeeper didn't look at Rowina as she said it.
It's not a compliment, it's an observation.
Rowina laughed softly without breath to answer.
Do you want to know something miss?
Neeve continued, putting the glass away.
It's been a long time since anyone asked him how his day was.
He would be grateful, even if he didn't know how to thank you.
Rowina's hand trembled slightly on the handle of her mug.
She set the mug down on the marble with doubled care.
The charity event took place on a Thursday.
It was an auction in aid of a children's hospital in a vaulted ceiling tall,
where the candleabras seemed too heavy for the wire that held them.
Rowina wore a dark green dress borrowed from Marlo's sister,
and Jago appeared at her side at the entrance, as if he'd matched the exact time to his own watch.
Odec Marshaar arrived 20 minutes later.
Rowina saw her approach from the other side of the hall,
greeting people with thin kisses.
A champagne coloured dress moving like liquid.
Odec stopped in front of Rowina, looked her up and down with a smile too polite to be polite,
and said in a tone that carried through the three nearest people,
you hold up well dear.
A borrowed dress in a hall of this caliber isn't for just anyone.
I hope the night is kind to you.
The air in the hall became specific.
Two women near the buffet stopped chewing.
Rowina felt the blood rise up her neck and choose between turning into fury
and turning into dignity.
Before she could decide, Jago's hand touched the small of her back.
Firm, without theatrical possession, just presence,
and he took half a step forward, shoulder pressed against hers.
Odec, he said, and his voice was no longer lower than usual,
only stripped of anything amiable.
If you have any doubts about the woman I came with, put those doubts to me directly.
Rowina owes you no explanation about where she buys any dress.
Neither do you.
Odec parted her lips, and something inside her smile gave way for half a second,
before recomposing.
Now touchy Jago, it was a compliment.
It wasn't.
He didn't raise his tone, he didn't need to.
Two people nearby rediscovered a sudden fascination with their own shoes.
Odec nodded, murmured a phrase about finding a friend and with Drew.
Jago didn't move his hand from Rowina's back for a few more seconds,
and in those seconds she felt everything.
His thumb resting exactly on the seam of her dress, the heat of his palm,
the silent weight of being chosen there before an entire room.
When he moved his hand away, it was slow.
Rowina drew a breath.
You didn't need to.
I did, actually, he answered, without looking at her.
She knew what she was doing.
The rest of the night passed in waves.
Rowina won a small lot with the money she had, a pair of glass earrings no-one wanted.
Jago won nothing.
He just watched her from afar, from across the hall,
and every time she raised her eyes, he was already looking.
They returned to the mansion around midnight.
She went up to the guest room and stood for a long time in front of the open suitcase on the floor,
at the bottom of it, under two folded blouses, and a pair of old shoes.
Was the file.
Brown, no label, tied with a rubber band.
Rowina pulled it into her lap, sat on the rug and stayed looking.
She didn't open it.
She ran her thumb along the edge, drew a deep breath,
and returned the file to the bottom of the suitcase.
She folded the blouses over it with exaggerated care, as if covering it were enough to undo
what labour-neath.
A phone on the nightstand vibrated.
Rowina glanced sideways.
A missed call.
Then another.
Then a third one she watched arrive.
Pollis Vaughan's name blinking on the screen like a silent alarm.
She let it ring until it stopped.
She kept looking at the phone until the light went out.
When she lowered her head again, the phone vibrated a fourth time.
A fifth.
Rowina closed her eyes.
Across the corridor, someone walked slowly.
Bear feet on the wood.
She knew who steps they were, and she didn't open the door.
The phone kept.
Chapter 4 The File She Wouldn't Open.
ringing.
Pollis Vaughan's fifth call came just after dawn.
And this time, Rowina answered.
She was sitting on the floor of the guest room,
still in the wrinkled green dress.
The glass earrings in her lap.
The phone trembling in her hand for the sixth time.
The rug beneath her smelled of old lavender.
The kind of lavender that isn't perfume.
It's time.
You vanished, said Hollis without a greeting.
His voice had that measured calm that preceded fireings.
I haven't heard your voice in three weeks.
Don't give me behind schedule.
It's behind schedule.
That's not the point.
The point is the material.
Where is it?
I'm working.
You're not.
Rowina closed her eyes and rested her forehead on her knee.
The knee was cold through the wrinkled fabric.
Outside the garden hadn't quite woken up yet.
A shallow grey light spread across the window,
as if the day was still convincing itself to arrive.
Pollis.
Rowina.
He drew a deep breath on the other end of the line.
I backed you.
I bought the ticket.
Paid for the hotel the first weekend, kept your shift going with Marlo covering three
straight shifts.
I'm not a benefactor.
I'm an editor.
And an editor needs to deliver.
Either you send me something by Monday night or I'll have to make a decision
neither of us once.
She didn't answer right away.
Outside, a bird insisted on the same short note near the window.
And Rowina caught herself thinking about how Jago used to be late with the coffee,
whenever there was a bird nearby.
He'd stand out on the porch for a moment,
listening, the cup forgotten in his hand.
She shouldn't have noticed that.
She had noticed.
I heard you.
She said finally.
You didn't.
Hollis answered.
But you will.
Monday night, headline or resignation.
He hung up first.
Rowina kept looking at the phone for a length of time she couldn't measure.
The reflection of her own distorted face on the black screen.
She stood up slowly.
She walked to the suitcase which was half open on a wooden chair near the dresser.
She pulled the brown file out by the rubber band, sat down again on the rug,
and rested the file on her own thighs.
Her hands were still this time.
Stiller than she expected.
She untied the rubber band slowly.
She opened the first flap.
Clippings of balance sheets.
Photocopies Hollis had obtained from some discrete source.
Notes in small handwriting written by herself before she met Jago Quint.
In a gray, noisy newsroom where the coffee was bad,
and ambition still seemed enough to pay the bills.
Rowina read two lines of her own field notebook,
and didn't recognize the woman who had written that.
She closed the file.
She tied the rubber band again.
She put everything back at the bottom of the suitcase.
The partner's dinner was scheduled for that same night.
Neve came up in the late afternoon with a dress hanging from a velvet hanger.
Deep wine, straight neckline, sleeves to the elbow.
The fabric had a specific weight to the touch,
that weight of something chosen with attention.
Rowina looked at her without understanding.
From the master said Neve and set the hanger on the chair against the wall,
he asked me to leave it here.
He said the miss isn't obliged to wear it.
Rowina laughed without joy,
and if I don't wear it.
He won't ask why, said Neve,
with a half smile that didn't quite complete itself.
But he'll notice.
He notices.
She wore the dress.
She couldn't decide whether it was surrender or courage,
and she chose not to decide.
The mansion's dining room had 18 places,
and a table that was a vanished skating rink.
There were six partners, three wives,
Silas Ashford at one end in the same gray suit as always,
and the face of someone who has already seen far too much,
without being surprised by anything,
and you door a quint at the other end,
seated as though the seat had been built around her.
Rowina entered beside Jego.
She was introduced by him in a sentence that left no gap.
Rowina Pike, she's with me.
It wasn't a description.
It was a signature.
The dinner advanced through courses she barely tasted.
There was talk of an acquisition up north,
of a land auction near the river,
of a niece's wedding in Charleston.
Rowina answered when addressed and listened,
when not addressed.
The wine was too good to be wasted on anxiety,
so she drank slowly and kept her spine straight.
At some point between the second course and the third,
Jego's hand found hers on top of the white table cloth.
He didn't hold it halfway or hide it under the table.
He left his hand resting on top of her hand,
in full view of everyone,
and went on talking to the partner to his left,
as if the hand was some object he'd found along the way,
and decided to keep.
Silas noticed first.
Rowina saw the small flicker in the lawyer's eyes,
almost invisible,
followed by a throat clearing that made way for nothing.
Jodora noticed next.
The matriarch didn't take her eyes off her plate,
but her fork paused half a second in the air,
and resumed moving with a care Rowina had learned to interpret as reading.
Jodora read people.
She did it all the time,
without appearing to be doing it.
After coffee the partner's rose for cigars,
and the wives went off to another parlor.
Rowina went up alone.
In the corridor she crossed paths with Silas,
who carried a folder under his arm and a look she couldn't decipher,
the kind of look that holds more than one interpretation,
and gives away none.
Good night, Miss.
He said,
Good night, Mr. Ashford.
He seemed to want to say something more.
He weighed the moment, decided against it,
and went on down the corridor with the firm stride of someone with a set destination.
In the guest room, Rowina shut the door and leaned against it for a moment.
The wood was cold against her back through the fabric of the dress.
She thought about tearing up the notes,
she thought about calling Hollis and telling him the story didn't exist.
She thought about telling Jago everything that night,
with the wine still in her body and the courage of exhaustion.
She thought about doing none of the three things,
and leaving it all for the train back.
She went to the bathroom, took off her makeup with cold water and cotton,
put on a simple linen nightgown lay down on top of the bedspread,
and stared at the white-washed ceiling as the house grew quiet,
room by room.
She fell asleep without realizing it.
She was woken by the sound of the door.
There was no knock.
The door opened slowly, letting in a thin band of light from the corridor,
and Rowina saw against that light, the silhouette of Jago quint.
He didn't turn on the room's lamp.
He walked to the middle of the room and stopped,
and only then did she notice what was in his hands,
the file, brown, no label, no rubber band now.
Rowina sat up in the bed in a single motion.
The air left her chest in an exhalation that made no sound.
Help.
Silas, he said, without raising his voice,
he saw Odette prowling this corridor earlier.
He thought it best I checked before she did.
His voice was low.
It was calm.
It was empty of anything she could use to hold on to.
Jago looked at the file he was carrying,
leafed through a page she recognized without needing to look closely,
and put the page back in its place,
with a care that seemed in that moment,
the cruelest thing in the world.
Ballons sheets, he said,
copies of old contracts, a list of names with notes beside them.
I recognized at least three of the names.
He lifted his eyes to her.
This isn't an interview.
It isn't, Rowina answered,
because denying it would have been a worse insult.
He nodded slightly.
That was all.
A single precise nod that didn't judge,
and therefore weighed more than any judgment.
You came here for this.
I came here for this, she said,
and I didn't know I would stop coming here for it.
But I did stop weeks ago.
I haven't opened that file once since.
Here it doesn't matter, he cut in,
and even cutting in he kept his usual low tone.
You opened it yesterday, I heard you open it.
I thought you were closing a suitcase.
The silence settled between them,
with a specificity, Rowina couldn't fill,
and he didn't try to.
Jego, thank you for coming to Savannah,
he said, and that was the sentence that went through her from side to side.
Thank you for the weeks.
The interview is paid for, if you still want it.
I only asked that you leave tomorrow morning before my mother comes down for coffee.
She opened her mouth, closed it, opened it again.
Don't do this like this, like what?
Without yelling at me, he considered the sentence,
he took too long to answer the kind of delay that is an answer in itself.
If I yell you'll be able to think I'm still angry.
His voice found a note she had never heard in him,
too low to have a name.
I don't want you to think that.
I want you to leave knowing exactly what stayed behind.
It was worse than yelling.
It was worse than anything she could have predicted that week or in any week before it.
Jego set the file on the dresser near the door,
with a precision that seemed calculated to make no noise.
He didn't return it to her hand.
He didn't take it with him.
He left it there, in the middle of the way,
like an exposed piece of evidence, neither of them needed to examine any more.
Then he turned toward the door.
Leave tomorrow.
The door closed behind him with the most polite noise a door has ever produced in the entire world.
Rhoina remained sitting on the bed.
Her hands opened on the bed spread.
Her heart beating in a rhythm she didn't recognize as her own.
Outside in the corridor, his footsteps moved away slowly.
No hurry, no hesitation.
And at some point between her room and his room,
they stopped for a second, before continuing.
She didn't cry.
Not yet.
She kept looking at the file on top of the dresser,
like someone staring at an animal that had followed her from too far away,
to now pretend it was a stranger.
Outside the window, the garden of the Quint Mansion,
breathed the humid night, the smell of earth and jasmine rising with the breeze off the river.
Somewhere near the water, a real owl called out once.
Rhoina thought of the glass owl set with red stone,
tucked in a dark velvet box at the bottom of her bag,
and felt that this was the memory that would hurt most on the train the next day.
But chapter 5 killing the story.
Rain back left before 8, and Rhoina sat by the window,
because the aisle required looking at people head on,
and people that morning would have seen what she hadn't yet seen in the mirror.
She rested her forehead against the cold glass,
and stayed that way for a length of time she couldn't measure.
Savannah fell behind in pieces, a roof, a tower, a line of trees bent by the river wind,
and none of it hurt with the noise she had expected.
It hurt low. It hurt the way Jago had said,
thank you in the small hours, when she was expecting a shout,
anything with enough volume for her to push back against,
the file was still on top of the guest room dresser.
She hadn't even asked for it back, leaving it there felt fair.
In the sense that justice is what's left over when everything else surrenders.
She didn't cry on the train. She counted roof panels of cars,
counted poles, counted the times the conductor passed down the aisle dragging a coffee cart.
The smell of the machine coffee was cheap, and watery.
Nothing like what Jago had learned to make, and that idiotic detail was what came
closest to breaking her. She reached the grey city just before noon.
The station smelled of lubricant and cheap bread.
Rowena carried her suitcase like someone carrying a witness.
She cried in the newsroom bathroom.
It was a dry cry of two minutes.
Curled up in a stall with her hand over her mouth because Marlo Trent was on the other side of the door.
Tapping the tip of her shoe and speaking loudly to cover for her.
Come out of their pike. If you stay in there any longer,
Hollis is going to knock on the door and then I'm going to have to bite him.
Rowena laughed in the middle of the cry without meaning to.
It was an ugly sound but it worked.
She came out with her face washed. Marlo looked at her for a whole second,
without sarcasm for the first time in years.
There was something different in her friend's expression.
The shoulders quieter.
The way she stood still without her phone in her hand.
You okay? No. Rowena answered.
But I will be. Marlo squeezed her shoulder and her hand stayed there too long for a joke.
That was how Rowena understood her friend had guessed everything before asking.
The newsroom had that midday noise.
Keys, phones ringing two desks over.
Someone shouting a page number down the hall as if the whole building needed to know.
Hollis Vaughan lifted his eyes over his glasses the moment Rowena passed down the central aisle.
He didn't smile. He didn't ask how the trip had gone.
He simply pointed with his pen to the door of his office.
A short, habitual gesture.
The kind that allows no negotiation.
She went in. She shut the door behind her.
That office smelled of aged paper and coffee no one had the courage to throw out.
And there was a plant in the corner that had been dying for at least two months.
It's leaves drooping over the edge of the pot without anyone having noticed.
Hollis sat down his pen.
Headline, he said.
End of the day.
There's not going to be a headline.
Hollis blinked once.
He leaned back in his chair.
Say that again.
There's not going to be a headline Rowena repeated and her voice came out firm
of them she expected.
I'm not going to deliver what you asked for.
Not today, not next week, not ever.
You went there with a mission pike.
I did, and I came back without it.
Hollis looked at the desk for a moment.
When he raised his eyes, there was less anger than she'd imagined.
And more a kind of old disappointment, the kind of disappointment bosses carry from other
bosses before them, piled up over years in rooms exactly like that one.
You know what this means.
I do.
Rowena set a folded paper on the desk.
I'm handing this over before you have to say it.
Hollis picked up the paper.
He didn't open it.
Why?
He asked.
And the question came almost gentle, which frightened her more than an insult would have.
Rowena was silent for a second.
She thought of a pretty professional answer.
The kind that looks good in retrospect.
She gave up.
Because the story stopped existing, she said.
He stopped being a story.
And I don't know how to write about someone who became a person.
Hollis looked at her for a long time, with the expression of someone re-reading an equation that
doesn't add up, then he nodded once, almost imperceptibly.
Get out before I change my mind, he said.
And Pike, she stopped at the door.
You were good.
Rowena swallowed before answering.
I still am.
Just not for this.
She shut the door carefully.
Hollis was leaning against the corridor wall, waiting with two cups of machine coffee.
And she pushed one of the cups into Rowena's hand without ceremony, like someone handing over a
survival item.
Did you do it?
She asked.
I did.
Shit.
Marlo Blue on the coffee.
Welcome to the club of the dignified unemployed.
Rowena laughed.
It was a short, broken laugh, but it was a laugh.
They went down the stairs instead of the elevator.
On the sidewalk, the city was grey the way it had always been.
And Rowena looked at the buildings without any of the glow that Savannah painted on to even a
cloudy morning.
Something was missing from that sky.
The smell of Magnolia was missing.
The way the Savannah river appeared between two streets when no one expected it.
A strip of lead-coloured water that somehow made everything lighter was missing.
E was missing.
You're going back, Marlo said, without asking.
I am.
Will he take you back?
I don't know.
He will.
Marlo insisted looking off into the distance.
A man who sends for you three weeks in a row doesn't close a door for good.
He locks it.
It's different.
Rowena looked at her friend, and for an instant,
the world stopped spinning so fast.
Marlo.
What?
Thank you.
Get out of here before I cry, Pike.
It doesn't suit me.
Rowena took the night train and slept enough not to look devastated on arrival.
The car smelled of old fabric and rain, and she kept her face turned to the dark window
for much of the trip, watching her own reflection without being able to look away.
On Sunday morning, Savannah received the train with the sun coming in from the side.
And the whole station smelled of bakery and river breeze,
she took a taxi without stopping to think.
She went in through the front.
She rang the bell.
Feeling answered.
His eyes widened for half a second, before returning to normal trained.
Miss Pike, I need to talk to him.
He's in his office with guests.
I know.
Feeling hesitated.
Then he stepped aside.
Miss is quint arrived in our ego.
He said quietly, almost a warning.
And Miss Martian came along.
Rowena nodded.
Druid deep breath once and walked down the marble corridor.
Like someone walking to a trial she herself had scheduled.
The corridor was silent except for her own footsteps.
And their echo on the old tiles sounded too firm for the way she was feeling inside.
Jay goes office was in the west wing of the mansion, and the door was a jar.
She heard before she saw, the voice of Odette Martian, sweet, too loud,
that voice of someone who pretends to console and measures the effect in a mirror.
A necessary evil you'dora.
Truly, better to find out now than, Rowena opened the door before Odette finished.
The entire office went still.
Jay goes to behind the desk, dark jacket hands resting on the top.
You'dora seated in the green velvet armchair near the window,
back straight as ever, as if her posture were the last line of defense.
Silas leaning against the bookcase.
Neutral expression.
Eyes that recognized Rowena before the rest of his body did.
Odette on the sofa, glass in hand, a smile dressing her mouth until it froze when she saw
who had come in.
Jaygo didn't move.
Only his jaw tensed once.
Rowena said Silas almost automatically, trying to smooth things over.
Stay, Rowena asked, without taking her eyes off Jaygo.
All of you.
Stay.
Odette opened her mouth.
Rowena gave her no chance.
I came to tell the truth, she said.
All of it.
I'm not going to apologise first because an apology before the truth is an insult.
Odora raised an eyebrow.
Nothing more.
Rowena breathed.
Her voice came out firm, even though her hands trembled inside her jacket.
I came to Savannah with two missions.
The interview was one.
The other was to come back with material that would destroy the Quint family.
My editor wanted a scandal story, and I accepted because I needed the job.
I accepted believing I could separate the work from the charade.
She paused.
I couldn't.
Odette let out a low incredulous laugh.
No one joined her.
I brought the file, Rowena continued, and her voice didn't waver.
You already know I brought it.
It was found.
It was red.
And it was returned in the small hours of yesterday morning with a thank you
that hurt more than any shout would have.
She looked at Jaygo.
He didn't look away.
He didn't confirm.
His face was that of a man counting every word before deciding what to do with them.
I could have gone back to the newsroom, written what my editor wanted, saved my career.
A voice rose half a tone.
I didn't write it.
I killed the story this morning.
I resigned before he could fire me.
There's no story anymore.
There's no file anymore.
There's nothing left in that guest room that's of use to anyone.
She took a step forward just one.
And I didn't come here for forgiveness.
I came because if I didn't say this in front of everyone who watched the lie happen,
the truth would remain a private thing and the lie was public.
That's not fair.
Total silence.
Udora blinked once.
Slowly.
Like someone recalculating something she'd thought was settled.
O'Dette looked at her glasses if it had betrayed her.
I dropped the story.
Rowena said.
And her voice lowered again.
Almost soft.
Because he stopped being a story.
I couldn't write about a man who learned my coffee by heart.
She finished.
The hands were still trembling.
She let them tremble.
O'Dette rose first.
Her glass coming down hard on the side tray.
What a spectacle.
She said.
Seeking Jago's eyes.
You're not going to believe this are you?
Jago didn't answer O'Dette.
He looked at Rowena for a length of time no one there could count.
Then he pulled back his chair unhurried and stood up.
J.
Chapter 6 His laugh.
Go cross the office in a single stride.
It didn't seem like a stride it seemed like decision walking.
Rowena didn't step back but she held her breath in the middle of her chest
as if her body had forgotten how to do it.
He stopped half a meter from her.
He didn't touch her.
He just stood there.
His eyes fixed on her.
And there was something in that gaze Rowena couldn't name.
Neither anger nor relief.
Something that made her hold her own breath.
O'Dette.
He said without looking back.
Get out of my house.
The silence in the room had weight.
The kind of silence that makes people hold their breath without realizing.
Jago.
Now, his voice came out low.
Curtis.
The way he spoke to everyone.
And even so, no one in the room had any doubt.
O'Dette picked up her bag with rigid movements her fingers gripping the leather.
She didn't look at you, Dora.
The door slammed behind her with the thin noise of high heels
that had lost their audience.
Jago breathed once.
Then he looked at Rowena as if he were checking a calculation that had taken
far too long to add up.
I want you to hear this," he said.
Loud enough for siless and you Dora to hear every word.
And loud enough to carry through the open door and reach the corridor.
Where half a dozen of you Dora's guests pretended not to listen.
She stays.
With me.
And tomorrow, all of Savannah will hear it from my mouth before hearing it from anyone else's.
He paused for an instant, as if the sentence carried weight.
I'm done letting fear choose for me.
He raised his hand slowly.
He touched the tips of his fingers to her chin.
The touch has light as a question.
Stay.
Rowena felt her eyes sting.
She didn't look away.
I'll stay.
Silas let out the air he'd been holding.
Udora didn't move.
But something in the line of her shoulders gave way a millimeter.
It was the matriarch who broke the silence at last,
with that voice that never missed its tone even on hard days.
Out of here, she said, addressing neither of them in particular.
All of you I need to think.
Rowena and Jago left together.
Silas closed the door with the care of someone who knows
that a well-closed door is sometimes worth an entire contract.
In the corridor Jago held Rowena's hand.
That was all.
He didn't kiss her.
He didn't speak.
He just held it.
His fingers laced through hers with a quiet firmness.
Unlike anything she'd known in him until then.
He let her out onto the back porch.
The one facing the Savannah River.
The late afternoon sun fell gold and on the water,
tinting the surface copper and amber,
and the smell of the garden came heavy with magnolia wet from the night before.
Somewhere in the middle of the garden, an insect sang the same repeated note,
Rhythmic in No Harry.
You killed the story, said Jago, looking at the river.
It wasn't a question.
I did.
You lost your job.
He turned his head slowly,
and his profile against the late afternoon light had a hardness
Rowena couldn't read in full.
She could only read the part that mattered.
I'm going to help you find another one, he said.
One you choose.
Not one I choose for you.
Rowena laughed softly.
The laugh came out choked.
A little crooked.
The way laughs happen when the body doesn't quite know yet,
whether it's crying or smiling.
You said choose and for you.
In the same sentence, quint.
Careful.
He closed his eyes for a second.
When he opened them, his shoulders had dropped half a finger,
and his mouth gave way in a near smile Rowena had never seen there.
I'll learn.
It was there behind them that the porch door opened.
Yudora came out without announcing herself.
She didn't look at Jago first.
She looked at Rowena, and there was in that gaze and a
preysal different from the earlier ones without the usual scalpel.
The matriarch crossed the stone floor,
and stopped in front of her.
Up close in the low rosy light of that afternoon,
Yudora seemed smaller than on the night of the ball.
Smaller and older and less sharp,
as if she'd left her armor hanging on the inside.
Rowena waited for the blow that didn't come.
Yudora extended her hand.
She touched Rowena's arm lightly.
A thumb sliding once over the sleeve of the jacket.
A gesture so restrained it could have gone unnoticed, but it didn't.
Then she turned her head and looked into the hall.
The wide door was open.
And from there you could see the empty chair.
The one that had always been near the window of the main hall.
Its back turned slightly to the side,
as if someone had just stood up and would come back at any moment.
Yudora kept looking long enough for the moment to grow heavy.
You have his laugh, she murmured.
Rowena didn't understand.
She felt her heart skipped a whole beat,
but she didn't understand.
Yudora didn't explain.
She just squeezed her arm once very lightly,
and went back inside.
The door closed behind her without a sound.
As if the house were protecting that secret too.
Rowena looked at Jago.
His jaw was locked.
His gaze fixed on some point of the river
that no longer belonged to that afternoon.
Jago.
Later, he said quietly.
Please, she didn't insist.
She stored the question in the same place where she stored all the details
that didn't yet have a frame.
She kept storing, because that was what she knew how to do.
And because not every detail asked to be opened on the same day it appeared.
Yudora back inside at the end of the afternoon.
When the river was already dark blue,
and the mansions lights were beginning to come on one by one,
as if the house were breathing.
They ate little.
No one spoke much.
Silas passed down the corridor once,
nodded agreeding, and vanished off towards the library.
Nive brought T without asking, and disappeared before anyone could thank her.
Then it was Jago who extended his hand.
Rowen were accepted.
They went up the main staircase together.
Her footsteps echoed on the marble.
His almost didn't.
He always stepped as if he didn't want to take up more space than necessary.
Half way up the stairs he stopped.
He turned her slowly.
His hand displayed against the nape of her neck,
and pressed his forehead to hers for a length of time that belonged to no clock.
I don't know how to do this right.
He said, too low to be anything but honest.
No one does.
He laughed.
It was a short laugh almost startled.
The kind of laugh that escapes before a person decides to let it out.
Rowen restored that laugh too.
She stored it the same way she stored everything that mattered.
Without noting it down, without recording it.
Just letting it settle deep.
They kept going up.
At the top the corridor had that late night mansion silence,
that isn't the silence of emptiness.
It's the silence of care.
The door to his room was a jar.
He pushed it with the back of his hand.
A casual gesture that contained a whole decision.
She went in.
He went in behind her.
The door closed slowly.
The kitchen.
The next morning.
Smelled of coffee and warm bread.
The Savannah light came in from the side through the high window,
cut into bands by the frames,
and fell gold and over the white tablecloth,
over the cups, over the still warm loaves that
neither had left in a basket,
and disappeared before anyone could thank her.
That was how Nive did things,
beforehand and without making noise.
Roena sat with her legs crossed in the chair,
the cup warming both her hands.
Jego sat beside her, so close that his knee touched hers under the table.
He didn't speak.
He just extended his hand over the white tablecloth and waited.
Roena placed hers on top.
They stayed that way.
Unhurried.
While the heat of the coffee rose in a thread of steam between them.
She looked at the cup.
He had made the coffee the way she liked it.
Two dashes of sugar.
More milk than any barista would accept.
He'd made it without asking.
She smiled into the cup and said nothing,
because she didn't need to.
From the other side of the kitchen,
through the arch doorway you could see the corner of the main hall.
And from there you could see the empty chair near the window.
Its back was still turned slightly to the side,
as it had been the afternoon before,
as on every morning Roena had spent in that house.
No one had moved the chair during the night.
No one had occupied it as far as she knew.
On any of the times she'd been there.
Alaf.
Someone you'd orah had known.
Someone Jago had known.
A name the house had decided to stop saying,
guarded with such care that even the silence around it had shape.
Roena opened her mouth.
Jago.
He lifted his eyes from the coffee.
He didn't answer.
Yesterday she said,
and her voice came out soft, calibrated,
so as not to break that morning.
Your mother said something.
About a laugh.
Jago's hand overhears tightened a little.
That was all.
A small involuntary squeeze the kind that happens before a person decides to do it.
Boo!
She didn't finish.
Not because he interrupted her with any word.
It was the silence that did the work.
A whole round silence that filled the table and the coffee,
and the savanna light falling between them,
as if the sun too were waiting.
He looked at the cup,
then at her hand under his hand.
Then for a very brief instant at the empty chair far off
golden in the morning.
He didn't answer.
Roena felt then with a cold and new certainty
that there was an entire story living inside that house,
not in the walls or the old furniture,
but in the people who lived in it and carried it without saying the name.
She had just knocked on the right door.
The door was not going to open that morning.
She stored the question in her throat.
The way she had always stored what didn't yet have its time.
She closed her hand around his.
Outside a bird sang a high note and flew away.
The empty chair remained empty,
golden in the sun,
occupying the place it had always occupied,
and she understood without anyone needing to say it,
that that morning of peace was only the beginning of something else.
Hey Roen here, that's it for Book 1, but guess what?
Book 2 is already done.
You can grab access to it for just a small fee.
Six months later, she woke up every day in Jago's arms.
In the dream house he had built for the two of them.
Slow kisses, whispered promises,
his body fitted to hers as if the world outside didn't exist.
Until the bodyguard started following her into the more bathroom.
Until he deleted the job offer that had come for her,
without saying a word.
Until the phone rang and a name,
a name no one in that family dare to speak,
may Jago go pale, hang up mid-sentence,
and lie with his eyes still glazed with dread.
She saw the raw fear there.
The same fear he had been hiding since the night they kissed for the first time,
pretending it was only a game.
The old secret between them was no longer a shadow.
It was an open wound.
Capable of explaining the controlling man Jago had become,
and of destroying forever the man she had loved.
Now she trembled alone in the luxurious bedroom,
tasting the bitter flavor of betrayed trust.
And what if the past he had locked away with guilt
was greater than the love he swore he felt.
And what if opening that door made him hate her forever?
And what if the beautiful golden cage was the only thing still keeping the two of them together?
Like I said, that was just a taste of book two.
To watch it uncensored, just click on the first link here in the pinned comment.
I'll see you on the other side in a few seconds.
Remember, just click on the first link down here in the comments.
And book two, complete, with no ads or interruptions,
will already be available for you.
It's very simple.
Book two is something I'm loving making,
and you're loving it too, so I promise there will be more.
It's where you find increasingly spicy stories,
a true dark romance, and precisely because this version is getting more and more heated,
the video isn't well accepted publicly on YouTube.
This closed environment is where I can actually share my essence,
and where I feel free to do my best work for you.
More news coming soon, I'll be waiting for you on the other side.
Now unfortunately, a lot of people have been downloading our audio,
effectively copying the entire story, and just re-uploading it to YouTube.
If you want to watch the original story, and be the first to get the next ones,
search for my stories by Rowan on YouTube for the best billionaire and CEO romance content.
Remember, the official channel is my stories by Rowan on YouTube,
and the my stories platform. I'll be waiting for you there. Love Rowan.