I've heard stories, but I never
imagined it would be like this.
This place holds secrets.
I know it.
She only needed one interview.
Jago Quint was the billionaire
no one could reach, and that
story could save her career.
So she accepted the most
dangerous deal of her life,
pretending
to be his girlfriend for one
night.
It was supposed to be simple.
Walk into the ball convinces
family and walk out with the
answers she
needed, but when
Jago's mother demanded proof of
love in front of everyone, she
did exactly what she
shouldn't have.
She kissed Jago.
And that kiss, which was only
supposed to be a lie,
started to feel far too real.
Chapter 1.
The Impossible Interview.
His room smelled of reheated
coffee and old paper, and
Rowina Pike had already drunk
three
cups before nine in the morning.
The gray light coming through
the window gave every face there
the same shade of exhaustion.
The kind of fatigue that doesn't
come from one bad night's sleep,
but from months piled
one on top of another.
She knew, hers was no different.
She held her folder against her
chest, and crossed the narrow
aisle between the desks,
greeting with a Kurt Nord anyone
who looked up.
Hollis Vaughn was waiting for
her with his elbows planted on
the desk, glasses pushed
to the tip of his nose.
The editor had a peculiar way of
looking at people, as if he were
checking whether they were
worth their own salary.
Rowina shut the door behind her,
ignored the chair he didn't
offer, and sat down without
waiting for an invitation.
I need the interview Pike.
Hollis didn't waste time on
introductions, and I need
something else too.
If you're about to tell me you
need a photo of Quint without
his jacket, I'm walking
out of this room right now.
I need a file.
The sentence landed in the
middle of the desk, like
something too heavy for the
furniture.
Rowina raised an eyebrow,
waiting for him to refraise to
apologise to turn it into a
joke.
Hollis did none of that.
He simply laced his fingers, and
kept looking at her, as if he
were collecting on an old
debt.
Proof, he added, that that
empire is hiding something it
shouldn't be hiding.
Everyone hides something Pike.
You just need to find out what?
You want me to get inside the
home of the most closed off
family in the south.
Land the interview no one's
managed to land in 10 years, and
still walk out of there with
compromising material.
I'm telling you that your job
here depends on it.
She didn't answer right away.
She sat staring at the coffee
stain on the rim of his mug.
Calculating how much of next
month's salary was already
committed to rent, how much was
still owed on her mother's bill.
The window behind Hollis let in
the muffled noise of the street.
A horn, a quick step.
The city running nonstop while
she sat there deciding how far
she was willing to go.
Then she nodded once, short,
like someone signing a contract
they haven't yet read.
Malo Trent intercepted her in
the hallway with two fresh
coffees, and a smile that was
already a question.
Malo was a copy editor, a
colleague of three years, and
the only person in the newsroom
who understood when Rowine
needed silence, and when she
needed noise, you look like
someone
who just sold her soul.
Malo remarked, handing over the
hotter cup.
Was it for much?
It was for next month's rent.
Malo laughed, a short laugh, cut
off halfway by the awareness
that the joke was worth
more to herself than to Rowine.
She leaned her shoulder against
Rowine as they walked down the
hallway, and for a moment,
Rowine felt like dropping
everything right there, walking
out the front door and never
coming back.
She didn't.
She drank the coffee until it
burned her tongue.
After noon came quickly, and
with it a note left at the front
desk.
No sender, just her name on the
front of the envelope, written
in black pen and handwriting
that wasn't a friend, slanted
controlled letters, each one in
its exact place.
Rowine had turned the envelope
over twice before opening it,
inside just an address and
a time.
Nothing more.
The office it pointed to was
three blocks away, in a discreet
building she had never noticed,
despite having walked past it
hundreds of times.
The sign at the entrance simply
read Ashford and Associates, in
letters too small to
draw attention.
Rowine aclimed the steps with
her folder still pressed against
her chest, and greeted
the receptionist with the name
that was on the note.
The man who received her was
younger than she expected.
Tall, navy, suit, no tie, with
that kind of discretion only old
money teachers.
He extended his hand and
introduced himself as Silas
Ashford, the Quint family's
lawyer,
a friend of Jago's since their
boarding school days.
The information came without
fanfare, the way someone hands
over a business card.
Have a seat, Miss Pike.
His voice had the same tone as
the handwriting on the envelope.
I'll be brief because the
proposal is brief.
I'm curious.
Mr. Quint agrees to grant a
two-hour interview to your
publication.
No restrictions on subject
matter.
Except one.
Silas made a minimal pause.
The kind of pause lawyers used
to let the client swallow the
next piece of information.
In return, you would attend the
family's Gallaboll in Savannah
as his companion on Friday.
One night, just one.
Rowine elapsed before her brain
authorized her mouth.
Companion.
That's the word he preferred.
And what word didn't he prefer?
The corner of Silas's mouth
moved half a millimeter, almost
the beginning of a smile,
but nothing followed through.
He slid a black envelope across
the desk, sealed, with her name
written on the front,
in the same slanted, controlled
handwriting as the first note.
Letters she now recognized
without effort,
and which definitely did not
belong to Silas.
The rules are in there.
One read is enough.
The expects an answer today.
Rowine looked at the black
envelope for too long.
She thought about the rent.
She thought about the look on
Holasis face.
She thought about the old
photograph of the reclusive
billionaire
that had circulated through the
papers forever.
Always the same profile of a
clenched jaw.
Always the same gaze that didn't
invite anyone to stay.
She tucked the envelope into her
folder without opening it.
Tell him I'll be in Savannah on
Friday.
Silas nodded like someone who
already knew the answer before
the question.
He rose, shook her hand again,
and walked her to the door with
practice courtesy.
Before closing the handle, he
said almost without voice.
He's not what the press writes,
that's all.
Rowine didn't ask what he meant.
She preferred not to know yet.
Marla was waiting for her on the
street with a cigarette that
pretended to be lit.
The kind of theatre she used as
an excuse to loiter on corners.
Rowine handed over the black
envelope without ceremony.
A friend turned the object over
in her hand,
studied the seal with more
attention than necessary, and
gave it back.
Don't open it now, Marla said,
open it on the train.
It's prettier that way.
Pretty ya.
Do you want to be someone else's
story or make history?
If it's the second, you open it
on the train alone,
and you cry if you need to cry
without anyone seeing.
It's the least you deserve.
Rowine laughed and the laugh
pulled some of the weight off
her back.
She rested her forehead on
Marla's shoulder for a short
second.
Just enough to remember she
still had a friend in that grey
city,
and then she went home to pack.
The station was too crowded for
her taste.
Rowine had dragged her luggage
between hurried bodies,
bought a sandwich she wasn't
going to eat, and settled by the
window of the car.
The seats smelled of dust and
warm synthetic leather.
That smell of a place where many
people have passed without
leaving a trace.
She sat staring at the tracks
for a while,
before taking the black envelope
out of the inner pocket of her
bag.
The seal gave way with a dry
sound.
Inside, three folded sheets.
The first two carried
instructions written with almost
legal precision.
Times, names she should
memorize,
clothes that would be delivered
to the hotel.
What to say if anyone asked how
long they had known each other,
Rowine erred them with the same
attention she gave to story
contracts,
mentally noting every detail,
every gap between the lines.
The third sheet was smaller, a
single line written by hand,
unsigned.
Don't smile at anyone like you
believe it.
Only smile when I'm looking.
She read it three times.
She put it away again.
She looked out the window as the
train picked up speed and the
city opened into suburb,
then countryside.
There nothing.
And she couldn't decide whether
that was an order, a warning, or
a request.
The train arrived in Savannah in
the late afternoon.
The air changed before she even
stepped onto the platform.
Warmer, denser,
laden with a sweet perfume she
couldn't yet name.
Magnolia maybe.
Or something that grew near
water.
Rowine across the station with
her folder under her arm,
looking for the driver who would
be waiting with her name on a
sign.
She found the dark car outside,
a man in a suit opening the back
door without ceremony.
Before getting in, she looked
one last time at the city's
skyline and saw in the distance.
The high roof of the quint
mansion cut against the sky that
was beginning to turn orange.
Too big, too old.
The kind of house that doesn't
invite you in.
It absorbs you.
Rowine sat on the leather seat,
rested her head against the cold
glass,
and pressed the black envelope
against her lap,
like someone clutching a
boarding pass to another
country.
She took the sheet out one more
time.
Only smile when I'm looking.
She re-read it, folded it, put
it away.
The car started up,
and the streets of Savannah
began to pass by outside like a
borrowed set,
with the moss heavy trees and
the old houses that each guarded
their own version of a secret.
And for the first time since
Holly's Vaughn had added the
word file,
Rowine a pike wondered,
whether she could go home as the
same person who had boarded the
train.
Chapter 2, a three second kiss.
Who tell sweet was bigger than
her entire apartment,
with a soft smell of jasmine
that seemed built into the
walls.
Rowine looked at herself in the
oval mirror for a long time,
adjusting the wine-colored silk
dress they had left hanging
behind the door.
The fabric fell effortlessly.
The kind of piece that only
existed when someone paid for it
without thinking twice.
The driver knocked at the door
at the exact time indicated in
the envelope.
Rowine went down,
crossed the lobby under stairs
she pretended not to notice,
and found the car waiting at the
curb.
The back door opened before she
touched the handle,
and the first thing she saw
inside was the impeccable crease
of dark trousers,
running down to a pair of
polished black shoes.
Jago Quint was seated on the
other side of the seat,
with one knee slightly apart
from the other,
hands resting on his own thighs.
He didn't stand, didn't extend
his hand.
He merely tilted his chin and
inch toward the empty spot
beside him,
and waited.
Rowine got in, adjusted her
skirt with a quick gesture,
and shut the door with more
force than necessary.
He noticed.
She saw that he noticed.
Neither of them commented.
Good evening, Miss Pike.
His voice was lower than she had
imagined from any interview
she'd ever read.
A voice that didn't rise because
it didn't need to.
Rowine returned her face and
looked at him full on for the
first time,
and had the displeasure of
confirming that the portraits
published over the years did
him no justice.
In person, he was a sculpture of
a straight jaw,
dark hair combed back with
calculated carelessness,
and eyes that decided the
temperature of the room before
saying anything at all.
Good evening, Mr. Quint.
Jago will do.
Then Rowine will do.
He nodded almost imperceptibly,
the car started up, and for a
while the two of them sat in
silence.
Rowine noticed his hands resting
on his knees,
long fingers, a silver watch
with no visible brand.
She also noticed that the seat
between them held a thin leather
folder,
closed, with one corner leaning
against the glass.
Details.
She collected details.
Are the rules clear?
He asked without turning his
face.
Crystal.
Any questions?
One.
Rowine awaited until he finally
turned his gaze to her.
How long do you intend for this
night to last?
As long as necessary, that's not
an answer.
It's the only one I have.
He looked forward again and
Rowine accepted defeat in that
round without arguing.
She kept watching his profile
against the dark window.
The hard line of his jaw, the
way his thumb pressed against
his own knee in a steady rhythm,
like someone counting something
inside himself.
She stored the gesture in her
memory, and said nothing.
The Quint mentioned appeared at
the end of the avenue of tall
trees,
lit from outside like a theatre
set.
Rowine drew a deep breath before
the car stopped.
Jago got out first.
Went around the vehicle and
opened her door with a courtesy
that sounded more rehearsed than
sincere.
He offered his arm.
She accepted.
His palm brushed briefly against
her hand as he helped her
position herself,
and the temperature changed.
Don't smile at anyone like you
believe it, he murmured.
Barely moving his lips as they
climb the steps.
You already warned me in
writing.
I'm reinforcing it.
The main hall swallowed them the
moment the door opened.
Rowine has smelled it before she
saw anything.
Magnolia and old money.
Exactly as Silas had said in the
instruction note.
The white walls rose high to a
ceiling of worked stucco,
and everywhere there were
antique chandeliers spreading a
honey-colored light over the
guests.
Long dresses, emerald chocas,
men in black tuxedoes,
greeting each other without
enthusiasm.
Jago introduced her to three
couples in a row,
always with the same assembled
sentence.
My companion for the evening,
Rowine a pike.
No complicated surnames.
No deer.
No love.
Rowine a smile in just the right
measure.
Answered questions in just the
right measure.
And noticed everything.
She noticed that he avoided the
terrace.
Twice a waiter passed offering
to take guests out to the
outdoor area.
And both times Jago declined,
with a minimal gesture of his
chin,
without even looking at the
glass door.
She also noticed that his gaze
had one point,
tripped over an empty chair near
the window.
A chair upholstered in dark
green velvet,
slightly set apart from the rest
of the arrangement,
as if it belonged to someone who
used to sit there and hadn't
arrived yet.
He looked away quickly.
Rowineerstorted.
What an unlikely evening.
The voice came from behind her
sweetest syrup heated too much.
Rowine returned and found a
woman with red hair pinned in a
low bun,
an emerald green dress,
a smile that didn't reach her
eyes.
Jago stiffened beside her.
Odeit, he greeted her without
warmth.
Jago.
Odeitmachand extended her hand
to Rowine,
palm down,
the gesture of someone expecting
reverence,
and the companion.
How interesting.
What do you do, dear?
I write.
Ah.
Odeit seemed to decide something
in silence.
How brave of him to bring you
here.
Brave of me to agree to come.
Odeit laughed.
A short note that contained
nothing of laughter.
Then she moved off with a wave
of her fingers,
leaving behind a trail of
expensive perfume.
Jago rested his hand at the
small of Rowine's back
for just a second,
a gesture of ownership that
wasn't affection.
Then he withdrew it.
You didn't need to provoke her.
He remarked.
Low.
I did, actually.
He didn't answer.
But the corner of his mouth
moved a millimeter,
and Rowine arrested it as if it
were the headline of the month.
It wasn't a smile yet.
It was close.
The silence in the hall changed
texture
before she understood why.
It was as if the air had drawn
back a few inches,
and everybody there in Unison
had turned their heads in the
same direction.
Rowine followed the others gaze,
and saw you door a quint
entering through the main door.
The matriarch didn't need to
announce herself.
A long black dress, a pearl
necklace that fell to the middle
of her chest,
gray hair pinned with a rigidity
that allowed no discussion.
She crossed the hall without
greeting anyone,
and stopped before her son and
his companion,
with the expression of someone
appraising merchandise.
Good evening, mother, said Jago.
You'dora didn't answer her son.
She turned her pale eyes to
Rowina,
and examined her from shoes to
hairstyle,
with a surgical calm.
Then she stepped half a step
closer,
and the voice that came out of
her was low,
but sharp enough to cut the
entire hall.
I don't see love here, my son.
The silence closed around the
three of them.
Rowina felt Jago's body
stiffened beside her,
his shoulders rising half an
inch.
Yudora stayed put, chin raised
waiting.
Proof said the matriarch.
If it's true, prove it.
The entire hall turned, heads
lifted from champagne glasses,
conversations ceased,
waiters stopped where they
stood.
Rowina felt the weight of the
whole hall falling on her and
Jago at the same time.
He locked up.
She saw that he locked up.
His thumb stopped counting on
his own hip,
his jaw hardened,
and for a whole second, no
decision came out of his body.
Rowina decided for him.
She raised her hand took his
face by the side and pulled.
His mouth met hers with a
hesitation of someone who hadn't
rehearsed this scene,
and for an instant, Rowina
thought he wouldn't respond.
Then his breath faltered.
She felt the falter,
felt the air caught halfway up
his chest,
felt his hand rise by reflex to
her back and settle between her
shoulder blades,
with a pressure that didn't
belong to the charade.
The kiss was supposed to last a
second.
It lasted three.
Maybe more.
Rowina lost count somewhere
between the moment he tilted his
head a little to the side,
and the moment she herself
forgot there was a hall around
them.
When they pulled apart, she
opened her eyes first.
He took half a second longer,
and what Rowina saw on his face
when he finally looked back,
was the same thing she felt
inside,
and which she wasn't prepared to
name yet.
Udora stepped back half a step.
She adjusted her pearl necklace
with a calculated carelessness,
and the corner of her mouth drew
a line that wasn't a smile but
pretended to be.
Good.
Mermaid the matriarch.
I hope to see you again many
times.
Many.
She turned on her heels and
moved off.
The hall little by little began
to breathe again.
Conversations returned like a
discreet murmur.
Waters moved.
Someone laughed in the distance
at something that wasn't funny.
Rowina kept looking at Jago.
His hand was still on her back
forgotten there,
in no hurry to leave.
He took his time pulling it
back.
When he did, his fingers passed
slowly over the silk of the
dress,
like someone memorizing a path
they might need to retrace
later.
Across the hall Odec-Marshon
watched them with a glass in her
hand,
and her smile was now a
different one.
Rowina registered it.
She already knew, without
needing a warning,
that that woman would want
payback.
Jago leaned in very slightly,
and spoke close to her ear so
low that only she could hear.
You owe me an explanation.
For the kiss?
For the length of the kiss.
Rowina didn't answer.
She didn't know the answer yet.
She took the glass away to her,
drank a sip she didn't even feel
go down,
and looked again at the empty
chair near the window.
Someone, at some point, had sat
in it.
Someone who now was no longer
there,
and Rowina Pike, who had
collected details since
childhood,
understood that the most
important story of that night,
had nothing to do with the
reason Hollis Vaughan had sent
her there.
Chapter 3, Coffee with No
Recorder.
The morning after the ball
arrived without ceremony,
the Savannah Sun came through
the gaps in the curtain of the
guest room,
at the Quint Mansion with an
almost impolite insistence,
and Rowina Pike opened her eyes
before she remembered exactly
where she was.
It took a whole instant for the
high ceiling,
the carved footboard, and the
thick silence of the house to
organize themselves in her head.
Only then did the kiss come
back.
It came back first through her
lip.
Then through the nape of her
neck,
then through her stomach.
Three seconds that now carried
the weight of biography.
She sat on the edge of the bed
and looked at her own hands.
They were cold.
Someone had left a coffee tray
on the sideboard beside the
door,
during the night probably,
because the cup was no longer
steaming.
Beside it a short note, written
by hand in a hand writing she
recognized at once,
garden, whenever you can.
Jay Rowina re-read the note
twice just to prove to herself
that it hadn't unsettled her.
It didn't stick.
The garden was at the back of
the house, far from the main
hall.
She noticed that as a small
paleide housekeeper,
let her down a corridor of
portraits.
The woman introduced herself as
neve,
lightly squeezed Rowina's arm
and said,
in an accent from rural Georgia,
that Mr. Jego was already
waiting.
There was warmth in her voice
but also scrutiny.
Rowina smiled with her mouth
closed and asked nothing.
Jego Quint was standing near an
old rose bush with his back to
the house.
White shirt sleeves folded to
the elbow,
hair still wet from his shower.
He turned when he heard the
gravel and for a second,
just one, his eyes met hers
unguarded,
without their usual controlled
gleam.
Then his jaw firmed up again.
Did you sleep?
As much as I could, she
answered,
the house makes noises.
It does. He pointed with his
chin toward a cast iron bench.
Sit with me.
We need to work out what comes
next.
Rowina obeyed, but chose to sit
in profile knees turned outward.
A small defense he noticed.
He said nothing.
You have the interview, Jego
began,
his voice low and chosen word by
word.
That's still standing,
but last night raised an issue I
didn't foresee.
My mother didn't believe it
until the kiss.
Maybe she believed it afterward.
If you disappear tomorrow,
she'll get suspicious again.
And I'll have three candidates
on the table by Sunday.
You're asking me for more days.
I'm asking for weeks.
Rowina swallowed the small shock
and breathed through her mouth
before answering.
Weeks of what?
Appearances.
A dinner here and event there.
Enough for Savannah to believe
you're the woman who finally got
into this house.
He paused.
Same payment, same interview.
Just a longer timeline.
There was logic in the proposal.
And there was a trap.
She knew both.
And if I refuse,
you get the interview anyway.
He said without hesitating.
We agreed on something and I
don't undo what's agreed.
That was what disarmed her.
Not the proposal.
The resolution of the proposal.
Rowina bit the inside of her
cheek.
Looked at the nearest rose
counted to three and said yes.
He didn't smile.
He just nodded slightly, like
someone closing her claws.
But when she stood up to go back
into the house,
his hand brushed her back for
half a second,
had a spot below her shoulder
blade.
And lingered an instant longer
than any contract required.
She stored the gesture alongside
the others.
She was already collecting.
The following weeks arrived
slowly,
and without a truce.
Rowina began to split herself
between the newsroom
where Marlo covered her shifts
with increasingly irritated
humour,
and the streets of Savannah,
where she learned there were
neighborhoods where the air
smelled of wet
Jasmine and others where it only
smelled of hoarded money.
Jego always sent for her at the
station,
with the same driver and always
in the same car.
He waited for her inside, in the
back seat,
shoulder leaning against the
opposite door.
One Tuesday, he took her to an
antique's fair under the oaks of
the old
Rowina stopped in front of a
tray of loose pendants,
and picked up one shaped like a
crooked owl.
Half green with age, set with
ridiculous red stones.
It's ugly, she said, smiling at
the object as if it were an
accomplice.
It is, Jego agreed.
She put the pendant back on the
tray.
She didn't ask for it.
Didn't haggle.
Didn't look at it again.
Half an hour later, when they
were heading back to the car,
he passed the dark velvet box
into her hand without any
ceremony,
and Rowina stood in the middle
of the sidewalk,
holding the crooked owl as if it
were a live animal.
You didn't haggle, she remarked.
No, he opened the car door for
her.
I knew what it was worth to you.
It was that day that Rowina
didn't turn on the recorder for
the entire afternoon.
She sat with Jego in his office
on the 13th floor of a glass
building in downtown savanna,
and they talked about things no
interview called for.
A cousin he had never saw.
A book she had read 12 times in
her teams.
A specific smell of the coffee
her mother used to make.
Jego poured her coffee that
afternoon in a way she hadn't
taught him.
Half a spoon of sugar, a splash
of milk.
Very hot.
Rowina looked at the cup, looked
at him, and didn't ask how he
knew.
Neeve let the answer slip a week
later in the mansions kitchen,
while drying a crystal glass
with the attention of someone
handling something bigger than a
glass.
He's been sleeping better since
you've been coming.
The housekeeper didn't look at
Rowina as she said it.
It's not a compliment, it's an
observation.
Rowina laughed softly without
breath to answer.
Do you want to know something
miss?
Neeve continued, putting the
glass away.
It's been a long time since
anyone asked him how his day
was.
He would be grateful, even if he
didn't know how to thank you.
Rowina's hand trembled slightly
on the handle of her mug.
She set the mug down on the
marble with doubled care.
The charity event took place on
a Thursday.
It was an auction in aid of a
children's hospital in a vaulted
ceiling tall,
where the candleabras seemed too
heavy for the wire that held
them.
Rowina wore a dark green dress
borrowed from Marlo's sister,
and Jago appeared at her side at
the entrance, as if he'd matched
the exact time to his own watch.
Odec Marshaar arrived 20 minutes
later.
Rowina saw her approach from the
other side of the hall,
greeting people with thin
kisses.
A champagne coloured dress
moving like liquid.
Odec stopped in front of Rowina,
looked her up and down with a
smile too polite to be polite,
and said in a tone that carried
through the three nearest
people,
you hold up well dear.
A borrowed dress in a hall of
this caliber isn't for just
anyone.
I hope the night is kind to you.
The air in the hall became
specific.
Two women near the buffet
stopped chewing.
Rowina felt the blood rise up
her neck and choose between
turning into fury
and turning into dignity.
Before she could decide, Jago's
hand touched the small of her
back.
Firm, without theatrical
possession, just presence,
and he took half a step forward,
shoulder pressed against hers.
Odec, he said, and his voice was
no longer lower than usual,
only stripped of anything
amiable.
If you have any doubts about the
woman I came with, put those
doubts to me directly.
Rowina owes you no explanation
about where she buys any dress.
Neither do you.
Odec parted her lips, and
something inside her smile gave
way for half a second,
before recomposing.
Now touchy Jago, it was a
compliment.
It wasn't.
He didn't raise his tone, he
didn't need to.
Two people nearby rediscovered a
sudden fascination with their
own shoes.
Odec nodded, murmured a phrase
about finding a friend and with
Drew.
Jago didn't move his hand from
Rowina's back for a few more
seconds,
and in those seconds she felt
everything.
His thumb resting exactly on the
seam of her dress, the heat of
his palm,
the silent weight of being
chosen there before an entire
room.
When he moved his hand away, it
was slow.
Rowina drew a breath.
You didn't need to.
I did, actually, he answered,
without looking at her.
She knew what she was doing.
The rest of the night passed in
waves.
Rowina won a small lot with the
money she had, a pair of glass
earrings no-one wanted.
Jago won nothing.
He just watched her from afar,
from across the hall,
and every time she raised her
eyes, he was already looking.
They returned to the mansion
around midnight.
She went up to the guest room
and stood for a long time in
front of the open suitcase on
the floor,
at the bottom of it, under two
folded blouses, and a pair of
old shoes.
Was the file.
Brown, no label, tied with a
rubber band.
Rowina pulled it into her lap,
sat on the rug and stayed
looking.
She didn't open it.
She ran her thumb along the
edge, drew a deep breath,
and returned the file to the
bottom of the suitcase.
She folded the blouses over it
with exaggerated care, as if
covering it were enough to undo
what labour-neath.
A phone on the nightstand
vibrated.
Rowina glanced sideways.
A missed call.
Then another.
Then a third one she watched
arrive.
Pollis Vaughan's name blinking
on the screen like a silent
alarm.
She let it ring until it
stopped.
She kept looking at the phone
until the light went out.
When she lowered her head again,
the phone vibrated a fourth
time.
A fifth.
Rowina closed her eyes.
Across the corridor, someone
walked slowly.
Bear feet on the wood.
She knew who steps they were,
and she didn't open the door.
The phone kept.
Chapter 4 The File She Wouldn't
Open.
ringing.
Pollis Vaughan's fifth call came
just after dawn.
And this time, Rowina answered.
She was sitting on the floor of
the guest room,
still in the wrinkled green
dress.
The glass earrings in her lap.
The phone trembling in her hand
for the sixth time.
The rug beneath her smelled of
old lavender.
The kind of lavender that isn't
perfume.
It's time.
You vanished, said Hollis
without a greeting.
His voice had that measured calm
that preceded fireings.
I haven't heard your voice in
three weeks.
Don't give me behind schedule.
It's behind schedule.
That's not the point.
The point is the material.
Where is it?
I'm working.
You're not.
Rowina closed her eyes and
rested her forehead on her knee.
The knee was cold through the
wrinkled fabric.
Outside the garden hadn't quite
woken up yet.
A shallow grey light spread
across the window,
as if the day was still
convincing itself to arrive.
Pollis.
Rowina.
He drew a deep breath on the
other end of the line.
I backed you.
I bought the ticket.
Paid for the hotel the first
weekend, kept your shift going
with Marlo covering three
straight shifts.
I'm not a benefactor.
I'm an editor.
And an editor needs to deliver.
Either you send me something by
Monday night or I'll have to
make a decision
neither of us once.
She didn't answer right away.
Outside, a bird insisted on the
same short note near the window.
And Rowina caught herself
thinking about how Jago used to
be late with the coffee,
whenever there was a bird
nearby.
He'd stand out on the porch for
a moment,
listening, the cup forgotten in
his hand.
She shouldn't have noticed that.
She had noticed.
I heard you.
She said finally.
You didn't.
Hollis answered.
But you will.
Monday night, headline or
resignation.
He hung up first.
Rowina kept looking at the phone
for a length of time she
couldn't measure.
The reflection of her own
distorted face on the black
screen.
She stood up slowly.
She walked to the suitcase which
was half open on a wooden chair
near the dresser.
She pulled the brown file out by
the rubber band, sat down again
on the rug,
and rested the file on her own
thighs.
Her hands were still this time.
Stiller than she expected.
She untied the rubber band
slowly.
She opened the first flap.
Clippings of balance sheets.
Photocopies Hollis had obtained
from some discrete source.
Notes in small handwriting
written by herself before she
met Jago Quint.
In a gray, noisy newsroom where
the coffee was bad,
and ambition still seemed enough
to pay the bills.
Rowina read two lines of her own
field notebook,
and didn't recognize the woman
who had written that.
She closed the file.
She tied the rubber band again.
She put everything back at the
bottom of the suitcase.
The partner's dinner was
scheduled for that same night.
Neve came up in the late
afternoon with a dress hanging
from a velvet hanger.
Deep wine, straight neckline,
sleeves to the elbow.
The fabric had a specific weight
to the touch,
that weight of something chosen
with attention.
Rowina looked at her without
understanding.
From the master said Neve and
set the hanger on the chair
against the wall,
he asked me to leave it here.
He said the miss isn't obliged
to wear it.
Rowina laughed without joy,
and if I don't wear it.
He won't ask why, said Neve,
with a half smile that didn't
quite complete itself.
But he'll notice.
He notices.
She wore the dress.
She couldn't decide whether it
was surrender or courage,
and she chose not to decide.
The mansion's dining room had 18
places,
and a table that was a vanished
skating rink.
There were six partners, three
wives,
Silas Ashford at one end in the
same gray suit as always,
and the face of someone who has
already seen far too much,
without being surprised by
anything,
and you door a quint at the
other end,
seated as though the seat had
been built around her.
Rowina entered beside Jego.
She was introduced by him in a
sentence that left no gap.
Rowina Pike, she's with me.
It wasn't a description.
It was a signature.
The dinner advanced through
courses she barely tasted.
There was talk of an acquisition
up north,
of a land auction near the
river,
of a niece's wedding in
Charleston.
Rowina answered when addressed
and listened,
when not addressed.
The wine was too good to be
wasted on anxiety,
so she drank slowly and kept her
spine straight.
At some point between the second
course and the third,
Jego's hand found hers on top of
the white table cloth.
He didn't hold it halfway or
hide it under the table.
He left his hand resting on top
of her hand,
in full view of everyone,
and went on talking to the
partner to his left,
as if the hand was some object
he'd found along the way,
and decided to keep.
Silas noticed first.
Rowina saw the small flicker in
the lawyer's eyes,
almost invisible,
followed by a throat clearing
that made way for nothing.
Jodora noticed next.
The matriarch didn't take her
eyes off her plate,
but her fork paused half a
second in the air,
and resumed moving with a care
Rowina had learned to interpret
as reading.
Jodora read people.
She did it all the time,
without appearing to be doing
it.
After coffee the partner's rose
for cigars,
and the wives went off to
another parlor.
Rowina went up alone.
In the corridor she crossed
paths with Silas,
who carried a folder under his
arm and a look she couldn't
decipher,
the kind of look that holds more
than one interpretation,
and gives away none.
Good night, Miss.
He said,
Good night, Mr. Ashford.
He seemed to want to say
something more.
He weighed the moment, decided
against it,
and went on down the corridor
with the firm stride of someone
with a set destination.
In the guest room, Rowina shut
the door and leaned against it
for a moment.
The wood was cold against her
back through the fabric of the
dress.
She thought about tearing up the
notes,
she thought about calling Hollis
and telling him the story didn't
exist.
She thought about telling Jago
everything that night,
with the wine still in her body
and the courage of exhaustion.
She thought about doing none of
the three things,
and leaving it all for the train
back.
She went to the bathroom, took
off her makeup with cold water
and cotton,
put on a simple linen nightgown
lay down on top of the
bedspread,
and stared at the white-washed
ceiling as the house grew quiet,
room by room.
She fell asleep without
realizing it.
She was woken by the sound of
the door.
There was no knock.
The door opened slowly, letting
in a thin band of light from the
corridor,
and Rowina saw against that
light, the silhouette of Jago
quint.
He didn't turn on the room's
lamp.
He walked to the middle of the
room and stopped,
and only then did she notice
what was in his hands,
the file, brown, no label, no
rubber band now.
Rowina sat up in the bed in a
single motion.
The air left her chest in an
exhalation that made no sound.
Help.
Silas, he said, without raising
his voice,
he saw Odette prowling this
corridor earlier.
He thought it best I checked
before she did.
His voice was low.
It was calm.
It was empty of anything she
could use to hold on to.
Jago looked at the file he was
carrying,
leafed through a page she
recognized without needing to
look closely,
and put the page back in its
place,
with a care that seemed in that
moment,
the cruelest thing in the world.
Ballons sheets, he said,
copies of old contracts, a list
of names with notes beside them.
I recognized at least three of
the names.
He lifted his eyes to her.
This isn't an interview.
It isn't, Rowina answered,
because denying it would have
been a worse insult.
He nodded slightly.
That was all.
A single precise nod that didn't
judge,
and therefore weighed more than
any judgment.
You came here for this.
I came here for this, she said,
and I didn't know I would stop
coming here for it.
But I did stop weeks ago.
I haven't opened that file once
since.
Here it doesn't matter, he cut
in,
and even cutting in he kept his
usual low tone.
You opened it yesterday, I heard
you open it.
I thought you were closing a
suitcase.
The silence settled between
them,
with a specificity, Rowina
couldn't fill,
and he didn't try to.
Jego, thank you for coming to
Savannah,
he said, and that was the
sentence that went through her
from side to side.
Thank you for the weeks.
The interview is paid for, if
you still want it.
I only asked that you leave
tomorrow morning before my
mother comes down for coffee.
She opened her mouth, closed it,
opened it again.
Don't do this like this, like
what?
Without yelling at me, he
considered the sentence,
he took too long to answer the
kind of delay that is an answer
in itself.
If I yell you'll be able to
think I'm still angry.
His voice found a note she had
never heard in him,
too low to have a name.
I don't want you to think that.
I want you to leave knowing
exactly what stayed behind.
It was worse than yelling.
It was worse than anything she
could have predicted that week
or in any week before it.
Jego set the file on the dresser
near the door,
with a precision that seemed
calculated to make no noise.
He didn't return it to her hand.
He didn't take it with him.
He left it there, in the middle
of the way,
like an exposed piece of
evidence, neither of them needed
to examine any more.
Then he turned toward the door.
Leave tomorrow.
The door closed behind him with
the most polite noise a door has
ever produced in the entire
world.
Rhoina remained sitting on the
bed.
Her hands opened on the bed
spread.
Her heart beating in a rhythm
she didn't recognize as her own.
Outside in the corridor, his
footsteps moved away slowly.
No hurry, no hesitation.
And at some point between her
room and his room,
they stopped for a second,
before continuing.
She didn't cry.
Not yet.
She kept looking at the file on
top of the dresser,
like someone staring at an
animal that had followed her
from too far away,
to now pretend it was a
stranger.
Outside the window, the garden
of the Quint Mansion,
breathed the humid night, the
smell of earth and jasmine
rising with the breeze off the
river.
Somewhere near the water, a real
owl called out once.
Rhoina thought of the glass owl
set with red stone,
tucked in a dark velvet box at
the bottom of her bag,
and felt that this was the
memory that would hurt most on
the train the next day.
But chapter 5 killing the story.
Rain back left before 8, and
Rhoina sat by the window,
because the aisle required
looking at people head on,
and people that morning would
have seen what she hadn't yet
seen in the mirror.
She rested her forehead against
the cold glass,
and stayed that way for a length
of time she couldn't measure.
Savannah fell behind in pieces,
a roof, a tower, a line of trees
bent by the river wind,
and none of it hurt with the
noise she had expected.
It hurt low. It hurt the way
Jago had said,
thank you in the small hours,
when she was expecting a shout,
anything with enough volume for
her to push back against,
the file was still on top of the
guest room dresser.
She hadn't even asked for it
back, leaving it there felt
fair.
In the sense that justice is
what's left over when everything
else surrenders.
She didn't cry on the train. She
counted roof panels of cars,
counted poles, counted the times
the conductor passed down the
aisle dragging a coffee cart.
The smell of the machine coffee
was cheap, and watery.
Nothing like what Jago had
learned to make, and that
idiotic detail was what came
closest to breaking her. She
reached the grey city just
before noon.
The station smelled of lubricant
and cheap bread.
Rowena carried her suitcase like
someone carrying a witness.
She cried in the newsroom
bathroom.
It was a dry cry of two minutes.
Curled up in a stall with her
hand over her mouth because
Marlo Trent was on the other
side of the door.
Tapping the tip of her shoe and
speaking loudly to cover for
her.
Come out of their pike. If you
stay in there any longer,
Hollis is going to knock on the
door and then I'm going to have
to bite him.
Rowena laughed in the middle of
the cry without meaning to.
It was an ugly sound but it
worked.
She came out with her face
washed. Marlo looked at her for
a whole second,
without sarcasm for the first
time in years.
There was something different in
her friend's expression.
The shoulders quieter.
The way she stood still without
her phone in her hand.
You okay? No. Rowena answered.
But I will be. Marlo squeezed
her shoulder and her hand stayed
there too long for a joke.
That was how Rowena understood
her friend had guessed
everything before asking.
The newsroom had that midday
noise.
Keys, phones ringing two desks
over.
Someone shouting a page number
down the hall as if the whole
building needed to know.
Hollis Vaughan lifted his eyes
over his glasses the moment
Rowena passed down the central
aisle.
He didn't smile. He didn't ask
how the trip had gone.
He simply pointed with his pen
to the door of his office.
A short, habitual gesture.
The kind that allows no
negotiation.
She went in. She shut the door
behind her.
That office smelled of aged
paper and coffee no one had the
courage to throw out.
And there was a plant in the
corner that had been dying for
at least two months.
It's leaves drooping over the
edge of the pot without anyone
having noticed.
Hollis sat down his pen.
Headline, he said.
End of the day.
There's not going to be a
headline.
Hollis blinked once.
He leaned back in his chair.
Say that again.
There's not going to be a
headline Rowena repeated and her
voice came out firm
of them she expected.
I'm not going to deliver what
you asked for.
Not today, not next week, not
ever.
You went there with a mission
pike.
I did, and I came back without
it.
Hollis looked at the desk for a
moment.
When he raised his eyes, there
was less anger than she'd
imagined.
And more a kind of old
disappointment, the kind of
disappointment bosses carry from
other
bosses before them, piled up
over years in rooms exactly like
that one.
You know what this means.
I do.
Rowena set a folded paper on the
desk.
I'm handing this over before you
have to say it.
Hollis picked up the paper.
He didn't open it.
Why?
He asked.
And the question came almost
gentle, which frightened her
more than an insult would have.
Rowena was silent for a second.
She thought of a pretty
professional answer.
The kind that looks good in
retrospect.
She gave up.
Because the story stopped
existing, she said.
He stopped being a story.
And I don't know how to write
about someone who became a
person.
Hollis looked at her for a long
time, with the expression of
someone re-reading an equation
that
doesn't add up, then he nodded
once, almost imperceptibly.
Get out before I change my mind,
he said.
And Pike, she stopped at the
door.
You were good.
Rowena swallowed before
answering.
I still am.
Just not for this.
She shut the door carefully.
Hollis was leaning against the
corridor wall, waiting with two
cups of machine coffee.
And she pushed one of the cups
into Rowena's hand without
ceremony, like someone handing
over a
survival item.
Did you do it?
She asked.
I did.
Shit.
Marlo Blue on the coffee.
Welcome to the club of the
dignified unemployed.
Rowena laughed.
It was a short, broken laugh,
but it was a laugh.
They went down the stairs
instead of the elevator.
On the sidewalk, the city was
grey the way it had always been.
And Rowena looked at the
buildings without any of the
glow that Savannah painted on to
even a
cloudy morning.
Something was missing from that
sky.
The smell of Magnolia was
missing.
The way the Savannah river
appeared between two streets
when no one expected it.
A strip of lead-coloured water
that somehow made everything
lighter was missing.
E was missing.
You're going back, Marlo said,
without asking.
I am.
Will he take you back?
I don't know.
He will.
Marlo insisted looking off into
the distance.
A man who sends for you three
weeks in a row doesn't close a
door for good.
He locks it.
It's different.
Rowena looked at her friend, and
for an instant,
the world stopped spinning so
fast.
Marlo.
What?
Thank you.
Get out of here before I cry,
Pike.
It doesn't suit me.
Rowena took the night train and
slept enough not to look
devastated on arrival.
The car smelled of old fabric
and rain, and she kept her face
turned to the dark window
for much of the trip, watching
her own reflection without being
able to look away.
On Sunday morning, Savannah
received the train with the sun
coming in from the side.
And the whole station smelled of
bakery and river breeze,
she took a taxi without stopping
to think.
She went in through the front.
She rang the bell.
Feeling answered.
His eyes widened for half a
second, before returning to
normal trained.
Miss Pike, I need to talk to
him.
He's in his office with guests.
I know.
Feeling hesitated.
Then he stepped aside.
Miss is quint arrived in our
ego.
He said quietly, almost a
warning.
And Miss Martian came along.
Rowena nodded.
Druid deep breath once and
walked down the marble corridor.
Like someone walking to a trial
she herself had scheduled.
The corridor was silent except
for her own footsteps.
And their echo on the old tiles
sounded too firm for the way she
was feeling inside.
Jay goes office was in the west
wing of the mansion, and the
door was a jar.
She heard before she saw, the
voice of Odette Martian, sweet,
too loud,
that voice of someone who
pretends to console and measures
the effect in a mirror.
A necessary evil you'dora.
Truly, better to find out now
than, Rowena opened the door
before Odette finished.
The entire office went still.
Jay goes to behind the desk,
dark jacket hands resting on the
top.
You'dora seated in the green
velvet armchair near the window,
back straight as ever, as if her
posture were the last line of
defense.
Silas leaning against the
bookcase.
Neutral expression.
Eyes that recognized Rowena
before the rest of his body did.
Odette on the sofa, glass in
hand, a smile dressing her mouth
until it froze when she saw
who had come in.
Jaygo didn't move.
Only his jaw tensed once.
Rowena said Silas almost
automatically, trying to smooth
things over.
Stay, Rowena asked, without
taking her eyes off Jaygo.
All of you.
Stay.
Odette opened her mouth.
Rowena gave her no chance.
I came to tell the truth, she
said.
All of it.
I'm not going to apologise first
because an apology before the
truth is an insult.
Odora raised an eyebrow.
Nothing more.
Rowena breathed.
Her voice came out firm, even
though her hands trembled inside
her jacket.
I came to Savannah with two
missions.
The interview was one.
The other was to come back with
material that would destroy the
Quint family.
My editor wanted a scandal
story, and I accepted because I
needed the job.
I accepted believing I could
separate the work from the
charade.
She paused.
I couldn't.
Odette let out a low incredulous
laugh.
No one joined her.
I brought the file, Rowena
continued, and her voice didn't
waver.
You already know I brought it.
It was found.
It was red.
And it was returned in the small
hours of yesterday morning with
a thank you
that hurt more than any shout
would have.
She looked at Jaygo.
He didn't look away.
He didn't confirm.
His face was that of a man
counting every word before
deciding what to do with them.
I could have gone back to the
newsroom, written what my editor
wanted, saved my career.
A voice rose half a tone.
I didn't write it.
I killed the story this morning.
I resigned before he could fire
me.
There's no story anymore.
There's no file anymore.
There's nothing left in that
guest room that's of use to
anyone.
She took a step forward just
one.
And I didn't come here for
forgiveness.
I came because if I didn't say
this in front of everyone who
watched the lie happen,
the truth would remain a private
thing and the lie was public.
That's not fair.
Total silence.
Udora blinked once.
Slowly.
Like someone recalculating
something she'd thought was
settled.
O'Dette looked at her glasses if
it had betrayed her.
I dropped the story.
Rowena said.
And her voice lowered again.
Almost soft.
Because he stopped being a
story.
I couldn't write about a man who
learned my coffee by heart.
She finished.
The hands were still trembling.
She let them tremble.
O'Dette rose first.
Her glass coming down hard on
the side tray.
What a spectacle.
She said.
Seeking Jago's eyes.
You're not going to believe this
are you?
Jago didn't answer O'Dette.
He looked at Rowena for a length
of time no one there could
count.
Then he pulled back his chair
unhurried and stood up.
J.
Chapter 6 His laugh.
Go cross the office in a single
stride.
It didn't seem like a stride it
seemed like decision walking.
Rowena didn't step back but she
held her breath in the middle of
her chest
as if her body had forgotten how
to do it.
He stopped half a meter from
her.
He didn't touch her.
He just stood there.
His eyes fixed on her.
And there was something in that
gaze Rowena couldn't name.
Neither anger nor relief.
Something that made her hold her
own breath.
O'Dette.
He said without looking back.
Get out of my house.
The silence in the room had
weight.
The kind of silence that makes
people hold their breath without
realizing.
Jago.
Now, his voice came out low.
Curtis.
The way he spoke to everyone.
And even so, no one in the room
had any doubt.
O'Dette picked up her bag with
rigid movements her fingers
gripping the leather.
She didn't look at you, Dora.
The door slammed behind her with
the thin noise of high heels
that had lost their audience.
Jago breathed once.
Then he looked at Rowena as if
he were checking a calculation
that had taken
far too long to add up.
I want you to hear this," he
said.
Loud enough for siless and you
Dora to hear every word.
And loud enough to carry through
the open door and reach the
corridor.
Where half a dozen of you Dora's
guests pretended not to listen.
She stays.
With me.
And tomorrow, all of Savannah
will hear it from my mouth
before hearing it from anyone
else's.
He paused for an instant, as if
the sentence carried weight.
I'm done letting fear choose for
me.
He raised his hand slowly.
He touched the tips of his
fingers to her chin.
The touch has light as a
question.
Stay.
Rowena felt her eyes sting.
She didn't look away.
I'll stay.
Silas let out the air he'd been
holding.
Udora didn't move.
But something in the line of her
shoulders gave way a millimeter.
It was the matriarch who broke
the silence at last,
with that voice that never
missed its tone even on hard
days.
Out of here, she said,
addressing neither of them in
particular.
All of you I need to think.
Rowena and Jago left together.
Silas closed the door with the
care of someone who knows
that a well-closed door is
sometimes worth an entire
contract.
In the corridor Jago held
Rowena's hand.
That was all.
He didn't kiss her.
He didn't speak.
He just held it.
His fingers laced through hers
with a quiet firmness.
Unlike anything she'd known in
him until then.
He let her out onto the back
porch.
The one facing the Savannah
River.
The late afternoon sun fell gold
and on the water,
tinting the surface copper and
amber,
and the smell of the garden came
heavy with magnolia wet from the
night before.
Somewhere in the middle of the
garden, an insect sang the same
repeated note,
Rhythmic in No Harry.
You killed the story, said Jago,
looking at the river.
It wasn't a question.
I did.
You lost your job.
He turned his head slowly,
and his profile against the late
afternoon light had a hardness
Rowena couldn't read in full.
She could only read the part
that mattered.
I'm going to help you find
another one, he said.
One you choose.
Not one I choose for you.
Rowena laughed softly.
The laugh came out choked.
A little crooked.
The way laughs happen when the
body doesn't quite know yet,
whether it's crying or smiling.
You said choose and for you.
In the same sentence, quint.
Careful.
He closed his eyes for a second.
When he opened them, his
shoulders had dropped half a
finger,
and his mouth gave way in a near
smile Rowena had never seen
there.
I'll learn.
It was there behind them that
the porch door opened.
Yudora came out without
announcing herself.
She didn't look at Jago first.
She looked at Rowena, and there
was in that gaze and a
preysal different from the
earlier ones without the usual
scalpel.
The matriarch crossed the stone
floor,
and stopped in front of her.
Up close in the low rosy light
of that afternoon,
Yudora seemed smaller than on
the night of the ball.
Smaller and older and less
sharp,
as if she'd left her armor
hanging on the inside.
Rowena waited for the blow that
didn't come.
Yudora extended her hand.
She touched Rowena's arm
lightly.
A thumb sliding once over the
sleeve of the jacket.
A gesture so restrained it could
have gone unnoticed, but it
didn't.
Then she turned her head and
looked into the hall.
The wide door was open.
And from there you could see the
empty chair.
The one that had always been
near the window of the main
hall.
Its back turned slightly to the
side,
as if someone had just stood up
and would come back at any
moment.
Yudora kept looking long enough
for the moment to grow heavy.
You have his laugh, she
murmured.
Rowena didn't understand.
She felt her heart skipped a
whole beat,
but she didn't understand.
Yudora didn't explain.
She just squeezed her arm once
very lightly,
and went back inside.
The door closed behind her
without a sound.
As if the house were protecting
that secret too.
Rowena looked at Jago.
His jaw was locked.
His gaze fixed on some point of
the river
that no longer belonged to that
afternoon.
Jago.
Later, he said quietly.
Please, she didn't insist.
She stored the question in the
same place where she stored all
the details
that didn't yet have a frame.
She kept storing, because that
was what she knew how to do.
And because not every detail
asked to be opened on the same
day it appeared.
Yudora back inside at the end of
the afternoon.
When the river was already dark
blue,
and the mansions lights were
beginning to come on one by one,
as if the house were breathing.
They ate little.
No one spoke much.
Silas passed down the corridor
once,
nodded agreeding, and vanished
off towards the library.
Nive brought T without asking,
and disappeared before anyone
could thank her.
Then it was Jago who extended
his hand.
Rowen were accepted.
They went up the main staircase
together.
Her footsteps echoed on the
marble.
His almost didn't.
He always stepped as if he
didn't want to take up more
space than necessary.
Half way up the stairs he
stopped.
He turned her slowly.
His hand displayed against the
nape of her neck,
and pressed his forehead to hers
for a length of time that
belonged to no clock.
I don't know how to do this
right.
He said, too low to be anything
but honest.
No one does.
He laughed.
It was a short laugh almost
startled.
The kind of laugh that escapes
before a person decides to let
it out.
Rowen restored that laugh too.
She stored it the same way she
stored everything that mattered.
Without noting it down, without
recording it.
Just letting it settle deep.
They kept going up.
At the top the corridor had that
late night mansion silence,
that isn't the silence of
emptiness.
It's the silence of care.
The door to his room was a jar.
He pushed it with the back of
his hand.
A casual gesture that contained
a whole decision.
She went in.
He went in behind her.
The door closed slowly.
The kitchen.
The next morning.
Smelled of coffee and warm
bread.
The Savannah light came in from
the side through the high
window,
cut into bands by the frames,
and fell gold and over the white
tablecloth,
over the cups, over the still
warm loaves that
neither had left in a basket,
and disappeared before anyone
could thank her.
That was how Nive did things,
beforehand and without making
noise.
Roena sat with her legs crossed
in the chair,
the cup warming both her hands.
Jego sat beside her, so close
that his knee touched hers under
the table.
He didn't speak.
He just extended his hand over
the white tablecloth and waited.
Roena placed hers on top.
They stayed that way.
Unhurried.
While the heat of the coffee
rose in a thread of steam
between them.
She looked at the cup.
He had made the coffee the way
she liked it.
Two dashes of sugar.
More milk than any barista would
accept.
He'd made it without asking.
She smiled into the cup and said
nothing,
because she didn't need to.
From the other side of the
kitchen,
through the arch doorway you
could see the corner of the main
hall.
And from there you could see the
empty chair near the window.
Its back was still turned
slightly to the side,
as it had been the afternoon
before,
as on every morning Roena had
spent in that house.
No one had moved the chair
during the night.
No one had occupied it as far as
she knew.
On any of the times she'd been
there.
Alaf.
Someone you'd orah had known.
Someone Jago had known.
A name the house had decided to
stop saying,
guarded with such care that even
the silence around it had shape.
Roena opened her mouth.
Jago.
He lifted his eyes from the
coffee.
He didn't answer.
Yesterday she said,
and her voice came out soft,
calibrated,
so as not to break that morning.
Your mother said something.
About a laugh.
Jago's hand overhears tightened
a little.
That was all.
A small involuntary squeeze the
kind that happens before a
person decides to do it.
Boo!
She didn't finish.
Not because he interrupted her
with any word.
It was the silence that did the
work.
A whole round silence that
filled the table and the coffee,
and the savanna light falling
between them,
as if the sun too were waiting.
He looked at the cup,
then at her hand under his hand.
Then for a very brief instant at
the empty chair far off
golden in the morning.
He didn't answer.
Roena felt then with a cold and
new certainty
that there was an entire story
living inside that house,
not in the walls or the old
furniture,
but in the people who lived in
it and carried it without saying
the name.
She had just knocked on the
right door.
The door was not going to open
that morning.
She stored the question in her
throat.
The way she had always stored
what didn't yet have its time.
She closed her hand around his.
Outside a bird sang a high note
and flew away.
The empty chair remained empty,
golden in the sun,
occupying the place it had
always occupied,
and she understood without
anyone needing to say it,
that that morning of peace was
only the beginning of something
else.
Six months later, she woke up
every day in Jago's arms.
In the dream house he had built
for the two of them.
Slow kisses, whispered promises,
his body fitted to hers as if
the world outside didn't exist.
Until the bodyguard started
following her into the more
bathroom.
Until he deleted the job offer
that had come for her,
without saying a word.
Until the phone rang and a name,
a name no one in that family
dare to speak,
may Jago go pale, hang up
mid-sentence,
and lie with his eyes still
glazed with dread.
She saw the raw fear there.
The same fear he had been hiding
since the night they kissed for
the first time,
pretending it was only a game.
The old secret between them was
no longer a shadow.
It was an open wound.
Capable of explaining the
controlling man Jago had become,
and of destroying forever the
man she had loved.
Now she trembled alone in the
luxurious bedroom,
tasting the bitter flavor of
betrayed trust.
And what if the past he had
locked away with guilt
was greater than the love he
swore he felt.
And what if opening that door
made him hate her forever?
And what if the beautiful golden
cage was the only thing still
keeping the two of them
together?
side.