I've heard stories, but I never
imagined it would be like
this.
This place holds secrets.
I know it.
Chapter 1.
An ordinary Tuesday
The house near the Savannah
River woke up slowly.
The way old houses do, carrying
the habit of breathing before
their people.
The light of dawn came through
the crack in the curtains in a
thin strip
and settled on
her shoulder, and Jago Quint
stood there looking at that
shoulder for longer than was
reasonable.
Rowena slept on her side, one
hand opened near her
face, like someone who had left
a question
half-assed, and decided to
finish asking at the next day.
The sheet had slipped down to
her waist, and the light caught
the loose strands of her hair
which still smelled of the soap
from the night before.
He got up without a sound.
His body knew this ritual.
Getting out of bed without
waking the one who stayed.
There was a calm inside him that
still scared him.
Six months after she'd moved
into that house.
That was love he'd discovered,
and at the same time it
was something else a small
dread,
almost decorative that lived
beneath his ribcage and beat
along with his heart.
He thought he knew how to handle
it.
A man who survived what he'd
survived, learns to tame his own
fear.
He went down the stairs stepping
on the side of the wood that
didn't creak.
The kitchen was still cold, with
that stale air of June mornings
that hadn't decided
whether they were warm or not.
He turned on the kettle.
Measured out her coffee like
someone writing a sentence he
already knew by heart.
Two scoops of grounds, water
that hadn't fully boiled, a
little less than the usual
ratio,
because Roenah liked her coffee
milder at the start of the day,
as if the morning needed to ask
permission before coming in.
The smell rose slowly through
the kitchen.
There was something in it he
could never quite name.
It wasn't the coffee itself.
It was what the smell stood for.
She was still there and she'd
come down.
There was a thought he avoided
at that hour, and the thought
showed up anyway.
If she ever vanished from there,
the smell of coffee would tear
him apart with devastating
efficiency.
He stirred the spoon slowly and
brushed the thought aside with
the same gesture you'd use to
wave off a polite fly.
Not today.
The male came early.
Feline, the personal assistant,
delivered the envelope at the
side door with the discrete
punctuality
J. Gope de Léfour.
There were three letters from
the office, one from the
management of one of the
properties,
and a cream-coloured envelope,
no return address,
a dress to Roenah Pike in the
impersonal handwriting of a
secretary,
at some respectable institution.
He recognized the letterhead in
the upper corner before he even
looked properly.
He stood there for a second with
the envelope between his
fingers,
feeling the specific weight of
quality paper.
I'll take this one. He said,
low.
He tucked the envelope into the
inside pocket of his jacket,
as if he were putting away an
important document he'd remember
to hand over later.
He knew he wouldn't remember.
He'd already decided not to
remember before he even finished
the gesture.
The worst part was that his hand
had made the move without
consulting him,
with an old efficiency he
recognized as his own and didn't
like recognizing.
Feline saw it.
Feline said nothing.
The two exchanged a brief
greeting, and the assistant left
the same way he'd come in,
is steps muffled by the runner
in the hallway.
When Roenah came down, coffee
was served in two cups.
She appeared in the kitchen
doorway in a long night gown.
Her hair loosely pinned up,
rubbing her eye with a closed
fist like a child.
The morning sun was coming in
now through the side window,
and drew a golden square on the
wooden floor between them.
He looked up and the small
decorative dread settled back
beneath his ribcage quiet.
You got up early?
She remarked, her voice still
thick with sleep.
I couldn't sleep with you
breathing so beautifully like
that,
J. Go answered, and his mouth
almost smiled.
She laughed.
It was a short slightly husky
laugh, the kind he collected
inside without admitting he
collected them.
She sat on the stool at the
kitchen island, took the cup
with both hands,
and smelled it before drinking
the way she did every day,
her eyes closing for half a
second over the steam,
a gesture so hers that he
already knew it by heart.
He watched without seeming to
watch.
Are you expecting anything
today?
He asked, and the tone was
casual in that practiced way,
rowing a thought for a second
her eyes still on the cup,
an answer, she said,
maybe.
That conversation I told you
about last week, she looked up.
You remember?
I remember, he answered.
You remembered?
In his pocket he had exactly the
answer she was waiting for,
and the answer was generous.
And the answer would take her
out of that house for six
months.
The pocket weighed on him in a
specific way.
He drank his own coffee and said
nothing more.
Rowena looked at him for a
second longer than her usual,
then she looked at her own
coffee,
and the rest of the morning ran
along beautifully,
the way their mornings usually
ran.
At noon, Silas Ashford was
waiting for Jago at the office
in downtown Savannah.
The lawyer had a way of sitting
in chairs that didn't belong to
him as if they did.
Legs crossed, one finger resting
against his temple,
the expressionless face he wore
when he brought bad news.
The air conditioning in the room
was set too high,
and the artificial chill clashed
with the heat coming in through
the wide windows overlooking the
square.
Short lunch, Silas announced
when Jago walked in.
Short why?
Because what I've got to tell
you doesn't go well with
dessert.
Jago closed the door behind him,
he sat down on the other side of
the desk.
The two had known each other
long enough to skip the run
around.
Someone's asking questions,
Silas said without raising his
voice,
again in three different places,
discrete questions, the kind of
trained person asks,
and the questions come too close
to what we agreed to never let
anyone get close to.
Jago didn't move, inside the
decorative dread grew an inch.
Name?
He asked, not yet, but they pay
well, and they pay with money
that leaves no trail.
That interest me more than the
name.
Jago looked at the desk.
There was a line of silence the
two of them respected,
the kind built over years of
loyalty,
Silas waited.
He always waited with that stone
patience he charged
dearly for by the hour.
Double the security at the
house, Jago said finally.
Quietly.
Rowina can't know.
Silas kept looking at him a
second longer than necessary.
Jago, she can't know Silas.
The lawyer ran his tongue along
the inside corner of his cheek,
a small gesture he made when he
wanted to say something,
and chose not to.
Then he nodded in that short dry
way of his.
And that envelope, Silas asked,
did the answer come?
Jago didn't answer right away.
He tapped his thumb lightly on
the tabletop once twice.
It came.
Are you going to deliver it?
I am.
When?
Jago looked up.
There was something in his eyes
that Silas had known long before
this conversation.
The same thing that lived in
that gaze ten years ago,
and that Silas had hoped for a
while had gotten better.
When I figure out how, Silas
nodded,
but his face didn't agree.
The two finished lunch in decent
silence with the noise from the
square
coming in muffled through the
windows.
When Jago left the office,
the cream envelope was still
weighing in the inside pocket of
his jacket,
and he had for the first time in
a long time, a brief urge to
tear it up.
Rowina spent the afternoon in
the living room of the house
near the river.
She was rereading some old
worknotes,
things she kept in a hardcover
folder that sat on a shelf in
plain sight,
no hiding place at all.
She'd learned to value that
transparency the way people do,
who have already lost someone by
hiding too much.
The afternoon light came in
slanted through the half open
blinds,
and striped the rug in golden
bands.
Outside the river made its usual
gentle sound,
the living room phone rang at a
little past five.
Neither he'd gone to the market
with Fielen.
Jago hadn't come back yet.
Rowina answered.
Quint residence.
She said.
The way she always answered,
half joking with the formality.
On the other end, a full second
of silence.
Then a man's voice horse with
age and with something harder to
name,
good afternoon I need to speak
with Mr. Quint.
He's not in at the moment, can I
take a message?
Another silence.
She heard the man breathe as if
he were weighing every word
before letting it out.
Rowina, a well-trained
journalist,
began paying attention with her
whole body,
without yet knowing why.
There was something in that
silence that wasn't in decision.
It was calculation.
It's the man coughed lightly.
It's about kit.
Tell him it's about kit.
He'll understand.
Rowina stopped breathing for a
second.
Not because of the name.
The name still meant nothing to
her.
She stopped because of the way
the man said it.
Like someone handing over a
password,
he knows will open a door that's
been locked for a long time.
Kit, she repeated slowly,
and her voice came out more
neutral than she was feeling.
May I ask who's calling?
The man was already answering
when the front door slammed.
Quick steps in the hallway.
Quicker than Jago's step usually
was at the end of the day.
He walked into the room with his
meeting posture still in his
body,
and stopped walking when he saw
the phone in her hand.
She watched the colour drain
from his face in real time.
It was something she'd never
seen before in that man.
No anger, no practice surprise,
just a physical animal
whiteness,
rising from his chin to his
forehead in seconds,
as if someone had flipped a
switch.
Who is it?
He asked, his voice too low for
the size of the question.
Roena didn't answer.
She held out the receiver.
Jago took it, brought it to his
ear,
listened for two seconds, closed
his eyes once,
a single blink longer than
normal.
The kind of gesture that isn't
reflex its decision,
and then said just one sentence.
Don't call this number.
He hung up.
He kept his hand on the phone
for a length of time she counted
inside her own chest,
beat by beat, Roena looked at
him.
She knew that man in her body,
in his smell, in the way he ran
his thumb under his eye when he
was tired.
She'd never seen him white like
that.
She'd never seen him need
support just to stay standing.
Jago, he didn't answer right
away.
Who was it?
She asked, with the trained calm
her profession had given her as
a gift.
He looked up, and that was when
she saw it.
But the first time since the two
of them had met,
she saw him decide to lie.
It wasn't a quick decision.
She saw the moment before it,
the instant when he could still
choose the other path.
An old employee, Jago said,
drunk probably got the wrong
number.
She kept looking at him.
He held her gaze with the
composure of someone who'd spent
his whole life holding gays,
he couldn't afford to lose.
He knew inside that she knew.
Still, he wanted her to let it
go.
He said a name, Roena said,
and her voice came out very low
almost gentle,
which was the way she used when
the question wasn't gentle.
Jago swallowed.
What name?
He didn't blink.
He carried his body to the
sideboard next to the sofa,
rested his hand on the wood as
if he needed something solid,
and spoke looking at the river
through the window,
his back to her.
I don't know him.
Roena stood where she was.
On the other side of the room
near the big window there was a
chair.
Just like the one in the
mansions main hall,
brought here when they moved in.
She had now six months of
looking at that chair without
understanding why no
one ever sat in it.
Why the seat was always turned
slightly toward the river,
as if waiting for someone who
knew where they'd arrive from.
She looked at the chair, looked
at Jago's back,
looked at the chair again,
and the chair for the first time
had a sound.
The name was short, short, and
old.
It had only three letters, and
had slipped down the phone line
like a poorly tied
secret, spoken by a horse voice.
Kit.
She didn't repeat it out loud.
She kept it.
She was very good at that.
That night Roena didn't sleep.
She lay looking at the bedroom
ceiling,
listening to his breathing
beside her.
That breathing she knew better
than her own,
that she could tell when it was
real sleep,
and when it was faked.
That night for the first time
she couldn't read it.
Outside, the river ran with its
usual soft sound,
indifferent to what was
happening inside that beautiful
house.
Inside her chest, an empty chair
had begun to creak.
The second.
Chapter two, tenderness isn't
truth.
Sun came into the bedroom in the
morning, as if nothing had
happened,
and Jago moved in bed the way he
always did.
His hand seeking her waist
beneath the sheet,
his face pressing into the nape
of her neck,
the short kiss at the spot where
her hair began.
Roena lay still, eyes closed,
and received it all with her
skin.
His warmth was real.
The weight of his arm was real.
It was easier to stay quiet a
second longer,
and let her body believe in what
her mind hadn't yet resolved.
Then she turned over.
Jago.
The call yesterday.
He opened his eyes with a staged
laziness.
She saw the staging.
It was quick, almost
imperceptible, but she saw it.
She'd learn to see the small
things in him before she'd learn
their names.
I already told you my love, it
was nobody.
You went white.
Jago smiled with half his mouth,
that small smile he reserved for
diffusing difficult situations
in boardrooms.
He raised his hand and tucked a
strand of her hair behind her
ear,
with a calculated lightness.
A gesture that had always worked
before.
One she herself had loved in
those first months,
when she still couldn't tell
genuine tenderness
from the tenderness that served
as a curtain.
I didn't, he said, his voice low
and firm,
you were against the light.
She looked at him in silence.
A pause of three, four seconds,
enough for any guilty person to
fill the emptiness with more
words.
He didn't fill it, he was too
good for that.
He leaned in, kissed the corner
of her mouth with a tenderness
that was real and at the same
time evasive about everything,
and spoke against her skin.
Let's have coffee.
Rowena let it go.
She kissed him back.
Short, got up, went to shower
alone.
And while the water fell too hot
on her shoulders,
she thought for the first time
in plain terms,
a sentence that bothered her a
great deal.
Tenderness and truth are not the
same thing.
She stayed under the water
longer than she needed to.
The bathroom smelled of the
citrus soap
Jago had started buying for her
when he noticed which one she
liked.
One more detail he memorized,
one more gesture she no longer
knew how to receive.
She came down dressed to go out.
Linen pants, a light-colored
blouse.
A small bag she used when she
went downtown.
Jago was in the kitchen reading
something on the tablet
with a cup of coffee in front of
him that must have been
half-loop warm by now.
He looked at her with that gaze
that crossed the room without
needing distance.
Where are you going?
She founded amusing, not the
question.
The tone.
It was his old tone.
The one she thought had been
left behind since they'd gotten
themselves organized.
Six months earlier to live
together there near the river.
Downtown, by a couple things.
Marlo arrives today, remember?
I remember.
He set down the tablet.
Taking the car?
I'm driving myself.
He nodded as if he were
accepting it.
He reached out.
Took a hand on the cold marble
counter,
squeezed it lightly.
His fingers wrapping around hers
with the ease of someone who
already knew every knuckle.
Be careful.
She went out the side door.
She walked along the stone
hallway to the garage,
took the keys off the hook.
The air outside smelled of the
river's dampness
and of some neighbouring garden
that must have had Jasmine.
It was early enough that
Savannah's heat hadn't yet
weighed down.
When she opened the electric
gate,
two men in suits were standing
outside next to a dark car she
didn't recognize.
They didn't seem like a threat.
They seemed like scenery.
The scenery of another kind of
house, not hers.
One of them approached with a
smile that was too polite.
Mrs. Pike, good morning, will be
going with you.
Rowena blinked.
Going with me, where?
Wherever you go.
House orders.
Security.
She looked at the man.
Looked at the other one.
Neither of them seemed
embarrassed.
Neither of them seemed to expect
her to argue.
That, more than anything else,
was what bothered her,
that they derived ready for the
normalcy of a situation she
hadn't authorized.
I didn't ask for security.
She said, with a calm that
wasn't easy to maintain.
You don't need to ask, Mom, it's
already been arranged.
She stood for a second on the
stone pavement.
Inside the house, behind her,
Jago knew.
Jago was on the tablet with the
lukewarm cup and he knew.
He'd given the order the day
before at the downtown office.
And he knew the exact second
she'd meet those two men at the
gate.
At that very moment, sitting in
the kitchen,
he swallowed some coffee that
was too cold to cover his own
nerves.
His hand pressing lightly on the
tablet for no reason at all.
Rowena didn't make a scene.
She simply said, all right, she
got into her car.
Let their car follow behind.
She drove to downtown Savannah
with both hands on the wheel
and the silence inside the car
so vast that she turned on the
radio.
Found it unbearable.
Turned it off.
A hand stayed on the leather of
the wheel,
and she looked out the window at
the old Magnolia's lining the
avenue.
White and heavy from so much
blooming
and thought that some beautiful
things were also suffocating.
Marlo Trent showed up on time at
the old cafe in the historic
district,
with a bag too big for anything
she could possibly need there.
And an expression Rowena
recognized from far off.
The expression of someone who'd
flown three hours
to give a dose of reality to
someone she loved very much
and who was in need of hearing
it.
Row, Marlo, they hugged the way
they'd hugged for years,
tight without ceremony.
Marlo rubbing her hand twice on
her back with that energy of
someone who'd arrived to fix
something.
The cafe smelled of cinnamon and
burnt coffee from an old
machine,
and the dark wooden tables had
marks from years of cups.
They sat near the window.
Marlo ordered black coffee.
Rowena, a cappuccino.
Across the street the dark car
parked with professional
discretion.
Those two yours, Marlo pointed
with her chin, no filter at all.
They're the houses, the houses.
Yeah, Marlo raised a eyebrow.
Marlo had an eyebrow that asked
whole questions on its own
without needing anything more.
Row, don't start.
Row, love doesn't treat you like
a hostage.
Rowena loved.
It was a short laugh a little
awkward but honest.
And she felt along with it a
good pang.
The pang of someone being
reminded of herself by someone
who'd known her before all of
this.
They talked for an hour.
Marlo talked about the newsroom
about the new editor who'd
reorganized everything.
About the people who still asked
about Rowena now and then with
that mix of curiosity and
respect
that comes just before being
forgotten.
Rowena listened and wanted to
feel a clean kind of longing,
uncomplicated, but the longing
that arrived had an uneven edge.
At some point, out of old
reflex, she took the recorder
from her bag.
A small, silver recorder that
she carried out of a habit of
more than six years,
always in the side pocket.
She looked at the device in the
palm of her hand as if she
weren't sure when it had ended
up there.
She put it back without pressing
a single button.
Marlo saw it.
Marlo saw everything always had.
Who are you now journalist?
She asked, with the corner of
her mouth croaked in a way that
was both a question and
affection.
Rowena laughed for real this
time.
A bigger laugh that arrived
without warning.
A woman waiting for an answer
that never comes.
What answer?
A proposal?
A job offer?
They sent it last week.
I still haven't gotten any
reply.
Marlo kept looking at her.
She held the cup with both hands
and waited a second longer
before speaking.
That second rowing a new.
The second that came before the
sentences that stayed.
Row.
What?
Are you sure it didn't come?
Rowena stopped the cappuccino
midway.
The cup hung suspended.
The heat rising to her face.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
Marlo deflected.
And looked at the dark car
across the street with an
expression that was nothing.
Never mind.
But the sentence stayed.
Marlo knew how to put sentences
in the air the way they'd hang
suspended.
And this one stayed the rest of
the coffee.
The rest of the way back.
The rest of the whole afternoon.
Rowena returned to the house
near the river in the late
afternoon.
With savanna's golden light
striking the paving stones from
the side.
And a thin mist rising from the
river as it always did when the
heat began to give way.
The two men followed behind in
professional silence.
Jego was still at the downtown
office.
The house was quiet.
Only neither in the kitchen.
Cutting something with that
silent precision of hers.
And the smell of rosemary coming
from some pot that had been on
the stove for a while.
Rowena went into Jego's private
study with an excuse she'd
prepared for herself while still
in the car.
She needed that old contract
from the house renovation work.
The carpenter had asked for a
copy of the original
specification.
It was a polite lie.
The kind you tell yourself
before doing what you were going
to do anyway.
She opened the first drawer.
Office papers all in order
labeled with the precision of a
man who tolerated chaos on no
surface.
Second drawer.
Contracts.
Thin folders with dates and
numbers.
Third drawer.
A cream-coloured envelope.
No return address.
With her name in the center in
the impersonal.
Typewritten handwriting.
Let her head in the upper right
corner.
Winslow foundation for
independent journalism.
The envelope was open.
She stood still.
The study itself went still
around her.
The dark shelves, the books
lined up by size.
The narrow window that looked
out onto the side garden with
the moss on the stones.
Her hands went strangely quiet.
She took the envelope.
She pulled out the contents
carefully, as if the paper might
confirm something she already
knew.
But didn't yet want to name.
Two sheets.
The first was the formal
invitation.
A job offer.
A series of long investigative
reports full ground complete
autonomy over the topics.
An offer that would bring her
career back to life from
scratch.
At the exact point where she'd
left off before Savannah.
Before the ball.
Before everything.
The second sheet was a carbon
copy.
A reply.
Dated 10 days ago.
Dear Serz.
We thank you for your generous
consideration.
At this time Miss Pike is not
available to take on new
professional commitments.
We renew our thanks.
A signature at the bottom in
handwriting.
The same handwriting that
appeared in the notes he left
her in the kitchen in the
morning.
The same as the contract she
signed alongside him.
The same one she'd learned to
recognize before even reading
what was written.
Is handwriting.
Ruinna kept looking at the sheet
for a length of time she
couldn't measure.
Her body didn't tremble.
Her body went very still.
And the stillness was heavier
than any tremor.
Ruinna put the envelope back in
the drawer.
Closed it with the same care
she'd opened it.
She left the private study
without taking the carpenters
contract.
She didn't need the contract.
She never had.
She went to the living room.
She sat on the sofa without
turning on the light.
The afternoon had closed into
that dark blue of early night
that came fast in Savannah's
summer.
And the room filled with a warm
dimness.
On the other side next to the
big window.
The empty chair was in its usual
place.
With the last light of day
reaching only the backrest.
She looked at the chair for a
long time.
Two stories she thought.
One of them has a short old name
that no one pronounces inside
this house.
The other has his handwriting on
a sheet that answered for her
without her knowing.
The phone rang.
It was Jago.
Love.
I'm not going to make it home
yet.
Don't stay hungry.
Eat without me.
She closed her eyes.
She held her voice in the right
place.
That exact place where the voice
stops trembling and becomes just
an answer.
Okay.
I love you.
You too.
She hung up.
She kept the phone in her hand.
The heat of the device against
her palm.
Outside the river ran with that
low constant sound she'd learned
to find calming
and that now sounded different.
The empty chair waited.
And for the first time in six
months,
Rowena Pike felt inside her own
chest.
The low firm creek of a decision
beginning to be made.
Chapter 3 The Name No One Said.
The cream envelope sat on the
table between them
as if it weighed more than the
wood holding it up.
Rowena had waited all day to set
it down there
at the exact spot where he
usually left his keys.
She chose the dining room table
because it was the only room
where Jago couldn't lean on a
work object.
No paper, no pen, no phone.
Just him, her and his
handwriting betraying his
handwriting.
Jago came in after eight.
He took off his jacket with the
slowness of someone who already
knew what he'd find.
The house near the Savannah
River smelled of jasmine from
the garden outside.
An out of season sweetness that
only worsened the sensation that
the air was breathing on its
own.
He saw the envelope.
He didn't ask what it was.
Inside he felt a lying sentence
form before he could stop it.
I was going to tell you and in
the same instant,
new it was false.
He wasn't going to.
If she hadn't found it, that
paper would have died at the
bottom of that drawer.
Rowena, his voice came out too
controlled to be sincere.
It's not what it looks like.
She crossed her arms over her
linen dress.
She didn't sit.
The yellow light of the
chandelier fell between them
like a border.
It's exactly what it looks like
Jago.
He breathed in deep.
The cold panic settled between
one river and another.
That old cold he knew from
another night, 10 years ago.
He swallowed twice before he
managed to speak.
I wanted to protect you.
From a job offer.
From an offer that was going to
take you away from Savannah for
six months.
Rowena smiled without joy.
And the decision to go or stay
was yours.
He opened his mouth and found no
answer.
She continued lower because the
low voice hurt more.
You answered for me.
You said, thank you for me.
You declined for me.
Each sentence fell like a small
stone into the bottom of a
glass.
And then you brought me
breakfast.
Rowena.
No.
She raised her hand.
And her hand was trembling and
she hated that.
You're not going to ask me for
time.
Time is the one thing you
shouldn't ask for today.
You had six months.
He took a step toward her.
She took a step back.
It was a small movement.
But he felt as if he'd been
shoved against the opposite wall
of the room.
Inside something in him.
The part that was always certain
began to crack.
He watched her mouth pronounce
the next sentence before he
heard it.
Who is Kit?
The name fell to the dining room
floor and stayed there gleaming.
Jago looked at the envelope.
Looked at her.
Looked at the window that faced
the dark river outside.
He said nothing.
And his silence was the first
real confession.
Good night, Jago.
She went up the stairs slowly.
He stood beside the table for
too long listening to her
footsteps disappear into the
upstairs hallway.
Then he sat in the nearest chair
elbows on his knees and stared
at his own envelope as if
the paper were capable of
answering for him.
Rowena didn't sleep.
She spent the small hours with
her eyes open at the ceiling of
the guest room.
That room she'd never entered
before and where the sheets
smelled of forgotten lavender.
She mentally repeated the list
of things she knew.
The name, the chair, the
terrace.
Udora's remark about a laugh
that wasn't hers.
The payments she hadn't yet
traced.
The envelope answered in his
handwriting.
There were two stories being
hidden.
She needed to unravel both.
In the morning before the sun
rose fully, she called a taxi
from the street.
She didn't ask for a house car.
She didn't tell Fielen.
She put on the plainest clothes
she had and went out the side
door and no guard saw her,
because no guard expected her to
leave before six in the morning.
Silas Ashford's office was in
downtown Savannah in an old
townhouse with tall windows
and a permanent smell of coffee
and old paper.
The sun hadn't yet warm the
sidewalk when she climbed the
steps.
Silas answered the door himself.
He didn't even ask what she
wanted.
He just pointed to the chair in
front of the desk.
You already know why I'm here.
I'm pretty sure I do.
Silas poured two coffees without
asking.
And I'm pretty sure I shouldn't
open my mouth.
Roeena accepted the coffee and
didn't drink it.
Silas.
Her voice came out firmer than
she expected.
Your his friend, I know that.
But you were also the only one
who looked me in the eye that
night at the ball
and didn't pretend not to see
what you were seeing.
I need to know who kit is.
Silas let the coffee rest
between his hands.
He stared at the tabletop for
long enough
that Roeena understood the
answer would hurt him too.
Kit was his brother.
He said it last.
Younger.
Was.
That's what they say in
Savannah.
And what do you say?
Silas raised his eyes.
There was a new caution in them.
The caution of someone crossing
a line and knowing it.
I say there was a boating
accident 10 years ago
that the boat was found
destroyed.
That the family buried a closed
casket.
He paused.
And that Jego never believed it.
Roeena felt her own chest drop.
Why did he never believe it?
Silas shook his head slowly.
Roeena.
Not today.
Not this.
This isn't mine to tell.
Silas.
I've already said more than I
should.
He looked at the door.
Go home ask him.
He won't answer me.
Then come back here when he
doesn't.
She got up.
At the door she stopped.
She didn't look back when she
said.
Thank you.
Silas didn't answer.
He kept looking at her coffee
that hadn't been drunk.
And for the first time in 10
years,
he felt he might be betraying
the right friend.
Back at the house near the
river.
Roeena found Neve in the
kitchen,
arranging sprigs of basil in a
glass jar.
The old housekeeper had her hair
pinned up in a loose bun
and wore the same grey apron as
always.
Roeena stopped in the doorway
for a second before going in.
Neve belonged to that house more
than Jego belonged to it.
If anyone knew, it was her.
Neve.
The woman looked up.
She smiled with that small smile
she kept for Roeena.
Good morning dear.
Shall I make some tea?
Neve.
Who is kid?
The smile disappeared so fast
that Roeena almost doubted it
had existed.
Neve's hands gripped the jar too
hard.
One of the sprigs slipped and
fell into the sink.
Oh dear.
Please.
Neve looked at the door leading
to the hallway.
She looked at the window that
faced the garden,
where the morning Jasmine was
still closed.
She looked at the counter as if
the answer might be printed on
the marble.
It's not my place.
I know it isn't.
Roeena took a step closer,
but I've been sleeping in this
house for six months.
And I can't pretend anymore that
I don't see.
He avoids the terrace.
You avoid answering.
Mrs. Udora has never said that
name near me.
And last night I asked my
husband,
the word slipped out before she
could choose another.
And he went silent.
Neve closed her eyes.
He avoids the terrace.
The voice came out broken almost
inaudible,
because that's where the boat
set out that night.
Roeena didn't move.
What night, Neve?
The night.
Neve wiped her hands on her
apron.
A mechanical gesture.
The only night.
The one this family could never
bury properly.
She turned her face aside.
Don't ask me for the rest dear.
Please.
Roeena swallowed hard.
Mr. Kitt.
Neve continued.
And now she was speaking to the
basil, not to her.
At a way of laughing loud.
Mrs. Udora used to say he'd wake
the whole
house when he was a child.
A small smile crossed her face
and vanished.
It was a beautiful laugh.
Too full for that mouth.
You have his laugh.
Roeena had to grip the counter.
The air went out of her slowly.
Her hand pressed on the cold
marble.
The certainty assembling inside
her ribs like an old building
rising from the dark.
Whose laugh it was.
Where the sentence came from.
Why Udora had looked at her that
way.
As she left that night at the
ball.
Thank you, Neve.
Dear.
The housekeeper held her arm for
a second.
Her fingers were firm and dry.
He suffered.
Don't let anger make you forget
that.
I won't forget.
The weekend passed in a silence
of war.
Jego didn't try to enter the
guest room.
Roeena didn't come down from
meals.
Feeling carried trays in
silence.
Left them outside the door.
Collected them untouched.
On Saturday afternoon, Roeena
wrote in her planner.
The list of everything she
needed to trace.
Payments.
Names.
Cities.
Dates.
She started with the public
library in downtown Savannah,
where the old newspapers were
kept on microfilm.
She spent hours hunched over a
reader that hummed softly.
The smell of dry paper and old
air conditioning filling the
small room.
She found the headline she knew
existed.
Quint Air Missing After Coastal
Storm.
The photo was small, grainy.
A young man smiling with his
mouth open.
His teeth a little crooked.
His hair touseled by the wind.
She looked at the face for a
long time.
There was something of Jego in
it.
In the shape of the eyes in the
line of the jaw.
There was also that Frank Lough,
Nieve, had described.
Too wide for a newspaper
portrait impossible to contain.
On Sunday, she cross-referenced
information.
She asked feeling for old
statements with some excuse.
And the assistant, who already
liked her more than he should,
gave in without asking.
She found regular payments going
out of a parallel account of
Jego's.
Monthly.
Always the same rounded amount.
Always to the office of a lawyer
with no recognizable family
name.
She found receipts from a
pharmacy in a small town she'd
never heard of.
She found, among the clippings,
Nieve kept in an old envelope in
the kitchen cabinet.
A photo, where a teenage kid
appeared beside an older man.
The same face she'd recognized
in the more recent records.
Marlo called it three in the
morning on Monday.
Roeena answered on the second
ring.
Roe, I had the strange feeling
that you needed to laugh.
Marlo.
Seriously, I was asleep.
Woke up out of nowhere.
Looked at the ceiling and
thought,
this woman needs to laugh right
now.
Roeena laughed.
She laughed for real mouth open
in the middle of the silent
guest room.
Then she started to cry and kept
laughing,
and Marlo on the other end
stayed quiet,
waiting for the hurricane to
pass.
I found out the name Roeena said
when she was able.
The kid guy, he was his brother,
was, that's what Silas said.
Marlo breathed in deep and do
you believe it?
I believe nobody pays for a
pharmacy for a dead man.
Silas on the other end.
Then, Roe, Marlo's voice was
serious now.
Are you sure you want to go down
this hole?
I already have.
Then hold on tight.
Roeena looked at the planner
open on the mattress,
and address had appeared twice
in the receipts.
A small town a few hours by
train from Savannah,
a name that matched the man from
the old photo.
She circled everything in red
pen,
and underlined the address three
times,
the pressure of the pen leaving
a groove on the paper below.
On the other side of the house,
Jego was sitting in the study
with a glass of whiskey he
hadn't touched in hours.
He'd heard the taxi arrive in
the morning,
he'd heard the taxi leave.
He'd heard Roeena ask feeling
for the statements,
with an excuse he knew because
he himself was the one,
who'd used that excuse decades
ago.
He knew she was piecing it
together.
He knew she was going to find
it,
and for the first time in 10
years,
he couldn't tell whether he was
afraid of what she'd discover,
or afraid of what he'd feel when
she knew.
He ran his hand over his
forehead,
his hand was trembling.
In the guest room, Roeena closed
the planner,
a name, an address, a small
town,
everything that had come before.
The old story, the charade at
the ball, the coffee,
without a recorder, had been
training for this decision.
She turned off the light, and in
the dark,
she heard clearly the sound the
empty chair made inside her now.
It was no longer a creek, it was
a whole name.
Chapter 4, The Town With No
Name.
In a scaven on Tuesday morning,
and he gave in because Roeena
stopped asking.
She walked into his office
without knocking.
She placed the open planner on
his desk,
the address circled in red,
the name of the man from the old
photo written beside it.
She said nothing.
Silas read it, leaned back
against the chair and closed his
eyes for a moment,
like someone who knew this
moment would come sooner or
later,
and had chosen too late.
You got to this on your own.
I get to almost everything on my
own, Silas.
The open his eyes, there was
guilt in them now.
An old guilty no longer tried to
disguise beneath the efficiency
of the faithful assistant.
If I complete the picture,
Jago will kill me.
Jago is already dying inside
Silas.
She said,
what do you want?
To bury both of them.
Silas kept looking at her for a
length of time
that seemed to stretch beyond
how long Silas usually lasts.
Then he opened a desk drawer,
and took out a small card no
letterhead,
with a name written by hand on
one side,
and an address on the other.
He slid it across the desk with
two fingers,
like someone handing something
over,
and at the same time apologizing
for having taken so long.
The man who carries the money is
this one.
His voice came out low, almost
horse.
He lives between Savannah and
the town.
He makes the trip by train once
a month,
always on the first Saturday.
He tapped the card lightly.
Kid lives in that town under
another name.
I'm not going to tell you which.
That he'll have to tell you
himself,
Ruinna took the card.
She felt the paper way more than
it should,
more than any paper card should
weigh.
Thank you.
Ruinna, Silas leaned forward his
elbows on the desk.
If he doesn't want to come back,
don't force it.
He has that right.
I won't force it.
And please, his voice nearly
broke before reaching the end of
the sentence.
Take care of Jago when you come
back.
She tucked the card into the
inside pocket of her bag.
She stood up.
She was almost at the door when
he spoke again.
Ruinna, yes.
By now, why did you tell me now?
He took a while to answer.
When he answered, he looked at
the window,
not at her.
At the street below where
Savannah went on a head,
knowing nothing.
Because I watched Jago spend 10
years dying slowly,
and I watched you arrive and him
start to live again.
And I can't watch him lose you
thinking he's protecting you.
He turned his gaze back to her.
Someone needs to break this
cycle.
You're the only one with the
courage to break it.
Ruinna nodded once.
She left.
Outside Savannah's air had that
humid mid-afternoon heat.
Dense and green, with the smell
of wet earth mixed with the
distant salt of the
estuary.
She walked to the station
without hurry,
feeling the uneven paving under
her shoes.
The sounds of the city around
her.
The street car passing by, a
child shouting in some backyard.
The clinking of glasses in a
corner cafe.
She bought a one-way ticket for
the four-ocluck train,
and called Marlo from the
payphone.
I'm going.
Alone?
Alone.
Marlo paused for a long time.
The kind that contains questions
one decides not to ask.
Do you want me to call someone
if you don't come back in 24
hours?
Call Silas.
Done.
Before boarding.
Ruinna stopped at the house near
the river.
She came in through the side
door.
Went up to the guest room
through some clothes into a
small suitcase,
with the objectivity of someone
who knows that thinking too much
is a luxury that doesn't fit in
the luggage.
She went down to the kitchen,
where the afternoon light came
in slanted through the shutters,
and drew thin stripes across the
stone floor,
and wrote a short letter on a
piece of writing paper.
The letter had a single line.
I'll come back when I bring what
he couldn't bring on his own.
She left the letter on top of
the day's newspaper.
She left.
Feline saw her come down the
stairs with the suitcase,
and asked nothing.
She asked him to call a taxi.
He called one.
Before the taxi door closed,
the assistant said quietly
almost to himself,
have a good trip miss.
She didn't correct him.
The train left Savannah at four
o'clock sharp.
Roenachosa seat by the window,
and rested her forehead against
the cold glass,
and for a long time thought
about nothing.
She passed low houses, flooded
fields,
a small town with a rusty water
tower in the center,
a river that wasn't the
Savannah,
a line of Cyprus's cutting into
the copper-coloured sky of the
late afternoon.
The sun began to set slowly,
tinting the landscape and orange
that looked like a painting.
She opened the planner and
re-read the address three times
as if she could forget it,
and she knew she couldn't.
On the other side at the house
near the river,
Jager arrived at seven at night
and felt that something was
missing before he looked in any
direction.
It was as if the house had
changed weight,
not temperature, not sound,
weight.
He passed through the living
room the kitchen,
saw the letter on top of the
newspaper.
He read it.
He read it again,
and something in him collapsed
with the same silent precision
of a structure
that gives way from within,
with no visible warning.
It was the same old night
returning to his nostrils,
the smell of the sea after the
storm,
the taste of metal in his mouth,
the physical animal certainty
that he had lost again,
and that this time the
punishment was proportional to
the size of the mistake.
He let the letter drop.
He sat on the kitchen floor.
He truly sat.
His back against the door of the
low cabinet
and his hands open on his knees
as if he didn't know what to do
with them.
He stayed there too long for it
to be dignity.
Scyl is showed up half an hour
later.
He hadn't been called, he simply
knew.
He came in through the side
door,
found Jager on the floor,
knelt beside him without
hesitation.
I told her,
Jager raised his face slowly.
There was something in his eyes
that wasn't anger.
It was an exhaustion so deep,
it passed beneath the anger,
and reached a place the anger no
longer reached.
You told her what,
the name,
the address,
the man who carries the money.
Jager closed his eyes.
It took him a full second to
breathe again.
I'm going to hit you siless.
Hit me.
Jager didn't hit him.
He clenched his fist, raised it,
and the fist stopped in the air
before touching anything.
He lowered his hands slowly,
rested it on his knee,
and stared at his own fingers,
as if he didn't recognize them.
As if that man sitting on the
floor of his kitchen
belonged to someone else.
She went alone.
She did,
and if he doesn't take her in.
He'll take her in.
He can't say no to anyone,
Jager.
He never could.
Jager swallowed twice.
And if he takes her in and
doesn't want to come?
Silas didn't answer.
There was no answer to that.
Jager squeezed his eyes shut.
Inside something in him was
reconstructing the timeline
with a precision that hurt.
The train's schedule,
the distance,
the time she'd need to arrive.
The night she'd spend alone in a
town he knew
from a map and from receipts,
but never with his own eyes.
He'd never gone.
He'd never allowed himself to
go,
and now she was going for him.
With the courage he'd traded for
control,
and he was sitting on the
kitchen floor
because he no longer knew what
to do with his own body.
Silas.
Yes.
If she comes back,
I'll fix it.
She'll come back.
If she comes back.
Silas rested his hand on his
shoulder and left it there.
She'll come back, Jager.
In the small town, the train
arrived at 9.20 at night.
Roina got off with the small
suitcase,
felt the asphalt different under
her feet,
quieter without savanna's
constant noise,
and looked for a small hotel a
block from the station,
with painted wooden windows and
a ceiling fan that turned
slowly.
She paid for one night,
went up, didn't have dinner.
She sat on the edge of the bed
until dawn,
with Silas's card in her hand
and the address memorized.
In the morning, she followed the
map on foot.
The town was smaller than she'd
expected,
a main street with five shops,
a central square with a
bandstand painted white and
peeling at the edges,
low houses scattered along dirt
roads where grass grew down the
middle.
The address led her to a modest
light blue house,
with an neglected front garden,
and a rocking chair sitting
motionless on the porch.
She knocked on the door,
once with her knuckle, firm.
A man opened it.
She recognized him before she
looked properly.
She recognized him by the shape
of the eyes,
by the line of the jaw,
by the way he stood in the
doorway.
The same way Jago had a filling
a threshold
that presence that filled the
space even in silence.
Except, this man was thinner,
harder,
with a small scar crossing his
left eyebrow and lighter hair.
Sun bleached.
He had the slightly crooked
teeth she remembered from the
newspaper photo.
Kit, he was paralyzed for a full
second,
then he stepped back half a
step,
who are you?
Rowena Pike, she didn't move
forward.
I've been with your brother for
a while.
The silence that came after was
dense and loaded.
Kit rested one hand on the door
frame,
as if he needed the support,
his fingers gripping the painted
wood.
You shouldn't be here.
I know.
He sent you.
He doesn't even know I came.
Kit looked at her for a long
time.
The physical shock was still in
him,
and the old anger rose
automatically,
and the fear hidden beneath the
anger too,
and there was something else,
deeper, that he could no longer
name well.
Then he stepped aside.
Come in.
The living room was small and
clean,
with that silence of a place
where a person has lived alone
for too long.
There was a dark wooden table,
two chairs, a sofa with warm
fabric on the backrest,
a shelf with few books and no
ornaments.
Kit pointed to one of the
chairs.
Rowena sat, he stayed standing
leaning against the wall arms
crossed.
Talk.
She talked.
She talked for a long time,
without embellishing, without
crying.
She talked about the
investigators Jago had hired
over the years.
About the money he left with
lawyers who had no names,
about the medications paid for
by third parties.
The debts settled before they
became dangerous.
About the empty chair no one
explained and no one removed
from the living room.
She talked about Yudora,
about the way she never said his
name.
About the way once on the porch
she had murmured about a lost
laugh.
She talked about the terrace
Jago avoided.
She talked about the envelope
he'd hidden.
About the control he confused
with love.
About the old fear he carried
because he thought that if he
let go,
he'd lose everything again.
Kit listened without
interrupting.
When she finished, he stayed
silent for a while.
Then he laughed.
A short, dry laugh.
Almost a grunt.
He spent 10 years looking for
me.
He did.
Without stopping.
And he never came himself.
Roena hesitated.
He thought you didn't want to be
found by him.
Kit closed his eyes.
Inside something that had been
hard for 10 years began to
crack.
Slow and inevitable as a crack
in stone.
He swallowed once.
swallowed again.
He wasn't wrong.
He was.
Roena's voice came out lower.
He just didn't know he was.
Kit peeled himself off the wall.
He went to the window.
Looked at the neglected garden
for a long time at the grass
growing between the
cowl-mate coffee.
They spent the afternoon and the
night talking.
On the porch with cups that went
cold twice in the sound of
crickets filling the dark around
them, Kit spoke aloud for the
first time about what he felt.
He said he'd fled because he
thought he wasn't important to
anyone.
But on that night, he'd asked
his brother for help and his
brother hadn't come.
And he understood, in that
instant, that his world was
worth less than a meeting.
That when the boat began to
crack in the storm, he had two
seconds to choose between
swimming
or sinking.
And he chose to swim because the
anger was greater than the
exhaustion.
That when he came out the other
side, on a stretch of beach he
didn't even know where it was.
He made the decision to
disappear because he thought no
one would miss him enough to
really
look.
And he looked, Kit said, looking
at the bandstand in the square
in the distance.
All these years.
Kit ran his hand over his eyes
slowly.
He made a mistake out of fear,
Kit.
Not out of choice.
Browiness spoke low, looking at
the same point he was.
He's afraid of you all the time.
Of what happened, and of what he
didn't do.
Kit laughed again.
This time without the dryness of
before, almost with affection.
And affection he clearly hadn't
expected to feel.
You talk about him as if you
knew him.
I know him.
You love him.
She didn't answer.
She didn't need to.
They stayed silent for a while.
With the warm wind passing
through the branches of the old
Magnolia,
growing in the corner of the
garden,
then Kit spoke, looking at his
own hands.
If I come back, I come back
once.
No promises.
If it doesn't work, I leave
again.
And this time no one finds me.
Agreed.
And I don't know if I'll be able
to look at him.
You don't need to know that now.
Kit nodded slowly, like someone
making a deal with himself,
as much as with her.
In the morning he took a small
suitcase.
Very small.
Rowina looked at that suitcase
and understood the size of what
he carried.
Not in what was inside, but in
how little there was.
Before they left for the
station, she sent a single
message to Silas,
from the telegraph on the
corner.
We arrived tomorrow, prepare you
Dora.
While they waited for the train
on the wooden bench of the
town's only platform,
Kit looked at the horizon and
said,
without turning his face,
Rowina, yes,
if you brought me here for him,
he swallowed.
Thank you, she didn't answer.
She simply rested her hand over
his hand, and his hand was cold,
and hers was too.
The train whistled in the...
Chapter 5, 10 years in a single
room.
Distance.
Jego didn't sleep.
The house near the Savannah
River was so silent
that he could hear his own pulse
in his throat,
sitting on the study floor
leaning against the shelf,
his suit rumpled and his tie
loose since the small hours.
He counted time by the way the
light came through the window.
First blue, then gray, then a
timid goal that arrived to
insulting for the weight of the
day.
Rowina's letter was still folded
in his lap.
He no longer needed to reread it
to know what was written.
I'll come back when I bring what
he couldn't bring on his own.
Each word weighed more than the
last.
Each word opened a door he'd
kept closed for 10 years,
and pushed him inside it with no
choice, no warning,
without even letting him breathe
first.
Inside, Jego had the cold
certainty that the punishment
had finally arrived,
not in the form of scandal, not
in the form of death,
not in the form of a headline,
in the form of a woman with an
ink scar in the Sunday paper,
going after what he hadn't had
the courage to bring.
And in the most cowardly part of
him,
a low voice said that this scar
could open again,
that this time the woman too
might not come back.
Silas came in at seven without
knocking.
He brought coffee Jego hadn't
asked for,
and a silenced Jego didn't want.
He stood in the door frame
waiting with that lawyer's
patience of someone who'd
already seen too many
clients on the floor of his own
office.
Talk, Jego said without looking
up.
She arrived, she's with him.
How do you know?
She sent me a message.
Short, Silas hesitated, and at
the bottom of that hesitation
there was an old guilt the
lawyer had
decided to carry in silence
until now.
He held out the phone.
Jego read the line on the screen
and took a full second to
breathe again.
We arrived tomorrow.
Prepare you dora.
He closed his eyes.
He felt the room spin as if
someone had flipped the floor.
There was a man inside him who
wanted to yell at Silas for
giving up the thread.
There was another deeper who
wanted to kneel and give thanks.
The first one for half a second.
Jego stood up, grabbed Silas by
the lapel, and stopped his fist
in the air before it closed.
His hand trembled, it never
trembled.
Don't hit, Silas said very low.
You're not a man who hits.
I'm not a man of anything right
now, Jego answered.
And let go of the lapel like
someone releasing a rope too hot
to hold.
They stood still.
Outside a bird insisted on a
whistle of three repeated notes
without tiring, without mercy.
Jego looked at his own
reflection in the glass of the
picture frame,
and recognized neither the
disheveled hair, nor the
civilised despair his eyes held.
Prepare her, he asked, and his
voice didn't quite obey.
Prepare my mother.
I will.
Silas.
Jego swallowed.
Thank you.
Silas looked at him long.
He said nothing.
He left.
It was feeling who arrived first
at the quint mentioned.
Udora was having tea in the
small parlor.
The newspaper still untouched on
the white linen napkin.
The matriarch looked up and
read.
In the younger systems posture,
that something was coming before
the words.
She didn't ask.
She waited, with that old skill
of letting Silas do the work.
Mrs Rowena asked that you come
to the main hall at five.
Feline said, with the trained
delicacy of someone delivering
news he didn't understand.
And Mr. Jego as well.
Udora folded the newspaper
carefully as if it might break.
Her hand, when it rested on the
table, had a strange lightness
for the weight of the day.
That's all?
She wanted to know.
That's all.
The matriarch didn't smile.
She didn't protest.
She nodded once and turned her
gaze to the window.
Where the garden trees swayed in
a breeze no one inside could
feel.
The trainer arrived at four.
Rowena got off on the savanna
platform with the same small bag
she'd left with.
And a thin man beside her who
insisted on keeping three steps
of distance.
Like someone still deciding
whether to stay, or turn around
and disappear again.
Kitt had his head down.
His cap pulled low.
His backpack held tight against
his chest like a shield.
Every sudden noise in the
station made his jaw clench.
He stopped twice on the way to
the taxi.
And both times Rowena pretended
not to see,
continuing to walk at a pace
that demanded nothing.
We can go back.
She said, at the third stop,
without pressure.
If you want to go back now, we
go back.
I'll take you back and won't
tell anyone you set foot in
savanna.
Kitt swallowed.
It's not that.
It's what then.
It's that I forgot what the
smell is like.
Rowena looked at him.
There was an 18-year-old boy
inside that thin man,
and the boy was blinking hard
not to cry on the sidewalk of a
station full of strangers.
She didn't touch his arm.
She just stood there at the same
height waiting.
The smell is the same, she
answered.
Magnolia and old money.
Kitt laughed.
A quick laugh, almost a sob.
Ah!
So it's the same.
They got into the taxi.
Rowena told the driver to stop
at the door.
Chapter 6 The Chair with Anona.
The mansion.
Not at the house near the river.
Kitt raised his face when the
facade appeared.
That heavy iron gate he knew
better than any other place in
the world.
He stared at it for a long time.
A leaf came loose from one of
the tall trees,
and fell on the hood of the car
with a lightness that seemed
calculated.
No one said anything.
I don't know if I can.
Kitt said, low.
You can make it to the door.
After that we decide.
And if they hate me, they don't
hate you.
They don't know how to hate you.
Kitt didn't answer.
The open the car door and got
out slowly.
Like someone stepping onto a
floor that might not hold his
weight.
The main hall smelled of
Magnolia and old money.
The afternoon came in through
the tall windows in bands of
golden light,
that crossed the marble and
stopped at the empty chair near
the window,
as if they knew exactly where to
land.
Rowena went in first.
She deliberately chose that
place.
Not the living room, not the
library, not J. Go's study.
Where everything had begun to
fall apart.
The hall.
The same room where one night,
month earlier,
a woman in a borrowed dress had
held the face of a silent man
and kissed him in front of 300
people.
The smell was the same.
The light came in at the same
angle.
The chair was still empty.
Rowena positioned herself
exactly where she had stood on
that other night.
As if she were marking a fixed
point on a map,
only she knew how to read.
Kitt stayed one step behind,
still in his cap, still with his
hand closed around the strap of
the backpack.
Feline opened the double doors.
Yudora came in first.
The matriarch noticed Rowena,
noticed the figure behind her.
And for a moment, tiny, almost
invisible,
her spine seemed to give way a
millimeter.
She restrained it.
She kept her chin high.
She crossed the hall to the
center and stopped, waiting.
J. Go came in after, and his
world stopped turning.
There was a thin man in the
hall.
Then, with his cap pulled low, a
small scar on his eyebrow,
his shoulders narrower than
memory had drawn them.
A man who slowly lowered the
cap,
revealing his short hair, and
looked up.
And it was the gaze of the
18-year-old boy,
who had taken a boat out alone
on a stormy night,
ten years before.
J. Go said nothing for a length
of time, no one there could
measure.
He took a step than another.
Then he stopped.
Inside it was as if a dam had
given way.
The old guilt, the anguish of
the last two days,
the fear of losing Rowena, all
mixing into a single hot point
in the middle of his chest,
too hot to be born with
composure.
He felt his throat tightened.
He felt his hands go cold.
He felt with brutal clarity that
the punishment hadn't come.
That life, against any
deserving, had given something
back.
Kit, he said.
And his voice came out choked,
ridiculous.
The voice of a big boy that
didn't fit that man.
Kit, Kit dropped the backpack on
the floor.
The thud was dry on the marble.
I ran away, he said, and his
mouth trembled.
I ran away because I thought I
wasn't important to anyone.
J. Go closed his eyes.
A tear fell before he could
command his body to hold it
back.
Then another. He didn't wipe
them.
I spent ten years, he answered,
trying to fix the worst choice
of my life.
Kit shook his head incredulous,
and the shaking became a tremor,
and the tremor became a short
dry sob.
J. Go crossed the rest of the
hall in three strides,
and hugged his brother any which
way.
A crooked hug without elegance,
without the composure all of
Savannah knew.
A hug that had waited ten years
to happen,
and that now happened all at
once, clumsy, and urgent.
Kit was slow to return it.
When he did, he gripped J. Go's
coat,
as if he were holding on so as
not to fall.
J. Go's coat at the back had
stopped breathing.
The feared matriarch, the woman
who demanded proof of love in
the middle of a crowded hall,
the woman Roena had met with
eyes of steel, took a step
forward,
then another. And with no
audience, without elegance,
without any of the posture all
of Savannah knew by heart,
J. Go's coat on the marble floor
beside her lost son.
The tweed dress folded like an
old cloth.
A hand sought Kit's face without
the courage to touch it right
away.
My boy, she said, and the
knife-edged voice became a voice
with no edge.
My boy, Kit turned to his mother
and couldn't speak.
He just rested his forehead on
her shoulder.
Udora closed her arms around her
son with a care no one ever had
seen that woman show.
Roena watched from the doorway,
inside she felt her body way
from two sides at once.
There was relief, yes, the real,
physical relief
of seeing the family finally
occupy the space it needed to
occupy.
And there was an exhaustion she
hadn't noticed accumulate,
until the adrenaline dropped for
good. The last 48 hours had
taken everything,
and there was two something hard
in the middle of her chest,
something that made her
understand that this moment
belonged to those three and that
she didn't need to sign it.
She took a step back, then
another. She closed the double
doors in silence.
The veranda facing the savanna
river had a warm late afternoon
wind,
Roena leaned against the cold
stone parapet,
and watched the water dark and
little by little.
The reflection of the light
going away in wide slow bands.
She didn't cry. She felt inside
her chest a new stillness,
the kind that only arrives after
days that are too long,
when the body finally drops its
guard because it has nowhere
left to put the tension.
Jego found her there ten minutes
later.
He'd washed his face, his suit
was still rumpled. His eyes
still red settled on her
before any words and stayed
there. Heavy.
As if they needed to confirm
that she was real and that she
was standing,
he stopped three steps away. He
didn't come closer.
Any word he realized would be
too small. Any sentence would
sound like a clause,
and he'd already spent six
months signing clauses with her
without asking permission for
it.
So he stayed quiet. He just
stood there, looking at her as
if it were the first time.
You brought him. He said it
last. I brought him. I don't
know how to thank you.
Don't thank me. It's not the
kind of thing you thank someone
for.
He nodded, a nod that was almost
a bow. The river below kept
darkening,
indifferent to the weight of
that veranda. A girl crossed the
sky in a lazy arc.
Ruinna felt the warmth of his
body near hers without needing
to look to be sure.
There was magnetism there. The
same as always. The same that
had risen up her back on a
beside him. There was a new
distance. A distance she decided
to preserve for now.
I need to sleep alone tonight.
She said, Jego took a second. He
didn't protest. He didn't make a
face.
He didn't embed any request
disguised as agreement. That's
fine. Ruinna turned her face to
him.
It's the first time in six
months you've given me an answer
without packaging. He almost
smiled.
Almost. I'm learning. He
answered. Very low. There was
exhaustion in his face.
But there was also something
open she'd never seen there
before. He wasn't the man of
ice.
He wasn't the man of calculated
control. He was a man who had
seen his brother alive after 10
years and no longer knew what to
do with his own chest. Tomorrow
will talk. She said,
Tomorrow I'll ask. He said, if
you'll let me. She nodded. He
raised his hand toward her face,
stopped halfway and lowered his
arm. The interrupted gesture
weighed more than the touch
would have
Ruinna inside understood that he
had understood. She went down
the veranda stairs without
hurry.
Feline took her to the house
near the river. Jego went back
inside to the family he had
forgotten
how to embrace without a
contract. That night in the
kitchen of the house near the
river,
Ruinna drank a glass of water in
silence and looked at the phone
on the table. There were no
messages. For the first time in
six months, no one knew where
she was because no one had been
put in
place to know. She turned off
the kitchen light and the
darkness arrived with a calm
that seemed
at last deserved. On the other
side of the city, in a room he
hadn't been in for 10 years,
Jego quint personally made up
his brother's bed, folded the
blanket, opened the window two
fingers to let the air in, and
sat on the hallway floor until
dawn, with the door a jar
listening
to kit sleep. Sunday morning
arrived at the house near the
Savannah River, with a low,
wary light that came through the
cracks in the curtains, like
someone asking permission.
Ruinna was in the kitchen.
Barefoot, with a cold mug in her
hands, she hadn't slept well.
The two wide bed had felt wide
in a new way, without anger and
without peace, only with a
question waiting for its answer
outside the door. She heard the
engine before she heard the foot
steps.
A car stopped on the gravel. The
door closed with the care of
someone who knew the whole house
was listening. Jego appeared in
the kitchen doorway, with the
cream envelope open in his hand.
He had no jacket. He had the
rumpled shirt of someone who'd
spent the night sitting on a
hallway
floor. He stopped two steps from
her, as if asking permission to
cross that last stretch of
floor. May I? He asked. Ruinna
nodded. He came. He set the
envelope on the table between
them,
facing her. The letter was
already unfolded inside. She
recognized the letter head, the
header,
the short paragraph that month's
earlier had been intercepted
before reaching her. They wanted
you for a series of long
reports, Jego said, his voice
low almost crumpled. In depth
investigation
no short deadline. Your by-line
on every piece I read it when it
came. I answered for you.
I wrote with thanks no. I lied
about it every day since. She
looked at the letter.
Then at his face. Jego was pale
in a way different from the
night of the phone call.
That whiteness wasn't fear of
what she'd find out. It was
shame at what he'd done.
Why, Ruinna asked without
sharpness? Just needing to hear
it. Because I was afraid you'd
accept,
he answered. The pause. Because
I was even more afraid you'd
accept and be away some nights.
I was certain without ever
having proof that if I let you
out of my sight, the world would
carry
something away. He swallowed
hard. He knew the size of his
own mistake. In you love isn't
protected
by locking a door. In you he'd
confused devotion with
possession. The choice he said,
was always yours. I took it off
the table. I'm giving it back
now. Ruinna felt her own chin
tremble without falling into
tears. She took the phone from
the counter and held it out to
him.
Start with the guards she asked.
He took the device without
arguing. He dialed from memory.
The head of the team's voice
answered on the second ring.
Jego spoke while looking at her.
Pull both teams from the house
today. Pull the two that follow
Mrs. Pike as well.
From now on, no one follows
anyone. He heard a question from
the other end that Ruinna didn't
hear. No, no replacement, no
exception. Terminate the
contract. He hung up. He handed
the phone back.
He stood there waiting for the
next verdict without trying to
soften anything. Ruinna breathed
in
deep. Something inside her
loosened a cord she hadn't
noticed had been pulled tort for
months.
She didn't smile. It was still
too early. What do you want for
dinner? Jego asked.
The question was small and
ridiculous and perfect. She
laughed before the tear fell. He
raised his hand
slowly, touched her cheek like
someone asking permission and
the tear stayed between them.
Something we make together, she
answered. He nodded. He said
nothing more. He stayed. And
staying.
There was the only big word that
made sense. They spent the day
slowly. He chopped vegetables.
With the exaggerated technique
of someone who'd learned late.
She laughed at the way he held
the knife.
Kit called from the room Udora
had prepared at the mansion and
said he was going to bed early.
His voice lighter than the day
before. Silas sent a dry message
asking if he was allowed to
breathe.
Marlo sent a two minute voice
memo praising her own sense of
timing for staying quiet.
Everyone from a distance gave
the house near the river. The
silence it needed to fit back
into them.
At night the kitchen went dark
without anyone turning on the
light.
They went up the stairs
together. It wasn't urgent. It
wasn't ceremonial.
It was hand in hand like two
people tired of themselves. In
the main bedroom the window was
open
and the river sent in a thin
breeze that smelled of wet
leaves. Jego closed the door
with his shoulder
without hurry. He stood looking
at Roenah for a length of time
neither of them could count.
Deep down in him. Desire mixed
with a new caution. She was no
longer just the body he knew.
She was the body that had
decided to come back even
knowing the price
and that made his hands clumsy
on purpose. Roenah took the
first step. She rested her palm
on his face.
His mouth met her palm before it
met her mouth. A small kiss on
the hand. A request for
permission that hadn't been in
either of their scripts. She
felt the day old stubble scratch
her skin.
She felt his warm breath. She
felt the decision to be there
release from within her chest
and become
body. He rested his forehead on
hers before kissing her. He
stayed there for a long time.
Breath against breath. Inside
him a sentence formed without
leaving his mouth. If I have to
prove it every day I'll prove
it. She too had one that didn't
come out. I didn't come because
I
forgave everything. I came
because I want to be here. It
was she who said the outward one
first.
Her mouth on his jaw. I'm not
here because I forgave
everything. I'm here because I
want to be.
He squeezed his eyes shut. He
let the answer fall very low.
Almost into her neck. I know.
The kiss came after that.
Different from the one month's
earlier in the hall of Magnolia
and old
money. There was no audience
there, no arrangement, no
counting. There was only the
care of two
people recognizing each other
after having lost sight of one
another inside the same house.
He ran his hand down the nape of
her neck, down her spine, and
stopped flat in the middle of
her back.
The same gesture as the first
kiss, with a different weight.
Rowena recognized the hand. She
recognized the new intention
within it. The clothes gave way
slowly.
He undied each button of her
blouse as if it were a sentence
chosen with care,
revealing the thin fabric of the
bra that barely contained the
soft curve of her breasts.
His fingers brushed the exposed
skin of her belly, tracing light
lines that made her abdomen
contract in anticipation. She
opened his shirt to the middle
of his chest and felt his heart
against her palm. He was
trembling inside in a way that
didn't show in his gestures.
She kissed the base of his neck,
pressing her lips with growing
delicacy,
feeling the quickened pulse
there. She heard his breath
falter, as it had faltered that
first
night in the hall. She kept the
echo. Her hand slid over his
shoulders,
pushing the shirt down until it
fell to the floor, exposing the
warm skin of his torso.
He returned the favor, sliding
the straps of the bra down her
arms,
freeing her full breasts. His
thumbs circled her nipples with
slow, reverent touches,
hardening them under the soft
pressure, before tilting his
head to capture one of them
between
his lips, sucking with a
measured rhythm while his tongue
traced precise circles.
Rowena arched her back offering
more, and he switched to the
other breast lightly nipping at
the sensitive skin around it. He
laid her down slowly on the bed.
He stayed
propped up on his elbows just
looking. She felt shame and then
let the shame go. He kissed the
bone of her shoulder, the curve
of her collarbone, the exact
spot where she had a small mole
he'd never remarked on out loud,
and that he now recognized with
his mouth. She laughed softly.
He smiled against her skin.
There was a slow part in which
the two of them lay breathing
against each other, hands
wandering slowly. His palms
explored the side of her ribs,
descending to her hips,
squeezing the soft flesh of her
thighs to part them gently.
Rowena turned her body slightly,
tracing kisses descending down
his chest, down his firm
abdomen,
until she reached the line of
hair that led lower. She slid
her hand over his shaft,
feeling it hardened completely
under her fingers, warm and
pulsing. She leaned in and
wrapped
the head with her lips, sucking
slowly while her tongue swirled
around it,
exploring every vein in texture.
He moaned low. His fingers
tangling in her hair without
forcing,
only following the movement. He
pulled her up with tenderness,
reversing their positions. His
lips descended down her body,
kissing the valley between her
breasts, her navel, until
reaching
the soft mound. His hands opened
her thighs more widely, and his
mouth found the wet, warm
center.
His tongue licked slowly along
the cleft, savoring her taste.
Then circled the swollen
clitoris with precision,
alternating soft sucks and quick
touches that made her tremble.
Rowena gripped the sheets, her
hips rising instinctively
against his face, the pleasure
building in deep waves. They
moved together adjusting each
other's bodies until she could
keep
attending to his shaft with her
mouth while he devoured her sex.
The soft sounds of sucking
and broken breaths filled the
room. Their bodies writhing in
perfect sync, each oral
caress bringing the other closer
to the edge without allowing
release yet. The urgency rose
suddenly and he positioned her
facing him, looking into her
eyes with an intensity that
confirmed
the mutual desire. She nodded
with her chin, he entered her
slowly. The thick shaft sliding
inch by inch through the wet
tight opening, filling her
completely until their hips met.
The first breath she released
was more relief than pleasure.
The relief of recognizing
someone she
thought had ended up on the
other side of a door. The
rhythms swung between a care
that almost hurt,
and an urgency they both knew
was the longing releasing. He
moved in deep, measured thrusts,
rotating his hips to brush
internal points that made her
moan, with drawing almost
completely
before sinking back in, feeling
her walls puls around him. She
bit his lip, laughed
cried a tear that he kissed
without asking why. He
understood. Stay, she asked,
without needing
to finish. He had already
stayed. He quickened the rhythm,
one hand braised beside her head
while
the other slid between their
bodies to stimulate the clitoris
with firm circles of his thumb.
Each penetration was more
intense, the wet sound of
colliding bodies echoing, the
sweat mixing
on their skin. Roenoraptor legs
around his waist pulling him
deeper, her breasts pressed
against
his chest, her nipples brushing
with every movement. She came
first. In a low arch that
blotted out everything around
her for a few seconds, the
orgasm passed through her like a
violent
wave, her sex contracting
rhythmically around his shaft.
The intense pleasure radiating
from
the inside out in spasms that
left her breathless. A whole
body trembling while successive
waves made her arch and moan his
name. He came next. His face
buried in her neck, saying her
name
against her skin. Only the first
name, low, no surname, like
someone writing on a fogged
pain.
His climax burst hot and
abundant inside her. The shaft
pulsing hard with each spurred.
His
body tensing entirely before
relaxing over hers. The two of
them united in the shared
climax.
Breaths intertwined, hearts
beating in the same quickened
rhythm. They stayed like that
for
long minutes. The shaft still
half erect inside her. Their
bodies entangled in a
traced light patterns with his
fingertips along her spine,
descending to the curve of her
buttocks. While she stroked the
hair at the nape of his neck,
feeling the goosebumps under her
touch. The room seemed smaller,
more intimate, wrapped in the
smell of skin, satisfied desire
and
something deeper that reaffirmed
itself with each beat of the
heart. Little by little the
movement
slowed to lazy touches. Soft
kisses on shoulders and chins.
Glances that said everything
the
begun with the recognition in
the kiss, now sealed itself in
the post-pleasure stillness,
where each shared breath
reinforced the certainty that
this time, they wouldn't lose
each other again.
They stayed there. Their
breathing took time to steady.
He didn't pull away right away.
She ran her fingers through his
hair. He rested his forehead on
hers.
I don't know how to do this
right, he said, to love without
holding on. I don't know how
to
then we learn together. Little
by little, she said. He nodded
against her forehead and stayed
there. A silent seal, with no
word over top of it. In the
following weeks, Kitt gradually
settled
into his old room at the Quint
Mansion, Houdora, who had always
known how to receive my
questies and senators with
equally calibrated coldness,
didn't know how to receive a sun
back.
She learned at breakfast,
without a manual. She sat on the
other side of the table and
served
jam without asking. The way Kitt
had liked it when he was 14.
Kitt let her. The silences hurt
less each day. Marlo adopted
Kitt at the first lunch where
she was introduced to him. She
called
him borrowed brother. And the
next day she was already sending
jokes by note to his room.
Silas appointed himself a
official godfather of no more
dropping the ball. An expression
he
repeated with the face of a
serious lawyer every time Jago
hesitated before any decision
involving
Roenah. Roenah accepted the
offer from the intercepted
letter, with the terms
rearranged by herself.
She wrote the first report in 15
days, then another. Then a
third, that Hollis Vaughan read
from
a far and didn't comment on.
Automize, the wedding was on an
autumn afternoon. In a garden of
old
trees and moss hanging from the
branches far from any hall.
There was no society
photographer,
no published list, no orchestra.
There was a string quartet that
played softly enough
to let the birds keep singing
over it. Kneeve held the bouquet
before the ceremony with a
reverence
no one asked for. She cried
without hiding it when she
handed it over. Roenah kissed
her cheek.
Kitt stood to the groom's left,
in a charcoal gray suit that
Silas had helped choose. The
scar on
his eyebrow had softened over
the last months. He looked at
his brother when Roenah began to
walk,
and Jago looked back, and for a
few seconds that Holl garden fit
into a single frame.
You'd or a cried without hiding
it, seated in the first row,
with a handkerchief she never
got
around to using. Besides her,
the chair that months earlier
would have stayed empty was
occupied
by Kitt, who had settled in next
to his mother between the
ceremony and the toast. No one
explained.
There was no need. Marlo gave a
short, sharp speech. She began
by saying she'd be brief
because,
long love puts you to sleep and
drew a laugh even from Udora.
She looked at Roenah and said,
you were the best journalist in
this city when I met you. You
still are. Only now you right by
choice,
not by fright. And that's the
only thing I've wanted for you
since the very first pre-dorn we
answered the phone crying.
Roenah laughed with a runny
nose. Jago squeezed her hand.
Silas raised his
glass a little later, and
mentioned in passing that a
certain airis had gotten engaged
to
a
one, and also in passing, poor
banker. They laughed. A telegram
arrived by Fielens' hand,
Roenah recognized the
handwriting even before reading
it. Paulis Vaughan had sent
forwards.
Good luck in there. She tucked
the folded paper into the pocket
of her dress. There were things
that got resolved without a big
letter. Only with a dry line
from someone who once asked for
more
than they had a right to, Dyson,
the following winter came softly
to the house near the river.
That morning had a pale, clean
light with no wind. Roenah was
in the kitchen in a robe,
her pinned up hair loose. Jago
came down in his socks, with the
face of someone who'd woken up
happy and didn't quite know why
yet. She took his hand before he
could take his coffee. She
carried
it to her own belly. She kept
looking at him. Jago took a full
second to understand. When he
understood, his eyes filled and
didn't overflow. He rested his
forehead on hers without
speaking.
The hand that was over her belly
stayed there quiet. The same way
it had lain flat on her back
in the middle of the night.
Since when, he asked quietly,
almost into her mouth. It's
still early,
Roenah said, but it is. He
breathed in deep. He laughed
without sound. He stayed there
with his forehead
pressed to hers for a long time
without needing to say anything
big. On the other side of the
kitchen,
the living room opened in
silence toward the river. Roenah
looked over his shoulder.
Near the window, in the chair
that for months had stayed empty
without anyone explaining,
someone was sitting. Kitt was
reading the newspaper with a
steaming mug beside him. His
hair
still wet from the shower. His
feet resting on the stool. He
felt her gaze, looked up, smiled
with just one corner of his
mouth. He went back to the
newspaper. Jago looked too. He
stayed there
a second. He squeezed Roenah's
hand more firmly over their own
child. The winter light crossed
the
on Jago's arm on Roenah's belly.
The empty chair at last had an
owner.