I  woke  before  her  like  always.  The  thin  July
light  slipped  through  the  half  open  curtain,
and  fell  in  a  slanted  stripe  across  Islander's  bear  shoulder.
I  stayed  still,
propped  on  my  elbow,  watching  her  face  as  she  slept.
A  mouth  slightly  parted.  Her  dark  hair
spread  across  the  pillow  on  my  side  of  the  bed.  One  hand
curled  near  her  chin  like  a  child's.
The  air  conditioner  hummed  low  almost  imperceptible,  and
there  was  a  scent  of  jasmine  coming
from  the  window.  She'd  insisted  on  planting  jasmine  on
the  balcony,  and  I'd  let  it  happen
without  arguing,  which  said  a  lot  about  what  she'd  done  to
me.  There  was  a  time  when  I  couldn't
sleep  in  that  suite.  Now  it  was  the  opposite.  I
couldn't  leave  it  without  first  making  sure  she  was
still  there.  I  admitted  inwardly,  something  I
still  felt  embarrassed  to  say  out  loud.  I  was  happy.
The  words  sounded  strange  in  my  head.  Almost  indecent  for
a  man  like  me.  Happy.  I  got  up  slowly,
pulled  the  sheet  over  her  shoulder  so  the  AC  wouldn't  hit  her
skin  directly,  and  went  down
barefoot.  The  cold  marble  of  the  staircase  under  my  feet
was  the  same  as  always,  but  even  that  seemed
different on the mornings she was upstairs. The mansions kitchen at that hour was mine alone.
Donna Kiarra was still in the back garden cutting rosemary. I could hear from far off the sound of
her scissors against the thick stems. The dogs slept piled up near the service door. My father's
old clock kept the slow rhythm of 620. I grabbed the coffee tin, measured it into the mocha pot the
way I landed her taught me without realizing she was teaching. Two sugar cubes, a drop of milk,
never too. Bastion came in through the service door with his planner under his arm, and stopped
talking before he even started. He looked at me, looked at the cup in my hand, looked back at me.
Good morning, he said dry. Good morning. He set the planner on the counter, with the ceremony of a
hand delivering an official document, a second of silence. Two ticks of the clock. Should I build
the household for the dawn becoming a barista? I didn't answer. The corner of my mouth betrayed
half an intention of a smile, and I corrected it before he noticed. He noticed. Pretended not to.
That's how he'd worked for 10 years. What's on the schedule? Fausto asked for half an hour this afternoon.
The elders sent word about the doc, and Donna Atavia. He paused, chose the word,
requested a family meeting at noon. Formal sitting room. I looked at him. Did she request a meeting
or announce one? Announced. I filed the information in the place where I store the things I haven't
yet decided what to do with. My mother had come back from Naples two weeks earlier than planned
without warning and without explanation, and I'd expected her to arrive with her temper sharpened,
with a list of grievances, with that silence of hers that cuts deeper than any shout.
I hadn't expected her to request the formal room. The formal room was for weddings, funerals,
and contract executions. My mother knew very well what each setting said before a single word was
spoken. Teller will be there. I'll ander and I. Bastion nodded. Brief. Anything else? I raised the cup.
Take this up before it gets cold. Set it beside the bed. Don't say anything. She hates being
and she's not talking to her. She's not talking to her. She's not talking to her. She's not talking to
her. She's not talking to her. She's not talking to her. She's not talking to her. She's not talking
to her. She's not talking to her. She's not talking to her. She's not talking to her. She's not talking
to her. She's not talking to her. She's not talking to her. She's not talking to her. She's not talking to her.
Her hood-papers photographer had caught her face at the exact moment the bell told for the last time
and none of the guests knew how to look at her properly. I did. I saw in the photo the exact
moment her face understood that a delmo wasn't coming and I saw that she decided right there
that she wouldn't cry in front of those people. That day I decided two things and I'm still
keeping both. To get her out of the trap the Sarah Vowls had set for her and to never tell her
I'd seen her cry in a white dress. I heard light footsteps on the stairs. The fourth step always
creaked and the sound reached me with the punctuality of an agreed upon signal. I came back to
the present. I left the kitchen, crossed the high ceiling to corridor, and passed through the hall
to the garden. She'd be by the chamelears. She was always by the chamelears before eight, said it
was the hour when the flowers breathed. She was, in a long night gown, hair pinned at the nape,
watering can in her hands. The morning still had that damp July light that makes everything seem
slightly unreal, and she moved among the plants with the ease of someone born there.
Though I knew that three months ago she barely knew the chamelears name. I came up behind her
without a sound, and kissed her neck right where I'd learned she shivers slightly. She shivered.
You shouldn't do that when I'm holding water. If you soak the chamelears and me along with them,
I won't be offended. She laughed softly, and turned her face until she tucked her chin against my
shoulder. Her hair smelled of rosemary, probably because of Donna Kiyara, who insisted on leaving
dried sprigs in every room of the house as if that were protection enough against anything.
Your mother is up to something. My mother is always up to something.
No. Today, she's up to something. I looked at her profile against the morning light.
She'd learned to read the house the way one reads the Bible,
word by word skipping nothing. If she said my mother was up to something,
my mother was up to something. Formal sitting room noon, I said, we go together.
Together, it was just one word, and it landed there like a signature at the bottom.
I took the watering can from her hand, set it on the ground and pulled her to me by the waste.
Beneath the cotton of the night gown, there was a small secret only the two of us knew,
and I could count on my fingers the people outside that house who also knew.
Iolanda. Me. The doctor. Donna Kiyara suspected, but Donna Kiyara suspects everything and is
rarely wrong. Do we tell them today she asked against my chest? My mother, your mother, I thought
a second. After the meeting, we'll read the room. She agreed without speaking. I felt her hair
against my mouth and decided that this was the last morning I'd put anything off. After lunch,
I'd tell Fausto to pull the old contract out of the drawer and destroy it with me in front
of me at my signature. There was a clause in it that I'd written with my own hand in another life,
and I'd carried the postponement of that clause, the way a man carries a small stone in his shoe,
not annoying enough to make him stop, but always hurting. Today I was taking out the stone.
Come, I said, eat something before you face the matriarch. She laughed again. She laughed more since
she'd been mine. I'd learned to listen to her laugh the way one learns a language he never cared
to learn, and ended up in love with its sound. We went inside, and the garden door closed behind
us with the soft sound of old woods settling into its frame. Four hours until noon, a whole lifetime
until noon. The formal sitting room was the only room in the mansion where I'd never felt whole.
Ceiling too high, mahogany shelves with books no one read. Two sofas of dried blood-colored velvet,
and a rug so pale it felt cruel to step on. The air in there had that specific smell of a
shut-up room you only open on occasion. Mothballs mixed with old varnish, and something floral
trying to mask the other two. Butavia liked that room because the room made an impression. That's why
she chose it. She sat with her back to the window, and the noon light came in behind her,
and turned her into a dark silhouette against the gold, a staging choice, the choice of someone who
knows how to stage. Bousto stood behind her, leaning against the shelves. His head lowered in a way
I'd never seen in the conceliary. Don Vittorio, Don Emilliano, and Don Sisto stood. The three of
them with that old bearing of men who'd learned to stand for hours at wakes for friends they
themselves had ordered killed. I came in hand in hand with Ludovico. I felt his finger squeeze
mine for half a second, almost involuntary, and let go. You read the room before I did. Mother,
son, Otevia moved her head a centimeter in my direction. Ealanda, I sat on the sofa across from them,
him at my side. I crossed my hands over my knee. There was a dark leather folder on the little table
between us, and the folder was closed, and the folder had the crest of the lion with the broken
crown blind embossed on the cover. My stomach sank half an inch. I recognized that crest.
It was the same as the letter that had arrived months ago. On a night when I still didn't
understand much of what I was living. The one Ludovico had put in the drawer without explanation.
Otevia opened the folder with the slowness of someone who knows no one will interrupt. She took
out a sheet. Just one. Before my son marries you twice, she said, without looking at me yet.
I thought it better you know the whole contract. She pushed the sheet with two fingers to my edge
of the table. I didn't move. Ludovico moved half a second to late. I felt his hand hesitate on my knee
and settle there. I looked at the sheet. It was paper yellowed at the edges. Family letterhead.
My signature at the bottom. That shaky signature I'd learned to make at the registry office
months ago with my head spinning from hunger and humiliation. And above my signature,
in the third clause at the bottom, there was a paragraph written by hand, by hand, not typed,
by hand. In the writing I knew from notes in the corners of library books,
from messages left at my bedroom door in the first month, from the dedication he'd written in a
pavice novel, and pretended hadn't been him. I read it once. On the day the air is born,
the marriage is dissolved. The wife leaves with a fortune corresponding to half the dawn's
net worth, alone. Without the child, full custody remains with the Karachiolo family. I read it again.
The words didn't change. I raised my eyes to his profile. He was looking at the sheet. Not at me.
At the sheet. And his mouth opened. And his mouth closed. He didn't say no. The tavia smiled
without smiling. Keep your word son. It's written in your own hand. I heard my own name sound
inside my head as if called from far away. Iolanda. Iolanda, listen. That writing is his. That
paragraph was him. That paragraph had been there the whole time. Beneath everything. While I
learned his coffee, while he pulled the sheet over my shoulder, while we stood in the garden with
our hands inside each other as if that were real. He finally turned to me. His eyes were the exact
color of the morning we walked into the Camelia garden. And in that color, there was now a terror
I'd never seen on his face, not in the small hours of the library, not on the night of the attack
in the street. Iolanda. No. I stood. My legs answered. It was the mornings only luck. I smoothed my
shirt with both hands as if that mattered. And I looked at the three elders, one by one, and then
atotavia.  And  lastly,  very  lightly,  at  Ludovico.  You  two  fit  together.  I  said,
the  both  of  you.
My voice didn't shake. To this day I don't know how. I walked out of the room, though everything
in me wanted to run. My heels struck the marble of the hall as if they belonged to another woman,
and the other woman climbed the stairs far too slowly. One step, two, three. And on the
13th I had to put my hand on the railing to keep from fainting. The wood was cold under my palm.
I focused on that. Only on that. In the bedroom corridor, I didn't go to the sweet I'd been
sharing with him for three months. I went to the door at the end. The door I hadn't open
since we decided to sleep together. The white paint around the knob was slightly faded. I'd
noticed that detail on the first day, and completely forgotten it afterward. The old contract room.
I turned the knob. The air inside was still warm, with the smell of old wood, and the dust that
gathers in places no one enters anymore. The bed made is on the day I'd left. The lamp on the
night stand with its bulb off. The straw chair and the corner where I'd sat on the night of the
first that would ever happen. To me, I closed the door behind me, and the click of the latch sounded
loud through the whole house. I sat on the edge of the bed. The mattress was cold. I laid my hand
flat over the belly no one yet knew existed, and for the first time in three months I said
quietly to no one, and to him were going to be okay. It was the first lie I told my child. The
afternoon fell over the old contract room without me moving from the edge of the bed. I watched
the sunlight cross the floor in a long rectangle. Shrink, stretch, shrink, vanish, the room turned
blue, then gray, then black. I didn't turn on the light. There was a sound I'd learned to ignore
over the past months. The sound of the house itself breathing, pipes, wood, expanding. Donna
Kiarra's distant footsteps in the pantry. I listened to all of it with a new attention, like
someone arriving at a place for the first time. The smell of cold wax on the floor. The creek
of a window at the end of the corridor. The whole house sounding like a living organism that
didn't know I was falling apart inside it. Maybe it was the first time. I started doing something
I didn't want to do and did anyway. I started rereading the last few months backward, each gesture
of his, and fitting them into the shape of that handwritten paragraph. The coffee, two cubes,
a  drop  of  milk.  He'd  noted  it  on  the  first  day.  At  Bastion  noted,  kept  the  order  alive  in
the
I thought it was the small tenderness of a man who doesn't know how to say the big things,
and what if it was just care of an investment? A man tens his cattle with the same constancy,
but the same cold, calculated attention, no affection, only foresight. The coat over my shoulders
on the rainy night. I'd kept that coat at the back of the closet in the first week. The way one keeps
a relic. The dark, heavy fabric, with his scent mixed with the wet cold of the street, and what if
had been the calculation of a man who knows an elegant gesture buys cheap loyalty? The small
hours of the library. Him broken in the armchair, the untouched glass, the talk about his dead brother,
and what if every sentence of that had been rehearsed to soften a woman who still thought she was
merchandise? And the handwritten paragraph proved she was. I listened to that voice until I almost believed
it. Then, I listened to another, the newer voice, the one three months old, the one saying I
wasn't an idiot. I'm not an idiot. I'd seen his face in that room, and I saw terror. Not a game.
I saw a man who didn't know what to do with his own hands while his mother slid the paper across the
table. I stayed between the two voices until my mouth was too dry to talk to myself. He knocked
on the door for the first time near nine at night. Three short knocks his way, without pleading,
I'llanda. I didn't answer. I'm not coming in. I just want to know if you've eaten. I didn't answer.
He stayed there. I heard his breathing on the other side of the wood, held back, controlled,
the way he controlled everything, except the things that truly mattered. I heard him let out the air
like a man giving up on a sentence before saying it. I heard the footsteps drawing away far too slowly,
as if he wanted to give me time to change my mind. I slept dressed on top of the comforter.
I dreamed of the church in Providence. In the dream, the bell wouldn't stop tolling. I woke with
sun on my face and my body heavy. I got up, went to the adjoining bathroom,
washed my face with cold water until my cheeks stung. In the mirror I looked at the woman with
swollen eyes and didn't recognize her at first glance. Second glance I did. It was still me,
just more tired. He knocked twice on Friday. In the morning, in the voice of a man who decided not to
impose. In the afternoon, in a horse or voice, as if the hours had scraped something loose inside.
Both times he said the same thing. I'm here. Both times I didn't open.
Donna Kira came up with a train near noon. She didn't knock. She left the tray on the floor,
against the door, with a note under the plate. I waited for her footsteps to fade,
and opened the door the smallest crack. I pulled the tray inside.
Soup, bread, a pair. The note had three words in her round motherly hand.
Eat for the little one. She knew. Of course she knew. Donna Kira knew everything in that house.
I ate the whole bowl of soup without tasting it. I ate the bread. I ate the pair down to the core.
It was the first thing I did for the little one. And the second thing I did for myself.
Nareena called near five. I answered because it was her. Are you alive? I am. Are you eating?
Now I am. You want me to come over? I thought a second. The idea of having someone in the room felt
too big to bear. Like a strong light in an eye used to the dark. Not today. Tomorrow. Tomorrow I'll say.
She was silent long enough for me to know. She was thinking about not hanging up. And then she said
her thing. If you need wine and a butter knife, you know where I live. I laughed. It was half
laugh, half sob, but it was. It was the first time in 24 hours that my face made a movement.
It wasn't pain. I know. I answered. I hung up. Play down again. And this time I managed to cry
without being angry at myself for crying. I spent all of Friday outside that door. Not the whole time.
There was a chair in the corridor, a moss-colored velvet armchair no one had used in years.
And I sat in it when my legs got tired of standing. I came back to knock when I thought she might
hear. I never left the floor. Bastion came up twice with office questions and went down with short
answers. Fausto asked to speak with me over the intercom. I sent word that not today.
I leaned my forehead against the door's wood near the end of the afternoon and spoke low
without calling her name. The wood was cold. I let it stay that way. I wrote that before you
existed in my life. I stopped. Before I knew you'd exist in my life. I stopped again. That
doesn't fix anything I know. On the other side her silence had weight. I could tell her silence
is a part. There was her thoughtful silence. Her wounded silence. Her sleeping silence. That was a new
silence. A silence that was weighing on me in return. I didn't ask to come in. I didn't have the right.
The clause I'd written with my own hand. In the week I decided to buy her from the Sarah Vals
was the only piece of my history with her that she didn't know. And that's why it was the only
piece in which she could still believe I'd plan to lose her from the start. If I forced that door
now I wouldn't be opening a door. I'd be confirming the paragraph. I went back to the study at
eight. I called Bastion. You know this house. I do. Find every copy of that contract. My mother's
Faustos, the one I keep in the safe, the one the registry sent to the secretariat and never came
back. All of them. Bring them to me. He stood still half a second. Enough to register that I wasn't
asking. And left without a single question. I opened the drawer of my father's study and took
out something that had sat there for three months. The handwritten draft of the clause.
Yellowed paper, black ink, my writing. I set it on the desk and looked at it the way one looks at
a dead animal he hadn't the courage to bury when he should have. There was a promise I'd
made to my own conscience three months ago. On the morning I Orlando had agreed to sleep at my
side without a contract. I promised myself I'd erase that clause one day. I'd put it off.
I'd thought I'd have time. I'd put it off like a man putting off a doctor with chest pain.
And now the pain had come for her not for me and that was what truly hurt in the whole story.
I put the draft under the blotter. It wouldn't burn alone. It would burn in front of the person who
needed to see it. I went up again. I leaned my forehead against the door one last time that night.
Good night, I Orlando. On the other side, a second. Two. And a whisper so low I could have invented it.
Good night. I didn't invent it. She said it. Saturday was born gray.
With a pale light striking sideways at the shutters and streaking the floor with opaque bands.
I got up before the heat pressed in. Took a long bath, chose a light dress. Pinned my
hair up with the two hands that no longer trembled so much. I opened the door of the old contract room
and stepped out for the first time in almost 40 hours. I didn't go looking for him. I knew that
at nine he'd be with Fausto in the downstairs office. I went down the opposite side of the staircase
and headed to the winter garden where Donna Kiarra's bromeliads caught the light through the glass
and everything seemed quieter than the rest of the house. Donna Kiarra appeared with a tray before I
asked. Camo-Mail-T, a small piece of bread with butter, an orange peeled into segments. She said the
tray on the wicker table. Still to second. Dried her hands on her apron. She didn't look at me straight on.
He loves you dear. She said, looking at the bromeliads, men like him are stupid about the things they love.
I didn't answer. She didn't wait for an answer either. She went back inside. I drank the tea slowly,
feeling the warmth of the cup in my palms. I ate the whole piece of bread. I ate the orange. And as I
ate, I understood something that had taken 40 hours to reach me. If he wouldn't tell it, I'd go after it.
I'd done this before. Once ago I'd gone to find the truth about a Delmo with my own hands and the truth
gave me back everything. Maybe the truth about that handwritten paragraph was also stored somewhere in
the city, in an archive, in someone's head, in his writing on some other paper. Bous도,
probably new. The cafe Veccia Roma, where everything had begun, held the beginning. And if there was a
beginning, I still hadn't fully understood. It was mine. I took the phone from my pocket and
switched to a message to Bastion. Car to Mara morning. Early, just the two of us. He answered in less than a minute.
Yes, he didn't ask where to. He didn't warn the boss. Bastion was Bastion. I spent the rest of the
morning in the winter garden. Ludovico didn't come looking for me. I knew he knew I was there. On the
other side of the glass. I knew he was waiting for a signal for me. And I knew he wouldn't force one.
There was something new in that silence that I'd learned to read in the coming days,
and that something was respect. He was letting me choose the distance. At the end of the afternoon I
went up again. I passed the door of his study. The door was a jar. A threat of yellow light leaking through the gap.
He was sitting at the desk. No tie. His shirt rolled to the elbows. A pile of folders on the right
and a pile of folders on the left. As if the work had come back to fill every hour I was away. He was
reading a sheet with an attention that hurt to look at. He raised his eyes and saw me. He didn't move.
Didn't smile. Just looked. The way he looked when he was holding something too big to fit into a sentence.
Good night. I said, good night. That was all. I continued down the corridor. I went to the
suite  that  was  hours  and  didn't  go  in.  I  went  to  the  old  contract  room.  I  laid  dressed  on
the
if there was anyone who'd learned to hunt her own truth in the past months. It was me. Tomorrow I'd begin.
Sunday began cold. The way Providence knows how to be cold even in summer. The light came through the window of the old contract room in a hard way
without generosity. I'd slept little. My hand stayed open over my belly. The way it had already become habit these past two days.
And I wondered in the second before waking fully. Whether my child already knew that his mother had made a plan with no
one for a hunt. I got up slowly. Put on dark pants, a turtleneck, black shoes, nothing that suggested Donna.
Nothing that suggested bride. Just a woman within a dress in her head. And a question that would no longer fit
inside her. Bastion waited in the car. Outside. He didn't ask a question. He just opened the rear door and
kept looking straight ahead while I got in. The radio was low. An old Italian song I knew without remembering
from where. Cafe Vecchi Aroma. I said, buckling the belt. Then the runnyeri office. Then an address I'll give you later.
He nodded half a millimeter with his head. Started the car. The drive to the old neighborhood took long
enough for me to count my breaths. We passed the intersection where, months before, a collector had
shown up at my apartment door with a manila envelope and a face that didn't ask permission. I was
another person that day. Or maybe I was the same. Just not knowing yet. The dawn called three times.
Bastion said, watching the rear view mirror. His voice was always the same. Dry is dry stone.
Asked where you'd gone. And you said, that I didn't rightly know. I smiled for a second.
It didn't last. The cafe Vecchi Aroma sat on a corner that time had forgotten to renovate.
Green onning. Peeling sign. The smell of good coffee escaping through the door. I went in slow
half a dozen tables taken. Old men playing cards in the back. A white-haired woman reading a newspaper.
I sat at the window table. The table. The one where he'd sat on the late afternoon of a
Thursday that now seemed to belong to another life. This chair was empty across for me. And even
empty it seemed occupied. The waiter came slowly. He was a thin man, clean apron. With that look of
one who'd worked in an old cafe since he was 15 and would never stop. Coffee please. I said,
he paused half a second. Looked at me the way one checks a password. Two cubes, a drop of milk.
The question landed between us. Quiet. I held my breath until it heard in my chest. How do you know?
My voice came out lower than I wanted. The waiter shrugged with the kind of ease you only learned
with time. Old order. Mr. Karachiolo asked a few months back that if you ever came in,
this was how you were to be served. Never came up. Today it did. He left before I could answer.
I stayed staring at the wood of the table, breathing through my mouth. Lodavico had left a standing
order at some ordinary cafe months ago, without telling me, without asking for anything in return,
without collecting. Like a man leaving a piece of home on every corner of the city in case I
needed to come back. I really wanted to be angry. Anger was easier to carry. The coffee came.
I drank it slowly. It was exactly the way I liked it. And the taste came along with a new scar.
I paid. Left. Fausto Ranieri's office was on the second floor of a dark brick building.
Three blocks ahead. Bastion parked. Stayed in the car. I went up the stairs alone. The wooden door
had his name and discreet gold letters. The kind of discretion that costs a lot. The secretary tried
to stop me. I walked straight past. With the politeness of someone who no longer asks permission.
Fausto was behind the desk. Glasses at the tip of his nose. A paper open in front of him.
He raised his head slowly when he saw me. He didn't seem surprised. He seemed tired.
He said, Marcee Cano. I corrected. Sitting in the chair on the other side of the desk.
For now, he closed the paper slowly. crossed his hands. How can I help you? When he wrote that
clause. Fausto breathed through his nose. Took off his glasses. Put them in his jacket pocket.
Sinyora, I am the family's conciliate. My job is to advise. Not to betray. I'm not asking you to
betray. I said, without raising my voice. I'm asking you to tell me when. That's all. The date.
He was silent for a while. Then he opened the drawer beneath the desk. Took out two bundles of paper
tied within twine. Set the first in front of me and untied it. Original draft. He said,
dated by hand. You know the handwriting. I did. His writing was one of those you recognize from far off.
firm, a little old fashioned. But the careful capitals of a man educated by priests. The date
in the upper right corner was a week before the day he'd called me to the cafe for the first time.
A week before I existed in his life in full. He drafted it alone. Fausto continued.
Looking at the sheet and not at me. Locked in his father's study. Didn't let me read it before
I witnessed the signature. Just called me to certify the mark. I asked if he was sure. He didn't answer.
Why? Fausto raised his eyes. He had the kind of gaze a conciliary learns. It doesn't judge.
But it doesn't spare either. He didn't write this to bind you. He wrote it to be sure he could let
you go. I gripped the edge of the desk. The wood was cold. Good to hold. That doesn't excuse it.
I said, low. It doesn't excuse it. Fausto tied the twine again. Put it away. It only explains it.
I stayed another minute. I had no more questions. I stood. He stood too in the polite way of old men.
Senyora. He said, when I was already at the door. For whatever it's worth. He asked me three weeks ago
to tear up that draft. I said, I'd tear it. I didn't. I never tear anything of the families without a
written order. He knew I wouldn't tear it. And he went away satisfied all the same. I stopped with my hand on the
knob. I didn't turn around. I just nodded and left. Narina's apartment was in federal hill.
Three streets below my old one. Bastion parked at the curb. Leant his head against the seat.
Close his eyes. I went up alone. Rang the bell. She opened wearing pajamas that must have been 10
years  old.  Hair  pinned  up  with  a  pencil.  Glasses  crooked.  Oh  my  God.  She  said,  she
pulled  me  inside  by  the  elbow.
You look like you saw Christ come down off the cross. Christ feels like too little. She closed the door
with her foot. Took me to the couch. Shove to pile of sheet music to the floor. Sat beside me.
The apartment smelled of bad coffee and old books. And I without meaning to started to cry.
It wasn't a pretty cry. It was the cry of someone who'd held it in for two days. Narina didn't say
anything for a while. She just ran her hand over my back. The way her grandmother must have run her hand
over hers as a child. Then she got up, went to the kitchen, came back with a mug of bad coffee in a piece of
orange  cake.  Eat.  She  said,  then  talk.  I  ate.  I  talked.  I  told
her  about  the  folder,  the  claws,
his handwriting, the locked room, the cafe with the waiter and the two cubes. The draft in
Faustos drawer. I told all of it in the messy way you tell your best friend, out of order,
with repetition, with a pause to breathe. I told her about the belly. Narina stopped chewing.
The piece of cake fell into her lap. She looked at me as if seeing me for the first time in three days.
I, Alanda, I know. She cried. Then laughed. Then cried again. Hugged me tight enough to hurt my
shoulder. You're not fighting just for yourself, girl. She said, still on my shoulder. This changes the
game.  I  breathed  deep  inside  her  hug.  It  really  does  change  it.  She  let  me  go.  Wipe  her  face  on
the
door. That man wrote the claws because he was scared. Fine. Said and done. Now either he destroys
the claws in front of his mother-in-law, or I show up there in person and he can deal with it. Choose.
I laughed. It was a small laugh, but it was a laugh. We'll see. I said, she stood, pulled me by the wrist.
Before anything you're going to the doctor. Nar, to the doctor, Alanda. Not tomorrow. Today,
you look like you haven't slept in three days and there's a little one in there who needs a
third who's whole. There was no arguing. Narina put shoes on me, put a person my hand, pushed me out
of the apartment. Bastion lifted his head from the seat when he saw me. Looked at Narina in the doorway.
She came down the stairs behind me and had a mug of coffee to bastion through the car window.
Take it. It's awful, but it's hot. Bastion accepted it with that minimal knot of the head.
Narina waited for me to get in the car. Patted the hood twice like someone saying goodbye to a horse.
Went back up. Bastion looked at the mug for half a second before taking the first sip.
Miss Narina, he said, low, more to himself than to me.
Has a heavy hand. With the coffee or with life, both. He started the car. The family's discreet clinic
was in a building with no sign. Three floors above a jewelry shop on a quiet street. I went up in the
elevator with Bastion behind me. A silent shadow. The doctor was a woman of around 50.
Short gray hair. A firm hand. She'd already treated two generations of Karachi Olos. She examined
me carefully. Ask questions without going around anything. Marked something in a chart I didn't see.
Then she sat in the chair across from me and crossed her hands. The way Fausto had crossed his
hours earlier. It must be a habit of those who live around this family. Everything's fine with the
child, she said. But your blood pressure is high. Higher than I'd like at this stage. You need rest,
you need to sleep. And above all you need to avoid any big shocks in the coming months. A big
shock drops the pressure. Dropped pressure drops the child. I laughed awkwardly. It was the kind of
laugh that isn't a laugh. The one that comes out of your chest because there's nowhere else for it to
come  out.  Doctor,  I  said,  I've  had  three  big  shocks  in  the  last  72  hours.  She  didn't
smile.  She  just
wrote a sheet with emergency numbers. Bastion paid downstairs with an envelope that appeared from
his coat pocket as if it had always been there. We went back to the car. After noon had already fallen.
Home, I said. Bastion nodded. The drive back was long the way roads get long when your head is full.
I looked at the street without seeing it. I went over everything. The date in the corner of the
draft. Bausto's sentence. Narina's gesture holding the piece of cake in her lap. The doctor
gripping the pen. And in the middle of it all, something new. I wasn't just wounded anymore.
I was planning. We reached the mansion when it was already night. Bastion stopped the car in the
courtyard. Got out. Open the door for me. I climbed the three entrance steps slowly. The front door
opened before I touched it. Ludovico was at the foot of the stairs. Exactly where he'd waited.
Months ago, when I'd tried to leave alone for the first time and Renolfo had shown up in the
street behind the market. The same place. The same height. His hands at his sides. His shoulders straight.
His mouth closed in a line that couldn't hide that he'd waited there for hours. I stopped in
the middle of the hall. The marble floor gave back the echo of my heels. Where did you go? He said.
It wasn't a question. It was just his voice trying to reach the edge of something. I recognized the
place. I recognized the foot of the stairs and the waiting. And I let the recognition pass across my
face without hiding it. After you, I said, except you weren't there. He closed his eyes half a second.
Open them. I'llanda. Tomorrow will talk. I passed him without touching.
Climb the stairs slowly. One hand on my belly under the coat. The other on the railing.
He didn't follow. He stayed where he was. The way men stay when they've learned too late that
grabbing doesn't hold. I lay down in the old contract room. The bed was still cold. But I slept.
Not much. But I slept. It was the small hours that woke me. A muffled sound. Downstairs.
The kind the mansion shouldn't make at that hour. I sat up on the bed with my eyes closed for a second.
Tuning my ear. Light footsteps in the downstairs corridor. A door opening slowly. And a voice.
A  table.  On  the  phone.  Speaking  Italian  too  fast.  The  way  someone  does  when  they  don't  want  to
be
mansions high ceilings carried sound upward as if designed for it. And I caught three words in the
current of hers. Enough. Air. Sarah Vall. I stayed there. Pressed against the wood. Without breathing.
My hand went back to my belly without me telling it too. And I understood. Without needing another
word that the witch wasn't scheming alone. She'd arranged the next step with the enemy Luda Vico thought
was contained. I went back to bed slowly. I didn't lie down. I sat leaning against the headboard.
Eyes open in the dark. Waiting for dawn. Tomorrow. Luda Vico was going to hear me out tomorrow.
I knew she'd come down. I'd been in the library since before dawn. The way I always had been when
the house demanded something I didn't yet know how to give. A low fire in the half. The coal
eating itself slowly from within. With that dry crackle that filled the silence without truly filling it.
An untouched glass beside the arm of the chair. The glass of a man who pours out of habit and
doesn't drink. The morning light still had that grey tone of the small hours that hasn't decided
between dark and day. And I waited without waiting. My eyes fixed on the embers. As if they might
tell me something I still didn't have the courage to tell myself. I heard her step on the stairs
before I saw her. I recognized it by the weight. The heels she wore inside the house.
Lita then the ones for the street. A second slower than usual. Because her body now carried a secret
that tired her more than she admitted. She came in through the library's arch door and stopped
half a second at the frame her hand still on the wooden frame. She was in a loose blouse,
hair pinned up. No makeup. I'd never seen her like this in the morning. Even with anger written
into every muscle of her face, she was the most alive thing in that room full of dead books.
She looked at the empty armchair beside me. Mine. She sat in it anyway, with that deliberate
calm of someone who knows exactly what she's doing and wants you to see. She crossed her legs
slowly. She held my gaze without blinking. Explain it to me now, she said. Without cutting anything
out. I breathed deep. The air was warm near the hearth and cold on the opposite side. And I felt
both at the same time. If there's one thing I've learned about speaking, I've learned that the
truth only fits in your mouth when you accept losing something by saying it. I'd accepted it
in Friday morning. When I leaned my forehead against the door of the room where she was locked
and admitted to the wood that the claws was mine and the price of it was too. The first time I
wanted to tell you this story, I began, was in the kitchen. He lifted her chin half a millimeter,
she knew which kitchen. You'd been in the house a week, I continued. I'd agreed with myself
that I wouldn't speak to you in the corridors. Formal greeting cold-look public dinner contract,
that was the arrangement. You cried in the small hours alone at the counter and the light you'd
left on made me come down. I was going to leave without going in. You heard me, turned around,
and fired off a sentence I still hear when I have nothing to do. She stayed quiet. Her hands
rested in her lap, with a stillness I recognized as effort. I don't need an audience to cry, thank
you. I repeated it without trying to imitate her. No one had ever spoken to me like that. Not a
woman, not my father. In that moment I understood two things I didn't want to understand.
The first, that you wouldn't fit into the contract I'd written, the second that I was going to fall,
and I fell right there. That night, with the glass of milk, still in your hand. She pressed the
back of the armchair with her fingertips. She didn't interrupt me. The second time was in the rain,
I continued. Coming back from Miljira Soli, you got into the car beside me, wet from the shoulder
up, your hair stuck to your neck. I took off my coat before I thought and covered you.
I was without a coat the rest of the way the cold coming in through the window. What I didn't tell
you is that I got home not trusting my own voice. I didn't open my mouth until the sweet door.
If I'd spoken, I'd have said something that couldn't yet be said, and the claws.
Her voice came quiet. But with a firmness underneath that left no room for a vision.
When? There I closed my eyes a second. The cold popped softly in the hearth. I opened them.
In the week I discovered the set of all his plans, I said. Before I called you to the cafe,
I was alone in my father's study. I'd already decided to buy the debt.
I'd already decided to get a delmo out of the city. I'd already decided on the contract,
and I drafted it all by hand at that mahogany writing desk with the window facing the winter garden.
Each line in silence, the only sound, the scratch of the pen on paper. She didn't look away.
The final claws I wrote last, I continued. After everything,
Fausto wasn't there. No one was. I wrote it because if one day you found out who I really was and
were left with no choice, I wanted you to be able to leave. Without having to ask,
without having to knock on my door asking permission to go. With money to start over in whatever
city you wanted, without my name on your passport if you preferred it that way. Silence. A log
tapped lightly against the iron grate of the hearth. By a lambda, I said, and my voice was no longer
firm. I didn't know how to love without leaving a door open. Writing that claws was the only
form of love I'd learned, building the exit for someone I didn't think would stay. She breathed
deep. Her chest rose and fell in a way I noticed, and I hated myself for noticing so clearly.
And afterward, she said, it wasn't a question. It was an order. Afterward I loved you.
I said simply, and I put it off. I thought I'd have time. I asked Fausto to tear up the draft
three weeks ago. He said he'd tear it. I knew he wouldn't tear it because a conciliary doesn't
tear paper without a written order. I came away without demanding the written order.
Because inside, I still didn't know if I deserved to destroy the door. She said nothing more
for a while. The silence between us had its own weight and temperature. Then she stood. She walked
to the hearth with measured steps, as if she needed something concrete to look at. She stood
with her back to me, facing the coal. Her shoulders were slightly slumped. The way someone carries
an invisible baby, and too heavy a truth on the same day. The reddish light of the embers struck
her profile and stayed there. Quiet. Long enough for me to realize she was using that silence
to organize something within herself. You put it off, she said, without turning.
That's different from lying. It is. I said, low. But it costs the same. She turned.
Her eyes were red, but they didn't fall. I don't forgive you today, she said. But I understand
for today it's what I can manage. I stood from the armchair slowly. I didn't approach.
I learned late, but I learned. Thank you, I said. She nodded half a millimeter with her head. She
asked me without touching. Stopped at the doorframe her hand in the same place where she'd stopped
coming in, as if the frame were a border she controlled alone. There's another thing, she said.
But I'll tell you later, not today. She left. I stayed looking at the fire, the glass remained untouched.
I left the library without running. If I ran, he'd come after me. And I still hadn't decided
what to do with what was inside me in that minute. The anger that still burned and that other
thing deeper than anger. The one that hurt in a different way because it had no easy name.
I walked down the corridor to his father's old study. The wood of the floor was cold under my inner
heels. The smell of Carnobo wax and old paper marking each step. Ludovico had shown me the key once,
months before. In the casual way of amans saying, this door is yours too. I'd never gone in alone.
I went in now. The study was darker than Ludovico's. Have your wood? The thick wool rug with a
gondy diamond pattern that muffled any sound. The smell of old cigar that never fully left the
walls no matter how they opened the window. The writing desk sat in the middle, basing the closed window.
I went straight to the top drawer without hesitating, like someone who knows what she came to get.
It wasn't locked. He trusted the people living with him too much. Inside, among folders and sealed
envelopes I didn't even dare touch. An old leather notebook with a crumpled corner. I opened it.
Loose sheets of drafts, some with incorrections, and others with edges yellowed by time.
I found it without needing to search much. The handwriting was unmistakable. The same one I'd
already learned to recognize in every note and dedication in the house. Date, in the upper right corner,
a week before the day of the cafe. It was all there. All by hand, with each clause numbered and the
last one written on the back of the sheet, separated from the others by a simple horizontal line.
I folded the sheet in four with the care of someone who knows old paper tears. I put it in the
pocket of my dress. At my hip, I closed the drawer slowly, with two fingers, without a sound. I left.
In the upstairs corridor I stopped. Otevius voiced rose through the stairwell, with the clarity that
only the mansion knew how to give. The ceiling was extremely high in that stretch, and the
salon of the formal sitting room sat right below my feet. The same room where she'd opened the
older three days before, with that smile of someone who'd kept the card up her sleeve her whole life.
The salon door was a jar, and the sound rose through the gap, as if someone had planted an acoustic
pipe between the floors. She wasn't speaking low. She never spoke low when she thought only
elders were listening. I leaned my hand on the railing. The iron cold against my palm. I didn't
crouch. I just stood. My son has stopped listening to the family. She was saying, fast Italian mixed with
the syllables cutting the air with the precision of someone who'd practiced that speech before.
He let the woman nurse his decision. And the three of you stay quiet as if the Donna hadn't been chosen
in this room for three generations. A male voice answered low. Don Vittorio by the grave,
deliberate timbre. I didn't catch the words. Don't come to me with a Tevius. She cut in.
You signed the original contract with me. The clause exists. It's legitimate, and I'm going to
force  it.  Another  answer.  Also  low.  Also  his.  It  only  takes  one  night.  Metavius
said,  and  their  her  voice
changed tone. Ruth thinner. Sharper. That quality of a knife passing over a wet stone. One night.
If the air doesn't arrive, the clause stops mattering. My son becomes mine again. And the stranger
goes back to the street she came from. The railing went ice cold under my fingers. The cerevaals,
she continued. Already know about the pregnancy. I sent word yesterday. Renoufou accepted the job
for the price I offered. It won't be at the mansion. It'll be on the way out. When she thinks she's safe,
and the three of you will pretend you didn't know. And afterward you'll pretend you're sorry.
And my son will pretend for a month that he's lost something important. Then he'll go back to
being what he was. Silence. The kind of silence three old men make when none want to be the first to
take. Then one of the elder spoke. And this time I caught the whole sentence. It was Don Sisto.
The youngest of the three old men. The one with the lowest voice. This is an attempt against
Karachiolo blood-o-tavia. This is an attempt against a bot-bride. She spat back without pausing.
Karachiolo blood is decided in this room. I didn't wait for the rest. I went down the stairs far too
slowly. Gripping the railing with both hands. Feeling the ice cold iron under my fingers as if
it were the only solid thing in that moment. With the hand written draft warm in my pocket
and my free hand firm on my belly. I crossed the service corridor. Pass the winter garden without
looking at the plants. All the way to the back of Miranda. The one where I'd cried alone weeks before.
On the day, Ludovico had told me the first half of the truth. And I still didn't know there was a
second half. I leaned my hip against the stone ballastrade. I breathed three times.
Deep, slow, counting the seconds of each breath. The doctor had said on Monday's late afternoon
that a big shock dropped the pressure and dropped pressure dropped the child. I wouldn't give the
witch that satisfaction. I wouldn't run. I wouldn't scream. I would tell Ludovico. Before Octavia
made her next move. Before Renolfo went out into the street with the agreed price in his pocket.
The clause had become a small piece of her game. The big piece was me, alive, walking out the door.
I couldn't let her move first. I ran my hand over my face. It was steady. Good. I turned to go back
into the house and I saw. At the back wall where the garden met the narrow street that wrapped around the
mansion leaning against a stone as if he'd been waiting since the beginning of the world. A man,
light gray suit. One hand in his pocket. The other arm loose and unhurried. A shark smile
I'd seen once before. Months ago. In the street behind the old market. When he'd gotten too close to
Ilgira Sole. And Ludovico had made him retreat with a look alone. Renolfo Saravala. He raised his
free hand. Slowly. With that calm of someone who has all the time in the world and knows it.
Like a man greeting an old acquaintance in the middle of the street on a Sunday. He held the
gesture half a second in the air. His eyes fixed on mine across the garden. Then he took half a step back.
Entered the shadow of the wall and vanished. I stood there with my hand on my belly.
Without moving, counting my breaths until I reached ten. The witch wasn't waiting for the next move.
She'd already made it. The blast entered my sleep before the sound itself did. It was a dry crack,
far off at the back wall. And then a second one closer against the stone of the wall.
I sat up on the bed in the old contract room with my hand already on my belly. As if my body had
learned the gesture before I did. The clock on the wall read 320 in the morning. I heard bastion in
the corridor shouting orders at two men I didn't know. I heard footsteps running up the service stairs.
I heard Donakirah calling my name from somewhere far off. My bedroom door opened with a shove.
Ludovico was there in the gap, wearing his coat over an open shirt. I recognized the coat before I
recognized his face. It was the same one from the rainy night. Months ago. The same heavy fabric
keyed put over my shoulders without saying a word. He never knew I'd kept that detail.
Neither did I. Until I saw it there again. Get up. He said, slowly. I got up too fast. The
dizziness came at once. A wave of heat rising up my neck and the room spinning half a degree.
He caught me by the elbow before I could hit the corner of the night stand. Slowly. He repeated.
Lower. We went down. In the hall, Donakirah was crouched behind the sofa with Narina,
who'd shown up at the mansion without my knowing when. Bastion was at the door. Gun in hand. His face
without a single line more than usual. One of the pains in the formal sitting room had shattered on the
floor in long shards. One of them caught my arm when I passed too close. The cut was a graze.
Short. More shock than blood. Ludovico saw the red line rise on my white skin before I felt it.
We're leaving here. He said. Now. Bastion drove. I sat in the backseat with Ludovico holding a
folded cloth against my forearm. He pressed with the firmness of a man who'd done this more times
than any man should. The lights of Providence passed by the window in yellow smears. No one spoke
for three kilometers. I had a secret that could no longer sleep in my pocket. Ludovico. He turned
his face toward me without letting go of the cloth. I'm pregnant. I said, and your mother has already
sold that information. He closed his eyes for half a second. That was all. No start. No shout.
No idiotic question. When he opened his eyes, they were those of the man the city feared.
But turned only toward the inside of the car. I know what to do. Bastion took a narrow road
climbing into the hills. I vaguely recognized the curve. Without knowing why. Ludovico didn't
tell me where we were going. Nor did I ask. The house was at the end of a packed dirt path,
surrounded by tall pines. Dark stone facade. Window shut for years. Tiles covered in dry needles.
Bastion stopped the car near the entrance and got out first. He stood at the door. Gun resting on his
thigh. His eyes on the road we'd come by. It was my father's. Ludovico said, opening the door for me.
No one here was ever happy. But no one knows of this house outside of three people. I went in.
The smell of shut up wood. Dust for more than one winter. A distant trace of dried lavender
in some piece of furniture. He lit the hearth without yet taking off his coat. The fire caught
fast. Hungry for the old paper he stacked beneath the kindling. He knelt with me before the hearth.
A thick rug cushioning our knees. From the small kit Bastion had thrown into the car. He took a
clean bandage, a dark bottle, and cotton. It'll sting. He said, I've had worse sting. He almost
laughed. He didn't. He ran the antiseptic over my arm with the patience of a man who'd been
taught to kill and was learning, right there, to heal. His hand paused a second longer than it
needed to over the skin. A small second. Nothing. My chest registered it as if it were a whole minute.
I almost believed it. I said, looking at the fire. These two days, I almost believed you'd planned
it all to lose me. He didn't stop the gesture. He just answered in the same low tone.
I planned to lose you because I didn't know I could stay. The silence after that was thick.
The hearth crackled. Outside the wind passed through the pines with a sound like breathing.
He wrapped the bandage around my arm with a firm knot on one side. There. He said, I didn't stand.
Neither did he. He lifted his hand from my elbow to my face. Slowly, giving me time to pull back if
I wanted. I didn't pull back. His thumb stopped on my jaw. I leaned my forehead against his.
It was the gesture we'd invented in the bedroom corridor months ago. The one I'd kept is if
it were a password only hours. If I touch you now, he murmured. It's like choosing. Again. Good.
He kissed me as if he were apologizing and promising at the same time. It wasn't the kiss of a
man who thinks he's one. It was the kiss of a man who'd finally stopped losing on purpose.
The heat of the hearth struck my back. The fabric of his coat was rough beneath my fingers.
I smelled the fire the antiseptic him. I thought in a flash too quick to hold.
That I'd waited weeks to breathe this close again. I thought I was still afraid. I thought the
fear now was of something else. He laid me down on the rug slowly. He slid his arm under the
nape of my neck. Before letting my weight rest on the floor. As if my body were the most delicate
thing he'd ever carried. His hand moved down the side of my hip and stopped. Open. Over the still
invisible curve of my belly. It stayed there. He looked at my belly like a man looking at a secret
that  had  become  a  promise.  Hours.  He  said,  low.  My  eyes  stung.  I  didn't  let  them  fall.  Mine.
I  answered.
And my voice came out firmer than I expected. And yours, he pulled the coat off his shoulders,
took off his shirt, and stood there in the orange light of the hearth with the old marks of his life
on display. A long scar on his left shoulder, a smaller one near his ribs. The outline of a
mall tattoo on his chest I'd never seen up close. I touched each of them with my fingertips.
Slowly. Like someone reading a story in Braille. He closed his eyes. You tremble when I touch you.
I said, only you. I pulled his face to mine. This time the kiss was deeper, slower, with a kind of
hunger and no hurry at all. His weight on my chest was dense and alive. The rug beneath my back was
rough and just the right measure. He undid the strap of my night gown with a patience that
almost irritated me. Slighting the thin fabric off my shoulders until it exposed my breasts to
the heat of the hearth. His large hands cupped each of them with reverence. His thumbs tracing
slow circles around the nipples that hardened under his touch, pressing with enough delicacy
to draw a trembling sigh from my lips. Ludovico. Slowly. He answered, his mouth at my neck.
We have time now. His lips moved down my chest and warm wet kisses. Savoring every inch of skin
as if he wanted to memorize the taste. His tongue circled a nipple, sucking it into his mouth
with a firm, steady pressure. While his free hand caressed the other breast, squeezing and releasing
in sync. My body arched involuntarily against him. My hands buried in his dark hair, pulling
him closer. He switched sides, giving the same attention to the other breast. His teeth grazing
the sensitive skin lightly, sending waves of intense pleasure spreading through my belly.
My hands explored the firm muscles of his back, moving down to the waistband of his pants.
He let me undress him completely, revealing the member already rigid and pulsing. The skin hot and
smooth under my fingers. I caressed him slowly, feeling the thickness, the vein that throbbed at my touch,
moving up and down in long, passionate strokes. He groaned low against my skin, the sound vibrating
in my chest. He moved lower, kissing the curve of my belly with infinite tenderness. His hands
parting my legs gently. His mouth found the wet, hot center between my thighs. His tongue tracing
slow, precise lines along the swollen folds, circling the sensitive point at the top with dedication.
He sucked softly. Then with more intensity, alternating broad licks and circular movements that made
me tremble. Two of his fingers entered me slowly, curving to reach the inner point that made
clenched around them. While his mouth never stopped devouring me with tender hunger. I pulled him up,
turning our bodies on the soft rug until he lay on his back. I mounted him. My body facing his,
and took his member in my hand before bringing it to my mouth. My lips wrapped around the swollen head,
sliding down slowly, tasting the salty clean flavor of him. My tongue swirled around the thick length as
rose and fell. One hand massaging the base and the other exploring his firm thighs. He groaned. His
hands holding my hips and pulled my sex back to his mouth, returning it with the same intensity.
Our mouths worked in unison. The reciprocal oral sex turning the air into muffled size and horse
groans. His tongue penetrated deeper into me while I sucked him with devotion. His hips moving
subtly to meet the rhythm of my lips. The pleasure was mutual, electric. Each
carousif is tongue sending shocks that made me suck harder around his pulsing member. The heat
rose in spirals inside us, but he turned me carefully, positioning me beneath him again. His eyes
met mine, full of desire and protection. He went slowly. He was meticulous. He was a man who knew
that one wrong pressure could hurt a wounded arm and a secret inside me. And he chose each movement,
like a man choosing a word that can't be taken back. His breathing slowed near my ear when he
finally positioned himself. He raised himself on his arms to distribute his own weight.
And I saw the effort in the muscles of his shoulders. The deliberate care. He fit into me in one
long restrained movement. His eyes on mine the whole time. I held my breath. He stopped right
after. forehead pressed to mine. Waiting for my body to remember him. His member filled me
completely, stretching the inner walls with a delicious warm pressure. Each inch entering slowly
until our bodies were joined entirely. Stay with me. He whispered. I'm here. The rhythm came
slowly. Deep. He kept one hand flat on my belly, protecting what was inside without stopping the
way he moved me. His other hand tangled in the nape of my neck. I heard the hearth heard the wind
in the pines. Hered his breath breaking against my cheek. Hered the low sound coming from my own
throat that I didn't recognize his mind. Each thrust was deliberate. His hips pulling back
almost completely before advancing again. His member sliding in and out with perfect friction
that grazed every sensitive point. His testicles struck softly against me with each deep thrust.
The rhythm gradually building as sweat glistened on his skin in the firelight. I thought
between one movement and another that this man had written a clause to let me leave. I thought
that  now  he  was  building  with  his  own  body.  The  reason  for  me  never  to  leave.  The  heat  rose.
His
mind  became  only  his  name.  Ludovico.  Here.  Ludovico.  I'm
here.  He  sped  up  slightly  without  losing
his focus. An each movement began to hit a spot that made me arch my hip against his. My fingers
sank into his back. I felt the heat of the hearth and the heat of him confused. Indistinguishable.
One single thing. He murmured something in Italian into my hair that I didn't understand. And
I didn't need to understand. The tone was clear. His member swelled even more inside me. The deep,
rhythmic thrusts carrying me to the edge of the abyss. My body clenched around him. The inner
muscles pulsing. And the intense pleasure exploded in powerful waves. A strong orgasm that made
me scream his name as spasms of ecstasy ran through every nerve. He followed right after. His
body tensing in one last deep movement. His member pulsing as the warm release surged inside
me and intense bursts, filling me completely. A horse sound escaped his throat against my neck.
We stayed like that a long time. His hand went back to my belly. It stayed open there. Quiet.
I put my hand over his hand. I closed my eyes and let the rest of the fear drain away.
I thought, with a remnant of me that hadn't yet surrendered everything.
Whether that had been a real choice or just the relief of still being alive after the blast,
I found no answer. I found his gesture. His hand over my belly. His breathing slowing.
It was answer enough for today. I fell asleep there on the rug, with his coat over the two of us.
I woke before her in the house in the hills. The fire had died to embers. The morning light
came through the cracks in the window in gray bands. I landed a slept with her hand over mine.
My hand still on her belly. I stayed looking at her face for a time I didn't measure.
There was a decision I'd put off for three months that would stop being postponable the moment she
opened her eyes. I'd written that clause alone in my father's study, a week before sitting at the
cafe Vecca Roma across from her. I wrote it because I didn't believe a woman could stay with me
for anything other than fear or debt. I wrote it because I wanted to leave an exit door open for her.
I wrote it because the only love I'd learned to give was permission to leave. I spent three
whole months knowing that she'd still existed. I put off destroying it. I thought I'd have time.
I thought erasing it later would count the same as never having written it. It didn't. As long
as that clause was in the world, I would keep being the man who'd needed it, and not the man who
chose her. She deserved the second. The first had cost her two days locked in a room she thought was
her place once again. I ran my finger over her shoulder, very slowly without waking her.
You're going to be Donna. The way one is named, I said. So low that only the fire heard.
She nod the way one is bought. I opened the door carefully so as not to wake her.
Vastian was outside, gun on his thigh, eyes on the road. He turned his face when he heard me.
Go back to the mansion, I said. Gather all the elders and my mother in the main room tonight.
Fausto witnesses. You witness. Say it's from my own hand.
Vastian looked inside. At the rug. At her. And back at me. He nodded half a degree, left.
I stayed there until she woke. When she opened her eyes and looked at me,
I knew I'd never write another door again. We stayed in the house in the hills the rest of Friday.
I slept twice more. Eight what bastion brought from the car. Let Ludovico tend the dressing on my arm
one more time. He spent the afternoon on the phone with Fausto, arranging the following night.
We went back to the mansion at the start of Saturday evening. I had the handwritten draft in
the pocket of my dress. I gave it back to him before going into the main room. Neither of us said anything
about it. It was agreed without words. The main room was full. Don Vittorio, Don Emiliano,
and Don Cisto seated in the high chairs at the back. Botavia and a side arm chair, spine straight,
hands crossed over her lap with the same polite contempt of the first day I set foot in that house.
Fausto standing near the hearth, bastion leaning against the wall by the door. I came in without
taking Ludovico's coat off my shoulders. He'd covered me again in the car, without saying anything,
and I hadn't given it back. I pulled my part of the contract from my pocket. The copy Don
Ciara had brought back to me in the old room on the first day of morning. I tore it in two in front
of them. I didn't shout. I let the pieces fall on the rug. I'm not leaving with any fortune,
I said. Nor with any child under my arm. I'm staying. Not for the door, for the house.
Botavia opened her mouth, closed it. I stared at her without blinking. Ludovico took a step forward.
He took the handwritten draft from the inner pocket of his jacket. He looked at his mother first,
then each of the three elders. The clause was mine. He said. The power it gave me over her was mine.
Now it belongs to no one. He held the sheet out toward the hearth. The paper caught fire at the
edge with an almost impatient haste, as if it too had waited too long. He held it until the last
safe instant, then let go. The ashes fell over the stones of the hearth. He turned to me. Not to them.
You are my equal. Of my family. The Donna of the Karachiolos. Don Emiliano, the eldest,
was the first to move his head. Half a degree. It was only half a degree. But it was him.
Don Vittorio followed. Don Sisto last, with an almost imperceptible delay.
Botavia didn't move at all. She stayed where she was. Hand still crossed.
Looking at her son the way one looks at a polite stranger. Botavia had lost. And she knew it.
Ludovico took my hand on the way out of the room. He pulled me into the corridor, away from the eyes.
And only then let out the air he'd been holding the whole time. And the cerevaules, I asked low.
He raised my hand to his mouth, pressed his lips to my wrist, and looked at me over my own hand.
Tomorrow I deal with the cerevaules. Today I'm yours. Bastion stood near the window of the
breakfast room with the newspaper folded under his arm and his usual face, which meant something
had happened. I learned that early. When his face had no expression at all, it was because he was
holding one. Two days had passed since the night of the elders. The mansion breathed the different air.
When I was still learning to recognize, Dona Kiyara served coffee with her chin higher.
The corridors, which had always seemed too empty, now had people who greeted me by the name
the family had reluctantly accepted. And there was a small, but real difference in the way that
greeting arrived. Less ceremony, more person. Ludovico raised his eyes from the newspaper.
Providence? He asked, Boston, Bastion answered. South dock, Renolfo Saravale,
found this morning with problems. Problems of what order? The order that doesn't
ask for a second visit, Sir. Ludovico turned his eyes back to the newspaper, as if Bastion had
commented on the weather. He turned the page with a calm, I no longer found cold. I found it deliberate.
There was a difference. I picked up my cup with both hands, felt the warmth enter my fingers,
and asked nothing more. Someone in Providence would no longer send word with dead flowers.
That was all I needed to know. The rest I left with him.
Nareena appeared in the doorway carrying a white box wrapped in green ribbon.
Cake, she announced, in that way she had of turning every entrance into an act.
Before anyone asks why. Bastion got up and pulled a chair for her, without a word,
without taking his eyes off the window. Nareena looked at the chair.
Looked at him. Sat, arranging the boxes ribbon on the table as if she'd seen nothing.
You know that stone face turned out kind of handsome after the coffee. She said,
loud enough for Donna Kiera to hear from the kitchen. Bastion coughed into a hand.
Change the subject by asking Donna Kiera for another plate. I filed it away somewhere inside me.
The chair pulled out and the averted look. And the cough that wasn't a cough.
And I didn't comment. There were stories that weren't mine yet.
Seven weeks later, the garden was covered in flowers. I didn't wear a veil. I chose a simple dress,
cut at the waist. No train and no adornment I'd need to carry. The bouquet was of Camilias.
The same ones I'd been watering since the start of that spring and pot scattered along the corridor
window. A small routine that had become mine without my noticing the exact moment.
Nareena had helped me tie the white ribbon around the stems the night before,
crying while she laughed at herself, which was exactly her way of being happy for someone.
I walked to the altar alone. There was no one to give me away. And even if there had been,
I wouldn't have accepted. No one gives away a woman who has already given herself. The morning
sun came in slanted between the rows of chairs, and the shadows of the rose stems on the arch
fell in long streaks over the stone path. I heard my own footsteps. They were the only ones.
Ludovico waited beneath the arch with his father's old watch on his wrist and his arms at his sides,
not crossed, hiding nothing behind them. He was in a dark suit. No tie. When he saw me arrive,
he swallowed. I saw the movement in his throat. I also saw the effort he made not to let more than
that show, and I saw that the effort wasn't enough. Nareena cried,
priddly, seated in the front row, with Donna Kiarra's hand over hers. Donna Kiarra cried in an ugly
way, an embroidered handkerchief pressed to her nose. Her shoulders shaking in generous silence.
Bastion was in a tie as few times as I'd ever seen him. A dark gray tie, meticulously nodded,
the only sign that that morning was different from all the others. Nareena turned to the nearest
person and said it loud enough to reach the altar. If he blinks twice in a row, she said,
it's a smile. Bastion blinked twice in a row, without turning his face. I saw it.
Atavia was in the front row on the right side, in a dark blue wool dress, and the bearing of someone
came because she needed to be seen. She was invited. She accepted out of politics. I didn't
look at her once, and when the priest began to speak, I realized I also wouldn't need to anymore.
The priest said short things. Ludovico said his vow so low that the chameleas barely heard it,
but I heard it. He said he'd learned, too late, that love isn't guaranteed with a clause,
that he'd spend the rest of his life without writing any exit door for me. That if one day I
wanted to leave, it would have to be me walking, because he'd no longer build the exit with his own hands.
I said my vow looking at him. I chose to stay. I'll keep choosing every day. He kissed me with
no contract between us. No door. With the morning sun on my back and the smell of Camelia in the air,
and his hands on both sides of my face, as if I were the only stable thing in a world he'd
spent his whole life trying to control. Winter came heavy in Providence. Enrico was born on
late January dawn, with snow falling outside the window and thick quiet pieces. No wind. As if time
had decided to be gentle at that hour. Labor was long. Ludovico didn't leave the room once. He
held my hand through every contraction. His forehead pressed to mine. murmuring things in
Italian that I'd begun to understand because of how much he murmured near me in hours without witnesses.
Outside, Narina waited with Donna Kiara, and an absurd basket with enough sandwiches to feed a whole
Italian because that was her way of enduring the weight. Bastion stood in the corridor with the gun
hidden under his jacket, protecting something that had no enemy that dawn. Enrico came into the
world with a strong cry. The size the family had waited for over three generations. The obstetrician
placed him on my chest first. He stopped crying almost at once, as if he recognized the place.
I stayed looking at him. That tiny piece of a person with wet black lashes and hands closed into
small fists, and I found no word sufficient for what I felt. I didn't try. Ludovico took him
afterward. He held his son in his arms with both hands open. The small body lost in his large arms,
and stayed motionless for a few seconds just looking. And that was when he wept. He didn't hide it.
He didn't turn his face. He didn't run his hand over his eyes as if wiping away something
he wept looking at his son. His chin trembling and the tears running down the line of his
jaw without him making any gesture to stop them. With a stillness that was only his and that I'd
never seen in any of the faces he used in the world. He has your nose. He said low to me when he found
his voice. Poor thing, I answered. He laughed in the middle of the weeping. He leaned his forehead
against mine. That gesture that had become our private language. Then he leaned his forehead against
Enrico's two, closing the triangle among the three of us. And we stayed like that for a time I
couldn't measure. Enrico, he said, you were right. I'd suggested the name weeks before,
on an ordinary night while we waited for the snow to stop outside. Enrico, in honor of his brother,
the one who died at 19 in a story he told me only once. Slowly, without a dormant.
Ludovico had looked at me for a long time when I said it, without saying yes or no.
As if he needed to carry the name a little before giving his answer. Only now, with his son in
his arms and the weeping he didn't hide, was he saying yes. Six months after the birth,
the morning in the sweet was one of the calmest the mansion had ever seen. Enrico slept in the
crib in the room next door, and the monitor beside my side of the bed, purred with his breathing.
That sound that had become the soundtrack of my small hours. The June light came through the cracks
and the shutters and wide warm bands. Ludovico came in carrying a tray with two cups,
barefoot, no jacket, in the previous day's shirt. He sat on the edge of the bed and handed me mine.
Two sugar cubes, a drop of milk. I laughed softly. The way one laughs at an old joke that keeps
working out of love for what it means. Do you remember? I asked, that I told you once months ago,
my mother's dream. He already knew which question it was. I saw it in the way he held his own
cup. Unhurried. He let me finish anyway. A library I continued. In federal Hill,
free books for the neighborhood children. She never had money to put a book in my hand that wasn't
borrowed from the school or from someone who owed a favor. I bought the building three months ago,
answered, looking at his cup. The work began last Monday. I didn't tell you because I wanted it to be
a surprise when the sign went up. It was going up next week. I stayed quiet. The band of sun
crossed the sheet slowly. The sign. I asked softly. What's it going to say? Marcecano Community
Library. Your mother's maiden name. You told me one dinner night and passing. The way one
tells something without expecting anyone to keep it. I kept it. I set the cup on the night stand
before I could spill the coffee over the sheet. I leaned my forehead against his. We stayed like
that a good while, without either of us finding a word worth more than the silence. In Rico
woke shortly after. I nursed him. Changed him. Handed him to Ludovico so he could make the baby laugh
with that stone face that no longer fooled anyone. At the end of the morning we went down to the
winter garden. I took in Rico in my arm so he could see the chameleas. The same ones that had become
my bouquet and that I still watered now with him on my hip, showing him the flowers as if he knew what
they were. Maybe he did. Ludovico sat beside me on the stone bench with the coffee he'd brought
down from upstairs. Still warm. The June sun came through the glass panes at a low angle,
warming the stone without burning. Do you remember the morning? He said in a low tone.
When I received an envelope and put it in the drawer, I remembered at once. The morning after the
night everything had shifted sides. On the other side of months and of all that came after. The
old envelope sealed with the crest of the lion with the broken crown. He'd put it away unopened
in front of me and hugged me too tight for an ordinary Saturday morning. I remember. I answered,
you hugged me too tight for it to be nothing. He ran his hand slowly over in Rico's hair,
who slept against my shoulder with his mouth slightly open. It really was nothing. Just the beginning.
I stayed looking at him. The winter garden was in a good silence. The kind that asks for no filling.
In Rico breathe deep against my neck. Ludovico's hand was open over mine.
Between the two bodies, in the middle of the stone bench, without grip, without weight, just there.
I thought of the islanda who'd waited at the altar of the church and providence in a white dress
with a bell-tooling 12 times to say what the whole city already knew. She was another person.
She was me, but she was another person. The one who didn't yet know that humiliation can be the first step
of a path worth walking. Ludovico raised my hand and kissed my wrist, slowly, without announcement.
In Rico let out a small sigh on my shoulder. Outside, the white camellia swayed lightly with the wind
coming through the gap in the garden door. The bot wife of Providence had a price. No one,
not even he knew it was this, to stay.