I was left at the altar in front
of the entire town. My
fiance vanished. The guests
laughed
behind my
back, and the wedding debt fell
on me like a sentence.
Within days, I lost my job,
my home, and what little dignity
I had left. That
was when Ludovico Caracelo
appeared. The most
feared man in Providence offered
me away out. He'd pay
everything. Clear my name, and
protect me.
If I agreed to be his wife on
paper, I thought I was
entering a cold contract. But
soon I
discovered my fiance hadn't just
run away, and that
Ludovico knew far more than he
let on.
The bouquet trembled in my hand,
and I couldn't decide
whether it was the weight of the
roses,
or the weight of the waiting.
Providence church smelled of
melted wax and old lilies. That
two
sweet perfume that clung to the
throat. The priest had
already checked the clock three
times. The first
he smiled at me the way you
tried to call my child. The
second. He turned his face to
avoid my eyes.
The third, he didn't even bother
pretending anymore. All of
Providence was seated behind me.
I felt the murmur rise up the
back of my white dress like a
cold current, a whisper that
swelled
with every passing minute. The
women in the fifth row had
stopped disguising their
whispering.
One of them laughed low, held
back, and I heard it because I
heard everything in that moment.
The rest of the fans, the
shuffle of feet, the tick-tock
of the old clock at the back of
the
nave, a delmo had set the time
for 11 o'clock. It was ten to
noon. Narina was right behind
me,
in the first row, squeezing the
back of my hand as if she could
hold me in place by the strength
of
her fingers. She didn't say
anything. Narina had a comment
for everything, a joke even at a
funeral.
And her silence right then was
the most terrifying thing that
happened to me that morning. I
closed my eyes,
took a deep breath, counted to
ten. I opened my eyes, and the
church door was still empty.
I, Alanda, Narina murmured close
to my ear. Sweetheart, don't
talk. My voice came out steady,
low, but steady. If you talk,
I'll fall apart. She squeezed my
hand again, and the bell began.
One toll, noon, two tolls. The
priest came down from the altar
and walked over to me. Three
tolls.
The women in the fifth row were
no longer laughing. Four tolls.
Five, six, eleven, twelve. The
bell
told for the last time, and the
echo hung in the church's
vaulted ceiling like something
dirty,
ugly to look at. No one moved,
no one coughed. All of
Providence held its breath at
the same time.
And I felt in my shoulders the
exact moment the town
understood, collectively, that I
had been abandoned.
The priest stopped in front of
me, hands folded. There was pity
in his eyes, and pity is the
one thing a bride doesn't know
where to put. My child, no. I
clutched the bouquet to my
chest.
You don't have to say anything.
I turned my back on him. Facing
the altar was easier than facing
Providence,
but the church had only one way
out, and that way passed by
every familiar face. Every stare
from those who had come to see
exactly what they were now
seeing. Narina stood up with me.
I'm
coming with you. She said, one
step at a time. I started
walking, one step, then another.
The dress
dragged behind me. And every
inch of that fabric weighed like
a remnant of what I had imagined
that
morning would be. I had imagined
laughter. I had imagined a shy
kiss at the altar. I had
imagined
a delmo squeezing my elbow with
that nervous way of his
whispering, I'm here, I'm here.
A delmo
hadn't come. I passed the third
row. Mrs. Marchetti, my neighbor
for 10 years, lowered her head.
I passed the fifth row, and no
one was laughing anymore. I
passed the distant cousin a
delmo
had invited at the last minute,
and he avoided my eyes with a
haste that almost broke me.
Narina held my arm. Look ahead,
just ahead. We reached the door.
The sunlight outside hit my
eyes,
and for a moment I saw nothing.
And in that white blaze of
light, I almost believed I was
going to
morning that it had all been a
bad last minute dream. It
wasn't. I went down the stone
staircase slowly,
because going down fast was
admitting that I wanted to run,
and I had decided without
deciding
that Providence would not see me
run. The stones were worn in the
middle, the iron railing
darkened by age. Each step
caused the same effort as a
breath. A yellow taxi stopped at
the bottom,
at the corner of the square. I
hadn't called it. Narina had. I
got in. She got in after me.
Federal Hill, she told the
driver. End of at wells near
Salvis Bakery. The driver looked
at me in
the rear view mirror. Saw the
white dress. Saw my face and
didn't ask anything. He started
the car
in silence. I rested my forehead
against the glass. The city
rushed past outside. The statue
in the
square. Old Salvis Bakery. The
corner where Adelmo had kissed
me for the first time three
years ago.
On that corner, he had told me
he would love me until the day
the world forgot how to turn.
The world had turned just fine
that morning. I got home before
I felt my feet. Narina opened
the door to my apartment. Went
in first. Started turning on
lights. I stood in the middle of
the
living room, still in the dress,
still holding the bouquet, and
looked around like someone
visiting a
stranger's house. Everything was
still in place. The cup I had
washed before leaving. The book
left
open on the arm of the sofa. The
empty vase waiting for the
wedding flowers. I sat on the
floor. I just sat.
The dress billowed around me
like a cloud, and I didn't cry
because crying was asking too
much
of the body at that hour. I just
sat there with the bouquet in my
lap and stared at the door.
Narina sat down next to me on
the floor. Without taking off
her shoes, without smoothing her
dress.
She rested her head on my
shoulder and stayed. He'll show
up. I said,
something happened. An accident.
Something. Narina didn't answer.
Narina. No. What do you mean no?
He's not going to show up,
Iolanda. She lifted her head and
looked me in the eye. If it had
been
an accident, someone would have
called. If something had
happened, his family would be at
the church.
No one was there. No one. I
stayed quiet. She was right.
That morning, none of the
mothers. Not his brother. No
one. I had seen it. And I hadn't
seen it. Sunday passed without
my
remembering it. Monday morning,
the phone rang. The principal of
the school where I'd been
teaching
literature for four years called
me by my full surname with a
strange formality. And I already
knew before she finished the
sentence. Iolanda, it's not a
good time to keep a teacher
involved in
scandal. Scandal? I leaned
against the kitchen wall. I was
jilted Mrs. Peretti. I wasn't
caught stealing.
Silence on the other end. Then
the mothers are talking. You
understand? A teacher needs an
intact
reputation. Reputation. I
repeated. The reputation of a
woman who was humiliated in
public is the
reputation she lost. Iolanda,
please, please, I said. Yes,
please, my
hung up. I stood in the kitchen.
My hands still on the phone. And
felt nothing. No anger, no
shock, no tears, just a very
polite emptiness.
Like the emptiness of a room
after the guests have gone.
Tuesday morning, the collectors
began.
The first one showed up at
eight. In a dress shirt and
carrying a black briefcase. And
said my
name over the inner com with a
casualness that froze my blood.
He came up. Sat in my living
room like
someone who'd been there before.
Open the briefcase and handed me
a paper. You signed here. His
finger stopped beneath my
signature. Next to a delmos.
Wedding paid for with borrowed
money.
$12,000. Do in 30 days. I didn't
sign any loan. He turned the
paper toward me. It was my
handwriting.
It was my signature. It was
right there. Beneath a line of
text I didn't remember reading.
Because now that I looked
closely, the signature had been
collected in the pile.
Along with the ceremony
paperwork. The day a delmos
asked me to sign just some
boring forms.
Love from the venue. I had
signed without reading. The man
waited for me to understand.
When I did, he closed the
briefcase. You have 30 days. If
you'd rather pay an
installments,
there's interest. If you'd
rather negotiate, there are
partners. Take your pick. He
stood up.
We're watching. He left. I
didn't move for a stretch of
time. I can't measure.
Then I went to the window and
saw his car parked across the
street. I kept watching. He
didn't look
up. He didn't need to. He had
already looked at me enough.
That afternoon, the second man
showed up.
Wednesday morning the third.
Thursday morning, the eviction
noticed taped to the apartment
door.
Narina arrived that night with a
grocery bag. And the serious
face she almost never wore.
She set the bag on the table,
pulled out a bottle of wine,
pulled out a butter knife. I
brought
wine and a butter knife. She
said, pick first. I laughed
before I realized I was
laughing. It was an
ugly laugh, short, lasting a
second. But it was a laugh. And
Narina recognized it the way you
recognize a friend's voice after
years. Butter knife. I answered.
I can't handle wine tonight.
She set the wine aside. Set
down. Took off her shoes. Do you
have anywhere to go? No. Do you
have
money? No. Do you have a plan?
Narina. If I had a plan, I
wouldn't be holding a butter
knife.
She squeezed my arm. Stayed like
that for a while. You're staying
with me. She said,
as long as you need. My couch is
ugly, but it's mine. I nodded
slowly. I didn't know if I was
thanking her or refusing. Both
things at once, maybe. She
stayed late.
Cooked pasta with whatever was
in the pantry. Made me eat three
forkfuls.
Took the wedding dress off the
hanger where it had hung since
Saturday and carried it away
without
asking me. Tomorrow I'll burn
it. She set it the door or
donated to charity. You decide
later.
I decided later. E. Wednesday
morning and envelope arrived. It
was on the floor by the door
when
went down to get the newspaper
out of habit. Not because I
wanted to read the news,
but because going down the
stairs was the only gesture of
the day that still felt like
mine.
The envelope was of thick paper,
the color of old cream, no
stamp, no postmark.
Just my name written in the
center. In firm tall
handwriting, slightly slanted to
the right.
Eolanda, Marcecano. No one wrote
my full name like that. Not even
my father wrote my full name
like that. When he was still
alive, I went up the stairs
slowly. Satted the kitchen
table,
opened the envelope carefully as
if something might escape from
inside it. There was only a
card.
Cafe Veccia Roma. Tomorrow. 5pm.
Perhaps I have a solution for
you.
L.C. I stared at the three
letters. L.C. Two initials an
period at the end. Like someone
who
economizes even with letters.
Providence had three ways of
pronouncing those initials.
And all three meant the same
person. Lutavico Caracolo. The
man the whole town bowed its
head to.
The man my father had forbidden
me to look at when I was a
child. And saw a procession of
black
cars passing down at Wells
Avenue. Don't look, Eolanda. He
had said, that car in the middle
is the
car we pretend doesn't exist. I
was little and I looked anyway.
I saw no one. The glass was too
dark.
Now that same man had written my
name with his own hand. He knew
my address. He knew of my
debt. He probably knew more
things about me than my
ex-fiance I knew. I set the card
down on the table.
I ran my finger slowly over the
L. The ink still smelled almost,
almost, or maybe it was my
imagination.
Picturing that fresh ink as a
way of him being closer. I
closed my eyes. I thought of the
eviction noticed tape to the
door. I thought of the man with
a black briefcase watching my
building
from across the street. I
thought of Mrs. Pairetti calling
me miss with disgust. I thought
of
Nareena on her ugly couch and
how much she deserved to sleep
in peace without a ruined friend
breathing in her living room. I
opened my eyes. I didn't go to
the cafe because I wanted to.
I went because I had nowhere
left to run. Cafe Veccia Roma
sat on a corner of the old
neighborhood
where time had decided at some
point to stop passing. Dark
wooden doors, smoked glass
windows,
a discreet bell that rang when I
pushed the door open, and the
noise inside dropped.
It didn't drop because of me.
All the stairs at the table
shifted. In a small,
synchronized
movement toward the table at the
back, and the table at the back
had a man sitting at it.
Ludovico Caracciolo was dressed
in dark from shoulders to shoes.
A suit cut with precision.
A white shirt open at the top
button, no tie. A cup of coffee
resting in his right hand. His
wrist
exposed, an old watch with a
worn strap. He raised his eyes
when the bell rang, and saw me
before
I decided what to do with my
feet. Dark hair combed back. Two
days' worth of stubble. His eyes
were
the worst. Eyes that already
knew of me before I arrived. As
if he had memorized my face
before
I even reached the door. I
walked to the table. He didn't
stand. He didn't pull out the
chair.
He just watched me come, and the
whole cafe watched me come with
him. I sat. Miss Marcie
His voice was low. Deeper than I
had expected. Words spaced out.
Like someone choosing them one
at
a time and giving up on the ones
he didn't need. Mr. Caracciolo,
I set my purse on my lap.
You know all of Providence is
looking at this table. All of
Providence looks at any table I
sit at.
He brought the cup to his lips.
Took a small sip. It's not about
you. What a relief. The corner
of his mouth twitched slightly.
It wasn't a smile. It was the
sketch of a thought he decided
not
to finish. A waiter appeared
hand behind his back, bent
enough to be respectful. What
will you have
ma'am? Coffee. Black. No sugar
today. The waiter nodded and
disappeared. Lutavico watched me
or did he say anything.
You called for me. I
straightened my shoulders. I'm
here. If you have
something to say, say it. You
don't like preamble. I don't
have time for preamble. He said
the
cup down slowly on the saucer.
The clink of porcelain was the
only sound at the table for a
moment.
You owe $12,000 to the Costanza
Brothers. He said. Neighborhood
loan-sharking. You lost your job
on Monday.
You lost your apartment on
Wednesday. You have a friend who
offered you her couch. You have
no
living relatives and providence.
And the fiancee? Enough. I cut
in. You've made your point. He
stopped.
Tilted his head a fraction of a
millimeter. In a gesture that
was almost a thank you for
my frankness. I was going to say
he continued that the fiancee is
a matter you still don't
understand,
but today isn't the day for that
conversation. And what day is
that conversation? A day that
depends on what you do in the
next five minutes. The waiter
returned with my coffee. I took
a sip too
quickly and burned my tongue on
purpose to have a physical
reason to pay attention. Then
say it. I said,
Ludovico rested his elbow on the
table. The old watch gleamed in
the low light. I erase every
cent of your debt. I buy the
Costanza's papers tonight. I
give you back the apartment if
you want,
or arrange another one. I handle
the school problem. Mrs. Peretti
will get a phone call and
remember that she likes you.
You're describing a miracle. I'm
describing a transaction.
Besides didn't waver. In
exchange for a single thing. I
took another sip. I didn't let
my hand
go. What thing? You marry me. On
paper. The cafe kept making
coffee around me. The steam wand
cut through the air. Someone
laughed at a distant table. And
I sat there listening to the
most
feared man in Providence
offering me a contract marriage
with the same calm you'd order
the check.
Is that a marriage proposal? I
said slowly, or a purchase
order. He almost smiled. Again,
he didn't smile. It's a
proposal. You can refuse. You
can get up from this table right
now. And the
only thing I'll do is pay for
your coffee. And tomorrow.
Tomorrow the Costanza brothers
still exist.
And the eviction notice is still
taped to the door. I held the
cup more firmly.
Marriage on paper. I repeated.
What does that mean exactly? A
civil contract.
City Hall. No religious
ceremony. He began counting the
rules on his fingers.
Without lifting his hand from
the table. Just moving them one
by one. You live in my house.
You have your own room. I have
another. Both doors stay closed.
Go on. In public, you're my
wife.
You go to events with me. You
smile when it's time to smile.
You don't need to pretend more
than that.
In private, nothing. I won't
touch you. I won't go into your
room. I won't ask about your
life.
And you won't ask about mine. No
questions. No questions. I set
the cup on the saucer.
I thought that no questions had
the smell of a locked door. And
locked doors were exactly the
ones I always wanted to open.
For how long? One year. After
that, you can ask for the
separation
without any contest from me. If
you'd rather stay longer, it's
negotiable. Why me? It was the
first
question of mine that took him a
second longer to answer. Just a
second. Because you need it.
His voice dropped half a tone.
And because I need a wife for
reasons that don't fit into this
conversation, I held his gaze.
He held mine. Neither of us
blinked for a stretch of time
that
would have been awkward at any
other table. I'll think about
it. I said, you haven't till
tomorrow morning.
Me. He took from the inner
pocket of his jacket, a
cream-colored card with tall,
firm handwriting.
The address of a city hall. If
you show up, it's yes. If you
don't, it's no. I took the card.
Our fingers didn't touch, but
they passed so close that I felt
the warmth of his hand for
a second before I pulled mine
back. Do you always negotiate
like this? I asked two sentences
in a card?
No. He leaned back in his chair.
But with you, I didn't want to
make things up. I stood up from
the table. I didn't thank him
for the coffee. He didn't expect
me to. I walked to the door with
my
backstrate, knowing all of
Providence would be recounting
this scene for weeks. When I
touched the
handle, I heard behind me, low.
Almost thought aloud. Two sugar
cubes, a drop of milk.
I stopped. I looked over my
shoulder. What? Ludovico didn't
look at me. He was stirring his
own coffee
with a small spoon. That's how
you take it. When you're not
testing me, I stood there a
second longer
than I should have. Then I
opened the door and left. I
slept badly. I woke before the
sun.
I shoured. Put on the least
wrinkled blue dress in my
closet. Gathered my documents
into a small
bag and went down the stairs
without saying goodbye to a
single thing. I left a short
note
for Narina on the kitchen table.
The kind that explains nothing
and promises everything. I'd
have to
take the scolding later. City
Hall was three blocks from the
harbor. I arrived 15 minutes
before
nine. He was already there.
Leaning against the corridor
wall. Hands in his jacket
pockets.
Looking at his own shoe like
someone who'd been waiting long
enough to have memorized the
floor.
Beside him, an older man, broad
shouldered, but the look of
someone who'd come back from
wars no one had named. Ludovico
raised his head when he saw me.
He didn't smile. He made no
ceremony.
He just waited for me to arrive.
Good morning. I said, good
morning. He made a discrete
gesture
toward the man beside him.
Bastion del Rose. He works with
me. He'll be nearby whenever you
go out.
Bastion tilted his head half a
degree. No hello, no pleasure,
no smile, just the half degree.
Nice to meet you. I answered
anyway because my grandmother
would have smacked me if I
didn't answer.
The clerk called us. We went
into a small room with a long
table.
Papers already prepared.
Ludovico pushed them toward me
before the clerk could open his
mouth.
Read it. Slowly. If there's any
claws you don't accept, we redo
it. I read every line.
It was exactly the way he'd said
in the cafe. Separate rooms,
appearances in public, no
questions, one year, right of
unilateral exit on her part. I
reached the last page and slid
my finger down to the signature
line. I saw nothing I wasn't
supposed
to see. Not then. It's fine. I
said, I signed. He signed after
me. The clerk stamped it.
There was no kiss, no photo, no
rice thrown on the way out. The
three of us left city hall in
the car was waiting. Black,
glossy, glass-to-dark. The kind
my father used to tell me not to
look at when I was a child.
Bestion opened the rear door.
Ludovico got in from the other
side and sat
next to me without saying
anything. The car took the road
toward the upper suburb.
Providence shrank in the window.
The red rooftops falling away
behind us. In green took over.
He didn't speak the entire way.
Neither did I. The mansion gate
appeared after 20 minutes.
Dark iron, tall, with a discreet
crest in the center. A lion's
head with the crown split in
two.
I didn't ask what it meant. It
was part of the no questions.
The gate opened. The car went up
a
lane of low trees. I saw the
house before I knew it was a
house. Three stories of pale
stone,
tall windows, a double staircase
at the entrance. A small woman,
my grandmother's age,
appeared at the door above. Her
pulled into a low bun, white
apron, dry hands,
donachyata, Ludovico said, this
is Yolanda. Donachyata looked me
over from head to toe,
not with judgment, with concern.
The kind of look only a kitchen
woman knows how to give.
Welcome. She said, you must be
tired. I'm fine. She didn't
believe me, but she nodded and
didn't
insist. Ludovico took me
upstairs. The upper corridor was
long, with identical door
as on both sides. He stopped at
the third door on the right and
opened it. This is your room.
It was too big for one person. A
canopy double bed, a desk at the
window, a built-in closet
along an entire wall. Everything
in shades of cream and gray, a
tasteful cold. My room is at the
end
of the corridor. He said, behind
me, on the left side, you don't
need to go past it. Understood?
If you need anything, Donachyata
is always nearby. And you, he
paused a second. If you need me,
Donachyata knows where I am. I
turned to look at him. He was
standing in the doorway,
one hand on the handle, looking
at some point between my
shoulder and the window. For the
first time
since the cafe, he seemed unsure
of where to put his gaze. Thank
you. I said, I wasn't quite sure
why. He tilted his head a
fraction of a millimeter. Close
the door. I heard his footsteps
go
down the corridor, in silence. I
sat on the edge of the bed. I
ran my hand over the dovet,
and the fabric was soft in a way
that made my eyes sting without
warning. I didn't cry.
Not that first afternoon. That
night, Donachyata came up with a
tray, hot soup,
fresh bread, a glass of red
wine. I didn't ask her to swap
it for water. I drank the wine
to the
last drop. I lay down without
changing my clothes and stared
at the ceiling of the canopy.
Near midnight, I heard footsteps
in the corridor, slow, measured
footsteps. They came from the
end of the corridor. They
reached my door. They stopped.
They stood there for a stretch
of time. I
couldn't measure. Five seconds.
Ten. More than ten. He didn't
knock. He didn't call out. He
made no
sound. Then the footsteps went
back. I heard them move away
slowly. The same rhythm in the
direction
they had come from. The door at
the end of the corridor opened.
Closed. I stared at the canopy
in the
same position and understood,
lying in that bed too big for
one person, that the man the
town feared
had come to my door on the first
night. Not to come in, not to
speak. Only to stop outside,
and then go back. I closed my
eyes. I didn't sleep. The
Karatio Lomanshin woke before I
did. I
discovered this on the first
morning when I came down the
marble stairs still in my robe
fastened up to my neck and found
the house already breathing.
Donachiyara, tidying the
sideboard in the
hall, the smell of fresh bread
coming from the kitchen. A staff
member I didn't recognize
cleaning
the vestibule stained glass with
silent movements. No one looked
at me as if I didn't belong
there.
No one looked at me as if I
belonged either. It was worse
than hostility. It was
professional
neutrality. Good morning, ma'am.
Donachiyara said, seeing me
standing in the kitchen archway.
Coffee here or in the garden
room, it took me a second to
understand that ma'am was me.
Here is fine,
I answered. If it's not in the
way, she laughed softly. The
kind of laugh only Italian women
of a certain
age know how to give without
taking their hands off their
apron. You, in the way in my
kitchen,
that's a good one. I sat on the
wooden bench against the
counter. Donachiyara said a cup
in front of
me without asking how I wanted
it. Two sugar cubes had been
dissolved in it. A drop of milk
had been added on top. The
coffee was exactly the color I'd
been drinking since I was 15.
I held the cup with both hands.
Did you tell Mr. Ludovico?
Donachiyara kept stirring a pot
on the
stove without turning around. No
one needed to tell me anything,
my dear. Mr. Ludovico left it
noted.
He asked that it be this way
every day. She paused briefly.
Always. I drank the coffee too
slowly.
That was how the first week
went. I'd discover a house rule
by accident. And Ludovico had
already
altered the rule in silence so
I'd fit inside it. On Monday, I
mentioned aloud to Donachiyara
that I missed the bookside left
in my apartment. On Tuesday,
three of my favorites were on
the
little table in my room with new
bookmarks between the pages. On
Wednesday, I told Bastion I
hated
the black car because it
reminded me of a funeral. I only
said it sarcastically, because
he
appeared in a dark suit in the
corridor and I wanted to provoke
him. On Thursday, Bastion
appeared
at the winter garden door with
his hands folded in front of his
body, with the stone face that
was already his trademark. He
asked me to ask whether you'd
prefer the gray car or the black
one to
go out today. I looked up from
my book. Do I have something
scheduled today? You will, if
you want to.
He blinked once. Bastion, I
said, trying not to laugh. Were
you always like this or were you
trained?
Both, ma'am. And he went back
down the corridor with a step
identical to the one he derived
with.
I kept staring at the door for
half a minute with the book
forgotten in my lap,
and admitted to myself that this
house was starting to become an
intimate joke I had an asked to
be
part of. The problem was, the
joke had an owner, and the owner
of the joke didn't smile.
Ludovico and I crossed paths
with icy formality. In the
corridor, he'd nod,
half a degree, enough not to be
rude. At dinner, we sat at the
two ends of the long table like
two
chest pieces pretending the
board was too big for any
attack. He'd ask if I'd needed
anything.
I'd answer no. He'd ask if Dona
Chiarra had been kind. I'd
answer that she was an angel.
He'd
fold his napkin and stand up. No
questions. That was the rule. He
kept the rule better than I did.
Wednesday evening, Narina showed
up at the gate with a leather
bag that looked like it weighed
more than she did. Bastion
opened the gate for her without
arguing. Dona Chiarra hugged her
like
Narina walked through the hall
with wide eyes and a comment on
the tip of her tongue. This
place
looks like a museum with
tasteful ghosts. I pulled her
into the kitchen before Ludovico
could
appear. Sweetie, she whispered,
taking a Tupperware container
out of her bag. I brought my
grandmother's
lasagna, not that Dona Chiarra
needs help, but my grandma liked
you, and I wasn't going to let
that slide. You're a social
hazard. I know. Where does he
sleep? Narina? Just so I know
the distance
between the two rooms, Missy.
It's field research. We sat on
the kitchen bench, split the
lasagna
into two bowls, and ate in
secret like two teenagers who'd
snuck out of the cafeteria.
It was the first time I'd
laughed since the church bell. I
laughed for real. My face half
lowered,
almost choking on a piece of
cheese. Dona Chiarra passed by
the door, pretended not to see,
and kept going toward the
garden. Ludovico passed by the
door five minutes later.
He also pretended not to see,
but I saw him. He had his shirts
leave rolled up to the elbow,
his hair a little out of place.
The kind of detail I shouldn't
have registered. He stopped in
the
archway for half a second.
Exactly long enough to identify
me laughing, and kept going down
the corridor
without saying anything. Narina
gave me a discreet kick on the
foot under the bench. Sweetie,
she whispered, mouthful. That
man just looked at you the way
you look at an open window in
the middle
of winter. Shut up. It's a
professional observation. You're
a music teacher, Narina.
Music is observation, my girl.
What do you think we listen to?
I nudged her with my elbow. She
laughed.
Dona Chiarra came back with a
picture of water as if nothing
had happened. I took a long
sip and said nothing more. That
night, when Narina left, the
corridor was too silent. I
passed the
library door, and saw the light
on under the crack. I didn't go
in. I went to my room,
closed the door, and took a long
time to fall asleep. The kitchen
was too big for crying at dawn.
I discovered this three days
later, on Monday, when I came
down barefoot at three in the
morning,
because I'd woken with my heart
in my throat, and a dream of an
empty church stuck to my neck.
I turned on only the light above
the stove. I sat on the cold
floor with my back against the
cabinet.
The crying came without sound.
The way I'd learned to cry when
I lived with my grandmother,
and she didn't like to hear
sadness after ten at night. I
heard the footsteps before I saw
his
shadow in the archway. He didn't
turn on the main light. He stood
there for two seconds in the
doorway,
in a white shirt open at the
collar. His hair sang he hadn't
slept either. He didn't ask
anything.
I lifted my chin before he could
think of touching me. I don't
need an audience to cry. Thank
you.
He stopped in a very specific
way, without retreating or
advancing. He just stayed.
Then, without saying a word, he
crossed the kitchen, opened the
cabinet beside my shoulder,
and took out a glass. He filled
the glass with water at the
sink. He set the glass on the
floor near my
knee. He sat on the floor across
from me. His back against the
opposite cabinet, his legs
stretched
out in a way that made his feet
almost touch mine, and he
stayed. He didn't talk. He
didn't ask.
He didn't offer a shoulder. He
stayed there. On the cold
kitchen floor, with his rumpled
shirt
and his gaze on some point
between my knee and the
baseball, breathing slowly. I
cried for two
more minutes. I drank half the
glass. I cried a little more. I
drank the rest. When I stood up,
he stood up too, without
touching me. He collected the
glass, carried it to the sink,
washed it with the same calm he
did everything else. Good night,
Ayolanda. I went back to my room
and
took a long time to fall asleep
again, but for another reason,
the first public dinner came on
Friday night.
Il Jira Sole, a restaurant that
served all of Providence without
serving anyone properly,
with a crystal chandelier and a
metre, who lowered his head half
a degree when Luda Vico entered.
He told me at breakfast with a
short sentence. In the way I
already recognized as his way of
asking
without asking. Il Jira Sole,
nine at night. It's important
that we appear together.
Dress? Whatever you think is
good, I chose the dark blue one,
the one with thin straps that
held a mid-caf. I put on the
only pair of earrings I'd
brought from the old department.
I came down the stairs with my
hair pinned at the nape and saw
Luda Vico waiting below,
in a black suit that looked like
it had been cut on his body, and
an expression he managed to
keep closed for three seconds
before looking away.
Let's go. He said. At the
restaurant, everyone looked. No
one stared.
We sat at a table near the back.
The metre poured the wine with
slightly trembling hands.
Luda Vico ordered for me without
consulting me. A dish I wouldn't
have ordered,
and that was exactly the way I
liked it. I raised an eyebrow.
Does Donut Jira have a notebook
of
records? I asked. She has a
memory. Her memory is about me,
about everyone who sits at her
table.
I took a sip. Luda Vico. He
looked up. Does this still feel
more like a contract than a
marriage?
He held the glass by the stem,
swirled the wine a quarter turn,
set the glass back on the table
without drinking. What would you
rather it feel like? I don't
know. I admitted. I'm still
figuring it out.
He almost smiled. Almost. It was
at that moment that Renolfo
Saravale crossed the restaurant.
I didn't know who he was. I only
felt the restaurant changed
temperature before he reached
the table.
Luda Vico stiffened half a
degree. Enough for me to notice.
Not enough for anyone else to
notice.
Renolfo was a man in a light
suit, a wide smile and heavy
shoulders,
with a colabrian accent that
dragged the consonants in a
strange way. Luda Vico,
what a nice surprise. Renolfo.
And this must be the new Mrs.
Caracciolo. Renolfo turned to me
with theatrical courtesy and
extended his hand and immense
pleasure. Before I could decide
what to do with my hand,
Luda Vico simply looked at him.
He didn't speak. He didn't move.
He just looked. The look
lasted exactly the length of one
breath and Renolfo understood.
He withdrew his hand with the
mile still hanging on his face,
in the way of a man who knows
he's lost this round,
and that the next subject is
better left untouched. Anyway,
Renolfo said with forced
lightness, good to see you Luda
Vico. And good night, ma'am. He
left. I kept looking at Luda
Vico.
He went back to his glass
without comment. I didn't ask.
I'd learned quickly in that
mansion.
That asking about a scene like
that was a waste. It rained as
we left the restaurant.
Not a heavy rain. A fine rain.
Early autumn weather and
providence. The kind of rain
that
soaks you inside without seeming
to soak you. I'd forgotten a
coat. Luda Vico had already
opened the car door for me when
he noticed. Without saying a
word, he took off his own coat
from his shoulders and put it
over mine. The fabric was warm
from his body. It smelled of
something woody I couldn't name.
He got in the car on the
driver's side. Bastion drove in
silence.
The way back to the mansion was
short. The coat weighed on my
back in a specific way.
No one said anything. When
Bastion parked, Luda Vico got
out, opened my door,
and waited for me to step out.
He still said nothing. He just
stood there on the gravel,
with the fine rain wetting his
shirt, waiting for me to pass in
front so he could close the
door.
I climbed the entrance stairs
with his coat on my shoulders.
Bastion stayed down below.
In the upper corridor, I
stopped. Luda Vico stopped two
steps behind. I took his coat
off my
shoulders very carefully. I held
it back out to him without fully
raising my eyes. Good night Luda
Vico.
He took the coat by the
shoulders. His thumb lingering a
second longer than it needed on
the
fabric that had touched my
shoulders. Good night, Ayolanda.
I went into my room. I closed
the door.
I leaned my back against the
wood. I looked at the imaginary
coat I was no longer wearing.
At the sensation of weight that
was still there, stubborn on my
shoulders. I put my hand to the
collar of my dress and felt my
own pulse at my fingertips,
beating faster than it should.
That was
when I understood. It wasn't
fear of him. It never had been.
It was fear of what was
beginning
to move inside me every time he
stayed quiet in the right place,
in the right way, at the right
time.
Fear of looking at a coat
hanging on a stranger's arm and
thinking of a woody scent.
Fear of the coffee served
exactly the way I'd been
drinking it since I was 15,
without ever having told him.
Fear of having cried on the
kitchen floor with a man sitting
silently across from me and
discovering that for two
minutes, it was less lonely than
any
conversation I'd had in the last
ten years. I leaned my forehead
against the door. The bell had
told for the last time two weeks
ago. And on the wrong side of
the corridor, a man I'd signed a
track not to love was closing
his bedroom door in silence. At
the end of the same night, he'd
covered me with his coat in the
rain. That was where, with my
hands still on the handle and my
pulse beating at my collar, I
realized I was, for the first
time since the church, truly
afraid,
and the fear had nothing to do
with death. Two
weeks later, I learned that a
mansion sleeps
differently from normal houses.
It doesn't sleep actually. It
slows down. The night staff
moved
through the corridors and silent
shoes. The lighting recedes to a
series of dim sconces along the
baseboard. And the vestibules
old clocks keep marking time as
if no one had asked their
opinion.
I had grown used to crossing
that silence barefoot. In my
robe fastened up to my neck,
when I couldn't sleep. And less
and less could I sleep. That
Monday dawn, I went down to get
a glass
of water. That was the official
excuse. The real one I wouldn't
have the courage to admit,
even to myself. The library
light was on. A yellow band
escaped from beneath the
half-open door.
I stopped in the corridor with
my hand at the waist of my robe.
I could go back. I should go
back.
I went forward. I pushed the
door with two fingers. Ludovico
was sitting in the tall armchair
near
the fireplace. His elbows on his
knees, and an untouched glass of
amber in his hand. No tie. No
jacket.
His white shirt open at the
collar and the sleeves rolled up
to the elbow the way he did when
he
worked outside the office. The
fire was low. The orange light
ran across his face and revealed
what
the day's mask hid. The short
scar at his temple that I'd
never noticed. The weariness in
his shoulders.
The jaw clenched in the way of
someone carrying something for
far too long. He raised his
eyes.
He wasn't startled. Couldn't
sleep. I came for water. The
kitchens on the other side.
I fastened the robe a little
tighter at my neck. You couldn't
either. He turned the glass
slowly between his fingers. I
don't drink. He said, looking at
the amber. I just hold it.
Why? Because if I drink, I talk
too much. We fell silent. I
shouldn't go in. I went in.
I sat in the armchair across
from his. With my legs folded to
the side. And the robe pulled
over my knees.
Neither of us moved for a while.
The fire crackled. One of the
corridor clock struck three in
the distance.
My brother liked this library.
He said suddenly. As if
continuing a conversation we'd
never
started. He'd read lying there.
On the rug, he said our father's
chair was uncomfortable on
purpose.
So no one would think of staying
too long. I didn't ask the name.
I waited. In Rico.
Ludovico kept looking at the
glass. He was 19 when the set of
olives sent a message in an
alley
in the old district. I was 22.
My father still alive. I was
forced to wait six years before
I
could collect that debt. I got
to the alley late. I got there
on time with Rinalpho. A log
shifted
in the fireplace and sent a
small spark toward the rug. He
looked at the spark with the
same calm
he looked at everything else.
The spark went out on its own.
I'm sorry. I said, and the
sentence
came out low. Without ornament.
He nodded. Half a degree. That
was all. I leaned my forehead
against the back of the
armchair. Without planning to, I
started to talk. My mother ran
away
from home when I was seven. I
said, with a man in debt. My
grandmother never forgave her.
She raised
me saying that owing someone was
the same as owing yourself, and
that a woman who depends on
others pays with her body sooner
or later. I swore from the age
of ten that I would never owe
anyone anything. I raised my
eyes to him. He was watching me
with an attention that had
nothing
to do with negotiation. Then I
sat down across from a man in a
cafe and signed a contract.
I finished. My grandmother would
laugh in my face. Lutavico
turned the glass once more.
You don't owe anyone anything I
alanda. I owe $12,000 to
someone. You no longer do. Then
I owe
$12,000 to you. He leaned half a
degree forward. His elbows still
resting on his knees. No.
No? You owe me exactly what I
wrote in the contract. Not one
comma more. Silence. We stayed
there
for another stretch of time. I
couldn't measure. Neither of us
touched the other. Neither of us
said anything else of
importance, but something moved
beneath my ribcage. Something
warm, uncomfortable,
that I had come to the library
terrified of finding. I stood up
before it became impossible to
stand.
Good night, Lutavico. Good
night, Eolanda. I went to my
room. I didn't sleep. But this
time,
the reason was different.
Tuesday afternoon I made the
mistake I'd been putting off
making. The door
to the small back room next to
Lutavico's main office stayed
locked. I'd noticed this in the
second
week. That afternoon, passing
through the corridor, I noticed
the door was a jar, not locked.
Dona Ciara had a headache and
Bastion had gone out with
Lutavico to someplace no one
told me about.
I went in. I should have left
the same second. I didn't leave.
The small room was a smaller
office, full of files, steel
shelves, a side table, an open
folder left on the table,
forgotten.
I went to the table as if my
body had gone before my head. I
lifted the folder cover. The
first
paper was a photo. A delmo.
thinner than the last time I'd
seen him. With a poorly shaved
beard,
coming out of a building that
wasn't in Providence. The photo
had a date at the bottom. Two
weeks
after the church bell. beneath
the photo, an address in Newark,
New Jersey. beneath the address,
an envelope with handwritten
notes and a firm slanted script.
The same as the note that had
arrived
at my apartment. Is a delmo.
Transfer confirmed. Silence paid
until further notice. I read it
three
times. I didn't understand. I
read it twice more. I understood
too little. That was when I
noticed
the step behind me. I turned
slowly. Ludovico was in the
doorway. He didn't huff. He
didn't raise his voice.
He just looked at the folder in
my hand than it me. Closed that
door behind you when you leave.
He said,
he didn't say to close it from
the inside. He said to close it
from the outside. I dropped the
folder on the table. My heart
beating in some spot that wasn't
my chest. I left. I passed by
him
without looking. I went to the
corridor. I was already crying
by the middle of the stairs.
Angry at the crying. Angry are
still at what I was feeling
beneath the crying. Over the
next few
hours, I rehearsed in my head
three different versions of the
same sentence. You knew where he
was from the
start. I knocked on the main
office door two hours later. He
told me to come in. He was
standing, hands
on the back of the chair,
waiting. As if he knew. You knew
where he was. I said, I
knew. Since when.
Since before you walked into the
cafe, what does that mean? He
didn't answer.
Ludovico, Yolanda. What does
that mean? He let the air out
through his nose. He didn't
answer properly.
He just looked at me in a way I
couldn't read. I knew his
silence now. I'd learn to read
many
silences in that house, but this
was a new silence. It wasn't the
silence of the rule. It was the
silence of someone about to
answer and choosing the moment.
I didn't wait for the moment. I
became a
person again. I said, my voice
coming out louder than I wanted.
A game that started before I
knew I was playing.
Is that what I became? No. Then
explain. He looked at the table.
He looked at me. He didn't
explain.
Ludovico. I'll tell you, but not
now. When. When I'm certain
you'll hear me out to the end.
I close my eyes for half a
second. When I opened them, I
decided that this mansion
wouldn't hold
me another hour. I left the
office without answering. I
climbed the stairs. Went into my
room.
Put a coat over my dress,
grabbed my purse. I went down
again. This time without looking
at any door.
I passed on a chair in the
kitchen. She saw my face and
didn't ask. I took the key to
the side door
no one used and went out through
the side gravel path. Going
around the mansion so I wouldn't
pass by the main entrance. The
service gate opened onto a
narrow lane. I followed the lane
to the street.
I followed the street to the bus
line. I took a bus to the old
district without looking at
anyone's face. I needed to walk.
I needed to breathe. I needed to
remember what it was like to
have a body that belonged to no
one. I got off at the stop near
the old market. The one that
closes
after six. Wet stone streets,
yellow lamp posts. Few people at
that hour, merchants gathering
crates, a loose dog crossing
slowly. I shoved my hands into
my coat pockets and walked with
no
destination. The anger pounding
at the back of my throat. I
passed the closed bakery,
turned on to a cross street that
led down to the docks. I walked
four blocks. It was at the fifth
that I noticed. A man in a light
suit had crossed the street at
the same pace as me. On the
other side,
he wasn't going anywhere. He was
coming toward me. Renolfo set a
volley. My step froze for half a
second
before I decided to keep walking
with my chin up. He sped up to
intercept me at the corner. He
got too
close. Mrs. Caratilo. He said
with the theatrical smile, what
luck for me. Excuse
me. I tried to pass.
He stepped to the side, cutting
off my path without touching me,
but closing off the street.
It won't take long. I just
wanted a minute. I don't have a
minute. You do. He tilted his
head
half a degree. The smile still
frozen. One thing I need you to
know. Okay. Your original debt
that
one from the wedding, he made a
small hand gesture. Like someone
describing something distant.
Was with us, Missy. It wasn't
with the castanzos. The
castanzos were just the front.
You're lying.
I'm not. The smile didn't move.
And we're still waiting for
payment. In person. The air left
my lungs
all at once. Get out of my way.
Just a message, Mrs. Caratilo.
He leaned half a degree. Still
without
touching me. Tell your husband
that we know where he keeps you.
Tell him we know where he sent a
and tell him that time's running
out. Okay. He took a step back.
He gave a nod,
almost courteous. And he was
about to exit the scene when a
car appeared at the top corner
with a sharp
breaking. The headlight hitting
him straight in the face.
Renolfo raised his hand to
shield his eyes.
Bastion leapt from the driver's
seat with his hand inside his
coat at the level of the
holster.
Get in, ma'am. That was all he
said. Renolfo raised both hands
with theatrical calm. Like
someone
who wasn't doing anything wrong.
He stepped back two paces into
the shadow of the corner. He
disappeared
into an alley before Bastion
could take another step. I got
into the car with legs that were
no
longer entirely mine. Bastion
slammed the door. He turned the
car onto the cross street. The
accelerated
enough to leave the old district
in less than three minutes,
without speaking to me. Only
when we got
onto the road climbing to the
upper neighborhood did he look
at the rear view mirror. Are you
all right,
I'm fine. You don't look at. I
ran my hand over my face.
Bastion, ma 'am. How
did you find me? He didn't
answer for half a block. Mr.
Ludovico asked someone to never
lose sight of you. Never. Since
the
day of the cafe, you follow me?
We look out for you. It's not
the same thing. It's not.
Bastion looked
ahead. But in this case it
worked out to be similar. I
stayed quiet the rest of the
way. My face
turned to the window and a
mixture of things in my throat
that I couldn't separate. Anger
at having
been followed. Relief at having
been followed. Shame at both.
Renolfo had said two sentences
that were
already burying themselves in
the exact spot where they'd hurt
later. Your original debt was
with us.
Tell your husband that we know
where he keeps you. Bastion said
one last sentence before we
parked
on the gravel. Mr. Ludovico will
want to talk. Better to let him
speak to the end this time. I
didn't
answer. I got out of the car. I
climbed the three steps of the
entrance. The main door was
already
open. Ludovico was at the foot
of the stairs. No jacket. No
tie. His sleeves still rolled up
at the elbow
the way they were in the
library. He wasn't angry. He was
something worse. He was afraid.
And Ludovico
Karachiollo afraid was something
all of Providence had never
seen. And I, without meaning to
saw,
he had a folder in his hand. It
wasn't the folder from the back
office. It was another folder.
Thicker. Heldunder his arm with
a car that didn't match the rest
of his body. He lowered his chin
half a degree. He looked at me.
And for the first time since the
cafe, his voice came out without
any
mask. Say, I'm
going to tell you everything.
The folder under his arm was too
thick. I recognized
the worn leather from far off.
The same color as the one I'd
seen in the back room. Tuesday
afternoon,
with the photo of a delmo and
Newark inside. Ludovico was at
the foot of the stairs. As
Bastion had worn in the car. And
there was no mask at all on his
face. Only weariness. And
something
deeper that I couldn't name. And
that squeezed my chest before I
could defend myself. Sit. He
said
low. When I came in through the
door. I didn't obey at first. I
stood there with my coat wet
from
the old district's drizzle stuck
to my shoulders. Still tasting
the metallic taste that the
mouth, Bastion came in behind
me. Looked at his boss. Looked
at me. And disappeared down the
kitchen
corridor without a word. Don't
let you out of didn't appear.
The mansion seemed to have
agreed
with her to hold its breath.
Sit, Elanda. Please. The please
was what moved me. I'd never
heard
that word from his mouth. I sat
in one of the library arm chairs
where he guided me. And he
pulled
the other one and turned it to
face me. So close our knees
almost touched. He said the
folder on
little table between us. He
didn't open it. What I'm about
to tell you, you've had the
right to know
for weeks. He began. His voice
horser than it usually was. I
put it off because I was afraid
you'd
get up and leave before the end.
Today if you get up, you get up.
I won't hold you. My jaw locked.
I made a small gesture with my
head for him to go on. Ludovico
opened the folder and took out
three
sheets. He didn't look at them.
Adelmo owed the cerevaules. He
said, he'd owed them for over a
year.
It wasn't gambling. It wasn't an
end of the month vice. He got
into a deal with Renolfo
thinking
he'd come out rich and came out
owing $35,000. And a promise he
didn't have the courage to tell
you
about. Adelmo's name and his
mouth sounded distant. As if he
were speaking of a man I'd known
in
another life. Maybe he was. The
promise was you. He continued.
His eyes fixed on mine. The
deal between Adelmo and the
Calabrian clan was simple. On
the wedding day, the cerevaules
would appear
at the church. Adelmo would sign
whatever he needed to sign and
disappear through the back door.
You'd leave with them. His debt
would be forgiven. You'd be the
payment in person.
Something inside me went cold.
In a way that left no tremor.
Only silence. I clashed my hands
in my
lap so I wouldn't move. The
wedding debt. He said, was built
on top of that. The castanzo
brothers
have been a front for the
cerevaules for three years. They
collected your signature in the
middle
of the venue papers because they
needed a rope around your neck
in case the church plan failed.
Two traps for the same day. One
for you to walk in wearing
white. Another so you'd have
nowhere to
run if the white dress wasn't
enough. How did you find out? I
said, and my voice came out
steady,
which surprised me. Three days
before the wedding. My lawyer
has an old informant in
the
house. The name crossed his desk
by accident. Linked to Renolfo,
Linked to yours. He brought it
to
me that same night. He stopped.
Ranna's hand over his face. Then
continued. I went after Adelmo
that same early morning. I
caught him at his place with a
bag packed for another city that
wasn't
the one he told you. He
confessed everything in 20
minutes. He cried. He begged
forgiveness from the
wall, not from you. I gave him
two options. He disappears from
Providence before dawn,
with enough money to reach
Newark and live quietly. Or I
let the Sarah Falls find out he
tried to escape
the deal. He chose Newark before
I finished the sentence. I
closed my eyes. I saw Adelmo at
the church
in his suit, smiling for photos
the week before. I saw the
church bell tolling 12 times. I
opened them
again. You made him abandoned me
at the altar. I made him abandon
you before he sold you. The
distinction landed between us
like an open blade. It didn't
hurt me the way it should have
hurt.
It just stayed there gleaming.
The bell, I said. And the bell
returned inside my head.
Tolling slowly. You let the bell
toll. I couldn't stop the bell
without stopping the town.
If I'd shown up at the church
pulling you away by the arm, the
Sarah Falls would know within
two hours that I'd stepped in.
You'd become a double target and
I'd become a war. I let the bell
toll because humiliation passes.
The bullet doesn't. I swallowed
hard. My mouth was dry in a
strange
way. The next day, he said, I
bought the Costanzo's debt. I
paid the $12,000 in your name
plus the rest the Sarah Falls
expected to receive on the side.
Two hours later, I had the paper
in my hand.
You no longer owed anyone
anything. Except you didn't know
that. And I couldn't come
looking for
you without the Sarah Falls
understanding that their
merchandise had a new owner. So
you waited
for me to lose my job. My
apartment, my name. I waited for
you to lose everything that
still
tied you to the town. He said,
and his voice finally wavered
because if I'd knocked on your
door
with money on Monday, you'd
throw it in my face. If I'd
knocked on your door on
Wednesday,
with you already having nowhere
to go, you'd listen to me. I
played you. I won't pretend I
didn't.
The silence pressed down. I
heard my own pulse in my ear.
The contract. I said,
it was the only way I saw to
have you under this roof without
the Sarah Falls understanding
what
was. If you became my wife on
paper, you became untouchable in
Providence. No one touches the
Don's
wife without starting a war. No
one wants to start. The whole
coldness, the separate rooms,
the rules, the no questions, was
to give you space, not to
control you. I didn't know how
to offer
you protection without it
looking like a prison. I chose
wrong. I chose too cold. I
stayed quiet.
He waited. He didn't try to fill
it. And a Delmo? I said
afterward. The photo in Newark.
I pay a man to keep an eye on
him. Not because I care about a
Delmo. Because as long as he's
alive
in some corner, the Sarah Falls
think the original deal can
still be collected. The day he
decides
to come back to Providence
thinking he can turn the tables.
I need to know before he does.
That's what
that note meant. Silence paid.
His silence. Not mine with you.
I stood up. I didn't know where
I was
I only knew I couldn't stay
sitting. I walked to the library
window, leaned my forehead
against
the glass, and looked at the
dark garden. His reflection
appeared behind mine in the
glass.
Seated. Still waiting. I need
air. I said, go. I left the
library with a firm step and
went down
the corridor to the back of
Miranda. The drizzle had
stopped. The winter garden had
its light low,
and the veranda was empty. I
leaned against the iron railing
and breath deeply for the first
time
in an hour. And then I cried. I
didn't cry over a Delmo. I cried
over the weeks I'd slept in that
room thinking I was merchandise.
I cried over the church bell,
tolding 12 times. Knowing now
that
behind that bell, there had been
a plan to hand me over behind a
cabinet. I cried over the glass
of water he'd set beside my knee
in the kitchen weeks ago, and
that I'd seen at the time as
elegant coldness. And now saw as
the only thing he knew how to do
without frightening me.
I cried because I'd spent weeks
thinking I was his shield when
in fact he was the one who had
become mine. He didn't come
after me. I stayed there until
the sky went fully dark. When I
went back
to the library, he was still
sitting in the same armchair.
The folder closed on the little
table.
His hands and his lap
intertwined. You should have
told me. I said from the
doorway. I was going to tell
you when you no longer needed
me. He said, without raising his
eyes, that sentence landed in
strange way. I stood there
absorbing it. That's pride,
Lutavico. I said, low. That's
fear with a
pretty name. He raised his eyes.
He didn't look away. It is. He
said, I know. I
sat back down in the armchair
across from him. I looked at him
for a stretch of time. I didn't
measure. He didn't rush me.
Tomorrow,
I said, finally, I want the
three elders here. In this hall,
I'm going to speak with them.
I'llanda, I'm calling them. Not
you. They called me a bot bride
behind my back. I want them to
hear
me face to face. He was silent
for a few seconds. Then he said,
tomorrow night. Tomorrow night,
I stood up and went up the
stairs slowly. I didn't go to my
room. I walked to the end of the
left
corridor. Stopped at the door
I'd never opened and went back
to my room because it wasn't yet
time.
But I knew it was a matter of
hours. I slept little. I dreamed
of the church bell
holding 12 times and of his hand
setting a glass of water beside
my knee. The next night,
the main hall was lit as if for
a family dinner. And it wasn't.
The three elders arrived 15
minutes
apart from each other. Don
Vittario came first. Tall and
thin with a silk scarf inside
his
overcoat. Don Emiliano next.
Stokki with the crest of the
split crown lion on his pinky
ring
and an unlit cigarette between
his fingers. Don Cisto last bent
by the ears with a silver
handled
cane. The family lawyer, Fausto
Renieri, the same one Lutavico
had mentioned in the library,
arrived alongside the hardest of
the three and stood leaning
against one of the columns,
silent, bastion stayed at the
door. Lutavico waited on the
other side of the hall,
without interfering. I came down
the stairs and the dark blue
dress Donutiara had laid on the
bed
for me without asking. I stopped
in the middle of the hall. The
three elders looked at me the
way
you look at an expensive piece
of China, assessing whether it's
cracked. Gentlemen, I said,
and my voice came out steady.
The three of you, at some point
in the last month, called me a
bride bought in some corner of
this house. I know this because
this house is large but not
large enough
for a whisper not to climb the
stairs. Girl, Don Cisto began,
his voice rasping. This is not
the
place for, I raised my hand. Let
me finish. I was bought, yes,
you're right about that part,
but you're getting wrong as
about the merchandise. The
merchandise wasn't me. It was my
life,
and whoever paid for it paid so
that it wouldn't be taken from
me by another clan. You know
which
clan. You know by whom. I saw
Donut, Miliano exchange a look
with Donvittorio. I continued.
I didn't come here to ask you to
like me. It's none of my
concern. I came to say only one
thing.
I chose to stay. Not because of
the contract. The contract still
has almost a year to go,
and you know better than anyone
that paper tears. I stay because
I chose to. No clause, no exit
door,
no price. My gaze crossed
Ludovico's from the other side
of the hall. He understood I was
speaking to
him too. His hand closed slowly
around his own wrist. In the
place where he wore his father's
watch.
That's all. I said to the
elders, good night. I turned and
went up the stairs. I didn't
look
back to know whether he was
coming. I knew he was. He caught
up with me in the middle of the
upper
corridor. He didn't speak. I
walked three more steps and
stopped in front of the door at
the end of
the left corridor. His mind was
three doors back on the right.
He stopped behind me. So close I
felt his
breath in my hair. I turned
slowly. His eyes were dark in a
new way, and his hand rose until
it almost touched my face and
stopped in the air, waiting. I
took his hand and pressed it to
my
face myself. He let out his
breath like someone who'd been
holding it for months.
His hand was warm
on my cheek. Mine over his,
trembled for half a second and
stopped. If you come in here, he
said,
low, his eyes on mine. There's
no more contract between us.
Good. I said, he leaned his
forehead
against mine. We stayed there,
breathing the same air of the
corridor. The sounds
of the house
seeming to know that this
instant was ours alone. The
corridor was dark except for the
yellow
light of the sconce at the end
of the wall. And that light
rested on his face in a way I
wouldn't have
had the courage to describe a
loud. Then he kissed me. It was
just one kiss. Slow, long,
quiet,
like someone finally saying a
sentence he'd rehearsed for
weeks, and discovered was
simpler than
he'd imagined. His hands slid
down to my waist and stayed
there with a firmness that
wasn't urgency.
It was decision. Mine rose to
the nape of his neck, and the
door at the end of the left
corridor
opened behind him. I went in.
The door closed. I woke with sun
on my face and didn't understand
it first where I was. The window
was different. Larger, facing
the side garden I'd never seen
from that angle. The curtains
were heavy linen. The color of
sand. Not the light white ones
of my room.
The smell of the air was
different, too. Dark wood.
Something citrusy and clean that
I'd already
learn to associate with him
without realizing when I'd
learned it. And there was a hand
on my back,
broad, warm, resting on my spine
with the calm of someone who
didn't intend to leave anytime
soon.
I turned slowly. Ludovica was
awake, propped on his elbow.
Looking at me the way a person
looks when
they finally allowed themselves
to look, without controlling,
without calculating. Just
looking.
As if I were a problem he'd
given up solving and decided
simply to have. Good morning. He
said,
his voice horse from morning.
Deeper than usual. Good morning.
He ran his thumb over the corner
of my
mouth. I don't know what he was
checking, but he did it with the
attention of someone verifying
that
something is still real. Half a
laugh of mine escaped before I
decided to let it. What is it?
I'm trying to remember the name
of my room. I said, I think I
forgot. He laughed low. It was a
sound
I'd heard very few times. And
that, that morning, seemed to
open something in his chest.
Something
he'd kept closed for a long
time. And now let out through
that small crack. There was a
knock at the door
with two discrete taps. Dona
Chiara's voice, from outside,
crossed the wood with the same
professional
serenity as always. Coffee sir
and madam. The tray is out here
when you want it. I heard the
sound of
her footsteps moving away down
the corridor, with a short pause
at the end before she
disappeared.
Exactly the length of a
contained smile. Calculated not
to be heard, and completely
audible
Ludovico got up, put on his
white shirt without buttoning
it, went to the door and came
back with the
tray. Two fine porcelain cups, a
saucer with thin biscuits, and
my cup already set with two
cubes
in a drop of milk. I put both
hands around it and said
nothing. The warmth passed
through the
porcelain and warmed my palms.
He saw that I saw. She knows
that I know. He said, sitting
again on
the edge of the bed. I left it
noted on the first day. I know
you did. We drank the coffee
without hurry. Through the
window of his room, the side
garden appeared whole. The
hedges still
with dew caught in the leaves.
The morning light cutting
through everything at a
diagonal. It was a
different view from the one in
my room. More open. Deeper. I
thought it would take me a while
to get
used to it. Then I realized I
was getting used to it now. We
went down together afterward.
Bastion
was crossing the hall with a
folder under his arm, and the
sure step of someone who has
three
tasks to solve before 10 in the
morning. When he saw us come
down side by side on the stairs,
he stopped for a third of a
second. The corner of his eye
betrayed half a millimeter of
curiosity,
and he kept walking toward the
library without breaking his
step. I thought I was going to
laugh.
I held it. Dona Kiarra passed us
in the kitchen corridor,
carrying a basket of flowers cut
from the
garden. White hydranges and
sprigs of rosemary and said,
good morning, sir, and madam,
with the same neutral intonation
as always, except for the corner
of her mouth that was making
a visible and silent effort to
stay still. Ludovico squeezed my
hand inside his more firmly.
His fingers interlacing mine,
and made no comment. We
continued down the corridor
toward the
garden as if coming down the
stairs together on a Saturday
morning where the most natural
thing in
the world. Maybe it already was.
Outside, the day had dawned
clear, with that firm winter
blue
that promises no warmth but
delivers light to spare. The
leaves still wet from the
previous
night's drizzle glistened. The
air smelled of damp earth, and
the thin smoke of coffee rising
from
the open kitchen. He led me to
the stone bench beneath the
Magnolia. Satt pulled me to sit
beside him,
and kept my hand inside his on
his knee. No tie. No audience.
No contract. Just the hand,
and the cold bench beneath us,
and the light hitting the
Magnolia leaves that still had
late blossoms
high in the branches. It's the
first time, I said low, that I
hold you in public without it
being
for appearances. Yes, he didn't
answer. He just squeezed gently.
His thumb passing over my
knuckles once.
We stayed there a good while,
without needing to fill it. A
swallow landed on the edge of
the stone
fountain, drank, and flew away.
The mansion's kitchen led out
the smell of hot bread through
the open
window, something in my chest,
which I'd been carrying clenched
since the church bell,
since the collector days of the
door. Since the afternoon I
signed a contract just to have
somewhere to sleep, began to
loosen slowly, not all at once.
Slowly, like a knot that
eased after being tied too tight
for too long. Bastian came up
the stone path with a firmer
step
than usual. He had an envelope
in his hand. Ludovico raised his
head, and I saw the exact moment
he
saw the envelope. His body
changed. Not much, just in the
shoulders, in the line of his
jaw,
in a way of straightening his
spine that wasn't posture. It
was alertness. It just arrived.
Bastian said, handing the
envelope into his hand. Man on a
motorcycle didn't stop. Ludovico
turned the envelope over. It was
old. The darkened cream color of
something that had spent time
kept in a drawer or a safe. And
on the back there was a red wax
seal with the split crown
lion crest stamped deep and with
precision. The same crest is the
Elder's Rings. The same as
the Manchins main gate. Except
that seal seemed older than the
Rings. Older than the library's
dark wood. Older than anything
I'd touched in that house. He
looked at the crest for two
seconds
longer than he should have. The
garden was quiet. The swallow
came back to the fountain and
flew away
again. Then he closed his hand
around the envelope carefully.
Thank you Bastian. Bastian
nodded and went back up the
stone path with nothing more.
Ludovico stood up. I'll be right
back.
I followed him with my eyes down
the covered corridor to the
office. The door closed with a
soft
click. I sat on the bench. My
hand marked by the warmth of
his. Watching the swallow land
for the
third time on the edge of the
fountain. I mentally counted the
seconds without meaning to
count. He
came back at 42, without the
envelope. With his hands in his
pockets, his shoulders slightly
lowered.
His face composed back into the
expression I'd learned to read
beneath. He sat again beside me.
He took my hand again. Firmer
this time. Two firm for a
Saturday morning that until a
minute ago
had been going very well. What
was it? I asked low. Nothing
that needs to reach you today.
I looked at him. He held my gaze
without looking away. And I saw
both things at once. The truth
about it not being today. And
the lie about it being nothing.
Two distinct things. Living in
the
same sentence. In the same dark
eyes I'd already learned not to
underestimate. I could ask.
I could insist. I could get up
from there and go to the office
drawer and open the envelope
myself.
Now that this house's door was
mine, too. I had that right. I
didn't. I chose to stay at
peace for one morning. A whole
morning. Without a knot in my
chest. Without a collector.
Without a bell.
I'd earned the right to choose
this. All right. I said, he
squeezed my hand again.
Then he relaxed his grip. And we
stayed there a while longer. On
the bench. Benete the Magnollia.
With the smell of the kitchens
bread arriving through the
window. And the swallow coming
back a
fourth time as if it too were in
no hurry to go anywhere. We went
to the winter garden late in the
morning. He brought a book. I
brought another. The space was
made of glass and iron. Full of
plants
don't a GR attended with an
attention I'd never seen
dedicated to plants. And the
light came in
from every side at once. Warm
and diffuse even in winter. I
sat on the long sofa near the
largest pain where the sun hit
hardest. He sat in the armchair
beside me. Stretched out his
hand
without looking and rested his
fingers on my ankle. The gesture
no longer asked permission.
He didn't take his hand away. I
read two pages without
understanding anything. I reread
them.
I understood. The light came in
through the pains and fell on
the broad leaves of the plants
in
bleak, slow bands. And I thought
without meaning to think it that
he'd put away that envelope
too carefully for it to be
nothing. That his hand was too
firm to be just a Saturday
morning.
I let the thought pass. Not
because I believed it. Because
today his hand was on my ankle.
And the sun was good. And I'd
climb the stairs the night
before without a contract. And
this
morning was mine. Tomorrow I
would ask. Tomorrow if he didn't
tell me I'd go after it. I'd
already
learn to go after things. And
I'd already learned that the
truth doesn't disappear. It only
waits. For today, I stayed. I
thought the greatest danger of
my life had been hiring ever
and for one night. But I was
wrong. The real danger began
when I started to believe that,
by his
side, I could finally be happy.
He loved me without hiding it,
protected me without confining
me.
His arms around me felt like the
only safe place in the world.
Until I found the envelope
hidden in his drawer. Three
photos. My face marked on the
screen of a
news report that hadn't yet
aired. A transfer receipt with
the exact date of the worst
night of my life
and a message from him. Short
sent to a number I didn't
recognize. She can't find out.
Within a few hours, my life
became a headline. The same
people who'd applauded me now
looked at me like an accomplice.
Dores slammed in my face. Voices
accused me terribly of something
I didn't even understand. An
evern, the man who swore to
protect me, disappeared for
hours,
and came back with a look I
couldn't decipher. I wanted to
trust him. But every silence
of his
eye, now I have to choose. Flee,
before he drags me down with
him. Or stay by the side of the
man
who may have orchestrated the
night that nearly destroyed me.
And what if the love that saved
me
is the same one that planned my
ruin? And what if every, I love
you of his was just the price to
keep me quiet? And what if, in
the end, the escort I rented
never stopped being the mafia
boss
the entire country fears? Like I
said, that was just a taste of
book two. To watch it
uncensored,
just click on the first link
here in the pinned comment. I'll
see you on the other side in a
few
seconds. Remember, just click on
the first link down here in the
comments. And book two,
complete. With no ads or
interruptions, we'll already be
available for you. It's very
simple.
Book two is something I'm loving
making, and you're loving it
too, so I promise there will be
more.
It's where you find increasingly
spicy stories. A true dark
romance. And precisely because
this version is getting more and
more heated, the video isn't
well accepted publicly on
YouTube.
This closed environment is where
I can actually share my essence,
and where I feel free to do my
best
work for you. More news coming
soon. I'll be waiting for you on
the other side.