Chapter 1. The morning before
the folder.
I woke before her like always.
The thin July light
slipped through the half open
curtain,
and fell in a slanted stripe
across Islander's bear shoulder.
I stayed still,
propped on my elbow, watching
her face as she slept.
A mouth slightly potted. Her
dark hair
spread across the pillow on my
side of the bed. One hand
curled near her chin like a
child's.
The air conditioner hummed low
almost imperceptible, and
there was a scent of jasmine
coming
from the window. She'd insisted
on planting jasmine on
the balcony, and I'd let it
happen
without arguing, which said a
lot about what she'd done to
me. There was a time when I
couldn't
sleep in that suite. Now it was
the opposite. I
couldn't leave it without first
making sure she was
still there. I admitted
inwardly, something I
still felt embarrassed to say
out loud. I was happy.
The words sounded strange in my
head. Almost indecent for
a man like me. Happy. I got up
slowly,
pulled the sheet over her
shoulder so the AC wouldn't hit
her
skin directly,
and went down barefoot. The cold
marble of the staircase under my
feet was the same as always,
but even that seemed different
on the mornings she was
upstairs. The mansions kitchen
at that hour was
mine alone. Donakyara was still
in the back garden cutting
rosemary. I could hear from far
off the
sound of her scissors against
the thick stems. The dogs slept
piled up near the service door.
My father's old clock kept the
slow rhythm of 620. I grabbed
the coffee tin,
measured it into the mocha pot
the way I landed her taught me
without realizing she was
teaching.
Two sugar cubes, a drop of milk,
never two. Bastion came in
through the service door with
his
planner under his arm, and
stopped talking before he even
started. He looked at me, looked
at the
cup in my hand, looked back at
me. Good morning, he said dry.
Good morning, he said the
planner on
counter, with the ceremony of a
man delivering an official
document. O second of silence.
Two ticks of
the clock. Should I build a
household for the dawn becoming
a barista? I didn't answer. The
corner
of my mouth betrayed half an
intention of a smile, and I
corrected it before he noticed.
He noticed.
Pretended not to. That's how
he'd worked for ten years.
What's on the schedule?
Fausto asked for half an hour
this afternoon. The elders sent
word about the dock, and Donak
Tavia. He paused, chose the
word, requested a family meeting
at noon. Formal sitting room.
I looked at him. Did she request
a meeting or announce one?
Announced. I filed the
information in the place where I
store the things I haven't yet
decided
what to do with. My mother had
come back from Naples two weeks
earlier than planned without
warning and without explanation,
and I'd expected her to arrive
with her temper sharpened,
with a list of grievances, with
that silence of hers that cuts
deeper than any shout.
I hadn't expected her to request
the formal room. The formal room
was for weddings, funerals,
and contract executions. By
mother knew very well what each
setting said before a single
word was spoken.
Teller will be there. I'll ander
and I. Bastion nodded. Brief.
Anything else? I raised the cup.
Take this up before it gets
cold. Set it beside the bed.
Don't say anything. She hates
being
and she's not talking to her.
She's not talking to her. She's
not talking to her.
not talking to her. She's not
talking to her.
She's not talking to her. She's
not talking to her. She's not
talking to her.
She's not talking to her. She's
not talking to her. She's not
talking to her.
She's not talking to her. She's
not talking to her. She's not
talking
to her.
The flash from the neighborhood
papers photographer had caught
her face at the exact moment
the bell told for the last time
and none of the guests knew how
to look at her properly. I did.
I saw in the photo the exact
moment her face understood that
Adelma wasn't coming
and I saw that she decided right
there that she wouldn't cry in
front of those people.
That day I decided two things
and I'm still keeping both to
get her out of the trap.
The Sarah Valls had set for her
and to never tell her that I'd
seen her cry in a white dress.
I heard light footsteps on the
stairs. The fourth step always
creaked and the sound reached me
with
the punctuality of an agreed
upon signal. I came back to the
present. I left the kitchen,
crossed the high ceiling to
corridor and passed through the
hall to the garden. She'd be by
the
chamelears. She was always by
the chamelears before eight said
it was the hour when the flower
is breathed.
She was, in a long night gown,
hair pinned at the nape,
watering can in her hands.
The morning still had that damp
July light that makes everything
seem slightly unreal
and she moved among the plants
with the ease of someone born
there. Though I knew that three
months ago she barely knew the
chamelears name. I came up
behind her without a sound and
kissed her
neck right where I'd learned she
shivers slightly. She shivered.
You shouldn't do that when I'm
you. If you soak the chamelears
and me along with them, I won't
be offended. She laughed
softly and turned her face until
she tucked her chin against my
shoulder. Her hair smelled of
rosemary,
probably because of Donna
Kiyara, who insisted on leaving
dried sprigs in every room of
the house
as if that were protection
enough against anything. Your
mother is up to something.
My mother is always up to
something. No. Today, she's up
to something. I looked at her
profile
against the morning light. She'd
learned to read the house the
way one reads the Bible,
word by word skipping nothing.
If she said my mother was up to
something, my mother was up to
something. Formal sitting room
noon, I said, we go together.
Together, it was just one word,
and it landed there like a
signature at the bottom. I took
the watering can from her hand,
set it on the ground and pulled
her to me by the waist. Beneath
the cotton of the night gown,
there was a small secret only
the two of us knew, and I could
count on my fingers the people
outside that house who also
knew. Iolanda, me, the doctor,
Donna Kiyara suspected, but
Donna Kiyara
suspects everything and is
rarely wrong. Do we tell them
today? She asked against my
chest.
My mother, your mother, I
thought a second. After the
meeting, we'll read the room.
She agreed
without speaking. I felt her
hair against my mouth and
decided that this was the last
morning
I'd put anything off. After
lunch, I'd tell Fausto to pull
the old contract out of the draw
and destroy it with me in front
of me at my signature. There was
a clause in it that I'd written
with my own hand in another
life, and I'd carried the
postponement of that clause, the
way a man
carries a small stone in his
shoe, not annoying enough to
make him stop, but always
hurting.
Today I was taking out the
stone. Come, I said, eat
something before you face the
matriarch.
She laughed again. She laughed
more since she'd been mine. I'd
learned to listen to her laugh
the
way one learns a language he
never cared to learn and ended
up in love with its sound. We
went inside,
and the garden door closed
behind us with the soft sound of
old wood settling into its
frame.
Four hours until noon, a whole
lifetime until noon. The formal
sitting room was the only room
in
mansion where I'd never felt
whole. Sealing too high,
mahogany shelves with books no
one read,
two sofas of dried blood-colored
velvet, and a rug so pale it
felt cruel to step on.
The air in there had that
specific smell of a shut up room
you only open on occasion.
Moth balls mixed with old
varnish, and something floral
trying to mask the other two.
Butavia liked that room because
the room made an impression.
That's why she chose it.
She sat with her back to the
window, and the noon light came
in behind her, and turned her
into a
dark silhouette against the
gold, a staging choice, the
choice of someone who knows how
to stage.
Bousto stood behind her, leaning
against the shelves. His head
lowered in a way I'd never seen
in
the conceliary. Don Vittorio,
Don Emilliano, and Don Sisto
stood. The three of them with
that old
bearing of men who'd learned to
stand for hours at wakes for
friends they themselves had
ordered
killed. I came in hand in hand
with Ludovico. I felt his finger
squeeze mine for half a second,
almost involuntary, and let go.
He read the room before I did.
Mother, son, Otevia moved her
head
a centimeter in my direction.
Ealanda, I sat on the sofa
across from them, him at my
side. I crossed
my hands over my knee. There was
a dark leather folder on the
little table between us, and the
folder
was closed, and the folder had
the crest of the lion with the
broken crown blind embossed on
the
cover. My stomach sank half an
inch. I recognized that crest.
It was the same as the letter
that
had arrived months ago. On a
night when I still didn't
understand much of what I was
living.
The one Ludovico had put in the
drawer without explanation.
Otevia opened the folder with
the
slowness of someone who knows no
one will interrupt. She took out
a sheet. Just one. Before my son
carries you twice. She said,
without looking at me yet, I
thought it better you know the
whole
contract. She pushed the sheet
with two fingers to my edge of
the table. I didn't move.
Ludovico
moved half a second to late. I
felt his hand hesitate on my
knee and settle there. I looked
at the
sheet. It was paper yellowed at
the edges. Family letterhead. My
signature at the bottom. That
shaky
signature I'd learned to make at
the registry office months ago
with my head spinning from
hunger
and humiliation. And above my
signature, in the third clause
at the bottom, there was a
paragraph
written by hand, by hand, not
typed, by hand. In the writing I
knew from notes in the corners
of
library books, from messages
left at my bedroom door in the
first month, from the dedication
he'd
written in a pavice novel and
pretended hadn't been him. I
read it once. On the day the air
is born,
the marriage is dissolved. The
wife leaves with a fortune
corresponding to half the dawn's
net worth, alone. Without the
child, full custody remains with
the Karachiolo family. I read it
again.
The words didn't change. I
raised my eyes to his profile.
He was looking at the sheet, not
at me,
at the sheet, and his mouth
opened, and his mouth closed. He
didn't say no. The tavia smiled
without
smiling. Keep your word son.
It's written in your own hand. I
heard my own name sound inside
my head
as if called from far away.
Iolanda. Iolanda, listen. That
writing is his. That paragraph
was him.
That paragraph had been there
the whole time. Beneath
everything, while I learned his
coffee,
while he pulled the sheet over
my shoulder, while we stood in
the garden with our hands inside
each others as if that were
real. He finally turned to me.
His eyes were the exact color of
the
Himelia garden. And in that
color, there was now a terror
I'd never seen on his face, not
in the
small hours of the library, not
on the night of the attack in
the street. Iolanda. No. I
stood.
My legs answered. It was the
mornings only luck. I smoothed
my skirt with both hands as if
that
mattered. And I looked at the
three elders, one by one, and
then atotavia. And lastly, very
lightly,
at Ludovico. You two fit
together. I said, the both of
you. My voice didn't shake.
To this day I don't know how. I
walked out of the room, though
everything in me wanted to run.
My heels struck the marble of
the hall as if they belonged to
another woman, and the other
woman
climbed the stairs far too
slowly. One step, two, three.
And on the 13th
I had to put my hand on the
palm. I focused on that. Only on
that. In the bedroom corridor, I
didn't go to the sweet I'd
been sharing with him for three
months. I went to the door at
the end. The door I hadn't
opened
since we'd decided to sleep
together. The white paint around
the knob was slightly faded.
I'd noticed that detail on the
first day, and completely
forgotten it afterward. The old
contract room.
I turned the knob. The air
inside was still warm, with the
smell of old wood, and the dust
that
gathers in places no one enters
anymore. The bed made as on the
day I'd left. The lamp on the
night stand with its bulb off.
The straw chair and the corner
where I'd sat on the night of
the storm
thinking that was the worst that
would ever happen to me. I
closed the door behind me, and
the click of
the latch sounded loud through
the whole house. I sat on the
edge of the bed. The mattress
was cold.
I laid my hand flat over the
belly no one yet new existed,
and for the first time in three
months,
I said quietly, to no one, and
to him, we're going to be okay.
It was the first lie I told my
child,
chapter two, the closed door and
the man outside. The afternoon
fell over the old contract room
without me moving from the edge
of the bed. I watched the
sunlight cross the floor in a
long rectangle.
Shrink, stretch, shrink, vanish,
the room turned blue, then gray,
then
black. I didn't turn on the
light. There was a sound I'd
learned to ignore over the past
months. The sound of the house
itself
breathing, pipes, wood
expanding. Donna kiaa's distant
footsteps in the pantry. I
listened to all of
it with a new attention, like
someone arriving at a place for
the first time. The smell of
cold wax
on the floor. The creek of a
window at the end of the
corridor. The whole house
sounding like a
living organism that didn't know
I was falling apart inside it.
Maybe it was the first time.
I started doing something I
didn't want to do and did
anyway. I started rereading the
last few
months backward, each gesture of
his, and fitting them into the
shape of that handwritten
paragraph.
The coffee, two cubes, a drop of
milk. He'd noted it on the first
day.
Adbastion noted, kept the order
alive in the mansion's kitchen
and at the cafe vekiae Roma.
I thought it was the small
tenderness of a man who doesn't
know how to say the big things,
and what if it was just care of
an investment? A man tens his
cattle with the same constancy,
but the same cold, calculated
attention, no affection, only
foresight. The coat over my
shoulders on the
rainy night. I'd kept that coat
at the back of the closet in the
first week. The way one keeps a
relic.
The dark, heavy fabric, with his
scent mixed with the wet cold of
the street,
and what if it had been the
calculation of a man who knows
an elegant gesture buys cheap
loyalty?
The small hours of the library.
Him broken in the armchair. The
untouched glass.
Talk about his dead brother. And
what if every sentence of that
had been rehearsed to soften a
woman
who still thought she was
merchandise? And the handwritten
paragraph proved she was?
I listened to that voice until I
almost believed it. Then, I
listened to another. The newer
voice.
The one three months old. The
one saying I wasn't an idiot.
I'm not an idiot. I'd seen his
face in
that room and I saw terror. Not
a game. I saw a man who didn't
know what to do with his own
hands while
his mother slid the paper across
the table. I stayed between the
two voices until my mouth was
too
dry to talk to myself. He
knocked on the door for the
first time near nine at night.
Three short
knocks his way without pleading.
I, Alanda, I didn't answer. I'm
not coming in. I just want to
know
if you've eaten. I didn't
answer. He stayed there. I heard
his breathing on the other side
of the wood.
Held back, controlled. The way
he controlled everything. Except
the things that truly mattered.
I heard him let out the air like
a man giving up on a sentence
before saying it. I heard the
footsteps drawing away far too
slowly. As if he wanted to give
me time to change my mind,
I slept dressed on top of the
comforter. I dreamed of the
church in Providence. In the
dream,
the bell wouldn't stop tolling.
I woke with the sun on my face
and my body heavy. I got up,
went to the adjoining bathroom,
washed my face with cold water
until my cheeks stung. In the
mirror
I looked at the woman with
swollen eyes and didn't
recognize her at first glance.
Second glance I did.
It was still me, just more
tired. He knocked twice on
Friday. In the morning,
in the voice of a man who
decided not to impose. In the
afternoon, in a horse or voice,
as if the hours had scraped
something loose inside. Both
times he said the same thing.
I'm here.
Both times I didn't open. Donna
Kira came up with a train near
noon. She didn't knock.
She left the tray on the floor
against the door with a note
under the plate. I waited for
her footsteps to fade and opened
the door the smallest crack. I
pulled the tray inside.
Soup, bread, a pair. The note
had three words in her round
motherly hand. Eat for the
little one.
She knew. Of course she knew.
Donna Kira knew everything in
that house. I ate the whole bowl
of
soup without tasting it. I ate
the bread. I ate the pair down
to the core. It was the first
thing I did for
the little one. And the second
thing I did for myself. In Arena
called near five, I answered
because it was
her. Are you alive? I am. Are
you eating? Now I am. You want
me to come over? I thought a
second.
The idea of having someone in
the room felt too big to bear.
Like a strong light in an eye
used to the
dark. Not today. Tomorrow.
Tomorrow I'll say. She was
silent long enough for me to
know. She was thinking
about not hanging up. And then
she said her thing. If you need
wine and a butter knife,
you know where I live. I
laughed. It was half-laf,
half-sob, but it was. It was the
first time in
24 hours that my face made a
movement. It wasn't pain. I
know. I answered. I hung up. Lay
down again.
And this time I managed to cry
without being angry at myself
for crying. I spent all of
Friday
outside that door. Not the whole
time. There was a chair in the
corridor, a moss-coloured velvet
armchair
one had used in years, and I sat
in it when my legs got tired of
standing. I came back to
knock when I thought she might
hear. I never left the floor.
Bastion came up twice with
office
questions and went down with
short answers. Fausto asked to
speak with me over the intercom.
I sent word that not today. I
leaned my forehead against the
door's wood near the end of the
afternoon, and spoke low without
calling her name. The wood was
cold. I let it stay that way.
I wrote that before you existed
in my life. I stopped. Before I
knew you'd exist in my life,
I stopped again. That doesn't
fix anything I know. On the
other side her silence had wait.
I could tell her silence is a
part. There was her thoughtful
silence, her wounded silence,
her sleeping silence. That was a
new silence, a silence that was
weighing on me in return.
I didn't ask to come in. I
didn't have the right. The
clause I'd written with my own
hand,
in the week I decided to buy her
from the Sarah Valls, was the
only piece of my history with
her
that she didn't know. And that's
why it was the only piece in
which she could still believe
I'd
plan to lose her from the start.
If I forced that door now, I
wouldn't be opening a door.
I'd be confirming the paragraph.
I went back to the study at
eight. I called Bastion.
You know this house. I do. Find
every copy of that contract. My
mother's Fausto's the one I
peep in the safe. The one the
registry sent to the secretary
at a never came back. All of
them.
Bring them to me. He stood still
half a second, enough to
register that I wasn't asking.
And left without a single
question. I opened the drawer of
my father's study and took out
something that had sat there for
three months. The handwritten
draft of the clause.
Yellowed paper, black ink, my
writing. I set it on the desk
and looked at it the way one
looks at
a dead animal he hadn't the
courage to bury when he should
have. There was a promise I'd
made
my own conscience three months
ago. On the morning I Orlando
had agreed to sleep at my side
without
a contract. I promised myself
I'd erase that clause one day.
I'd put it off. I'd thought I'd
have time. I'd put it off like a
man putting off a doctor with
chest pain. And now the pain had
come for her not for me. And
that was what truly hurt in the
whole story. I put the draft
under the
blotter. It wouldn't burn alone.
It would burn in front of the
person who needed to see it.
I went up again. I leaned my
forehead against the door one
last time that night. Good
night,
I'll under. On the other side, a
second. Two. And a whisper so
low I could have invented it.
Good
night. I didn't invent it. She
said it. Saturday was born gray
with a pale light striking
sideways
at the shutters and streaking
the floor with opaque bands. I
got up before the heat pressed
in.
Took a long bath, chose a light
dress, pinned my hair up with
the two hands that no longer
trembled so much. I opened the
door of the old contract room
and stepped out for the first
time in
almost 40 hours. I didn't go
looking for him. I knew that at
nine he'd be with Fausto in the
downstairs
office. I went down the opposite
side of the staircase and headed
to the winter garden where Dona
Kiarra's brameleads caught the
light through the glass and
everything seemed quieter than
the rest
of the house. Dona Kiarra
appeared with a tray before I
asked. Camo-Mail-T, a small
piece of bread
with butter, an orange peeled
into segments. She set the tray
on the wicker table. Still to
second.
Dried her hands on her apron.
She didn't look at me straight
on. He loves you dear. She said,
looking at the bromeliads. Men
like him are stupid about the
things they love. I didn't
answer.
She didn't wait for an answer
either. She went back inside. I
drank the tea slowly,
feeling the warmth of the cup in
my palms. I ate the whole piece
of bread. I ate the orange.
And as I ate, I understood
something that had taken 40
hours to reach me. If he
wouldn't tell it,
I'd go after it. I'd done this
before. Once ago I'd gone to
find the truth about a delmo
with my own hands
and the truth gave me back
everything. Maybe the truth
about that handwritten paragraph
was also
stored somewhere in the city, in
an archive, in someone's head,
in his writing on some other
paper.
Fausto probably knew. The cafe
Vecchia Roma, where everything
had begun, held the beginning.
And if there was a beginning, I
still hadn't fully understood.
It was mine. I took the phone
from my pocket and messageed
bastion, car tomorrow morning.
Early, just the two of us. He
answered
in less than a minute. Yes, he
didn't ask where to. He didn't
warn the boss. Bastion was
bastion.
I spent the rest of the morning
in the winter garden. Lutavico
didn't come looking for me.
I knew he knew I was there. On
the other side of the glass. I
knew he was waiting for a signal
for me. And I knew he wouldn't
force one. There was something
new in that silence that I'd
learned to read in the coming
days, and that something was
respect. He was letting me
choose the distance.
At the end of the afternoon I
went up again. I passed the door
of his study. The door was a
jar.
A threat of yellow light leaking
through the gap. He was sitting
at the desk. No tie.
The shirt rolled to the elbows.
A pile of folders on the right.
And a pile of folders on the
left.
As if the work had come back to
fill every hour I was away. He
was reading a sheet with an
attention that hurt to look at.
He raised his eyes and saw me.
He didn't move. He didn't smile.
Just looked. The way he looked
when he was holding something
too big to fit into a sentence.
Good night. I said, good night.
That was all. I continued down
the corridor. I went to the
suite that was hours and didn't
go in. I went to the old
contract room. I laid dressed on
the
comforter and on my belly,
staring at the white ceiling
until it stopped spinning. I
closed my eyes.
If there was anyone who'd
learned to hunt her own truth in
the past months, it was me. To
borrow, I'd begin. Chapter 3.
What his handwriting never said.
Day began cold. The way
Providence
knows how to be cold even in
summer. The light came through
the window of the old contract
room in
a hard way, without generosity.
I'd slept little. My hand stayed
open over my belly. The way it
had already become habit these
past two days. And I wondered,
in the second before waking
fully,
whether my child already knew
that his mother had made a plan
with no one for a hunt. I got
slowly. Put on dark pants, a
turtleneck, black shoes, nothing
that suggested Donna. Nothing
that
suggested bride. Just a woman
with an address in her head and
a question that would no longer
fit
inside her. Bastion waited in
the car, outside. He didn't ask
a question. He just opened the
rear door
and kept looking straight ahead
while I got in. The radio was
low, an old Italian song I knew
without remembering from where.
Cafe Vecchi Aroma, I said,
buckling the belt, then the
runnyeri office.
Then an address I'll give you
later. He nodded half a
millimeter with his head.
Started the car.
The drive to the old
neighborhood took long enough
for me to count my breaths. We
passed the
intersection where, months
before, a collector had shown up
at my apartment door with a
Manila envelope
and a face that didn't ask
permission. I was another person
that day. Or maybe I was the
same,
just not knowing yet. The dawn
called three times. Bastion
said, watching the rear view
mirror.
His voice was always the same.
Dry is dry stone. Asked where
you'd gone. And you said,
that I didn't rightly know. I
smiled for a second. It didn't
last. The cafe Vecchi Aroma sat
on a corner that time had
forgotten to renovate. Green
onning. Peeling sign. The smell
of good coffee
escaping through the door. I
went in slowly. Half a dozen
tables taken. Old men playing
cards in the
back. A white-haired woman
reading a newspaper. I sat at
the window table. The table. The
one where he'd
sat on the late afternoon of a
Thursday that now seemed to
belong to another life. His
chair was
empty across for me. And even
empty, it seemed occupied. The
waiter came slowly. He was a
thin man,
clean apron. With that look of
someone who'd worked in an old
cafe since he was 15 and would
never
stop. Coffee, please. I said. He
paused half a second. Looked at
me the way one checks a
password.
Two cubes, a drop of milk. The
question landed between us.
Quiet. I held my breath until it
heard in my chest. How do you
know? My voice came out lower
than I wanted. The waiter
shrugged
with the kind of ease you only
learned with time. Old order.
Mr. Caracciolo asked a few
months back
that if you ever came in, this
was how you were to be served.
Never came up. Today it did. He
left
before I could answer. I stayed
staring at the wood of the
table, breathing through my
mouth.
Ludovico had left a standing
order at some ordinary cafe.
Months ago. Without telling me.
Without
asking for anything in return.
Without collecting. Like a man
leaving a piece of home on every
corner of the city in case I
needed to come back. I really
wanted to be angry. Anger was
easier to carry. The coffee
came. I drank it slowly. It was
exactly the way I liked it. And
the
taste came along with a new
scar. I paid. Left. Fausto
Ranieri's office was on the
second floor
of a dark brick building. Three
blocks ahead. Bastion parked.
Stayed in the car. I went up the
stairs
alone. The wooden door had his
name and discreet gold letters.
The kind of discretion that
costs a lot.
The secretary tried to stop me.
I walked straight past. With the
politeness of someone who no
longer asks permission. Fausto
was behind the desk. Glasses at
the tip of his nose. A paper
open in front of him. He raised
his head slowly when he saw me.
He didn't seem surprised. He
seemed
tired. He knew what I could at
Chiolo. He said, Marcicano. I
corrected. Sitting in the chair
on the other side of the desk.
For now, he closed the paper
slowly. Crossed his hands. How
can I help you?
When he wrote that clause.
Fausto breathed through his
nose. Took off his glasses. Put
them in his
jacket pocket. Sinyora. I am the
family's conciliate. My job is
to advise. Not to betray. I'm
not asking
you to betray. I said without
raising my voice. I'm asking you
to tell me when. That's all. The
date.
He was silent for a while. Then
he opened the drawer beneath the
desk. Took out two bundles of
paper
tied within twine. Set the first
in front of me and untied it.
Original draft. He said,
dated. By hand. You know the
handwriting. I did. His writing
was one of those you recognize
from far off.
firm. A little old fashioned.
With the careful capitals of a
man educated by priests. The
date in the upper right corner
was a week before the day he'd
called me to the cafe for the
first time.
A week before I existed in his
life in full. He drafted it
alone. Fausto continued.
Looking at the sheet and not at
me. Locked in his father's
study. Didn't let me read it
before I
witnessed the signature. Just
called me to certify the mark. I
asked if he was sure. He didn't
answer.
Why? Fausto raised his eyes. He
had the kind of gaze a
conciliary learns. It doesn't
judge.
But it doesn't spare either. He
didn't write this to bind you.
He wrote it to be sure he could
let
you go. I gripped the edge of
the desk. The wood was cold.
Good to hold. That doesn't
excuse it.
I said, low. It doesn't excuse
it. Fausto tied the twine again.
Put it away. It only explains
it.
I stayed another minute. I had
no more questions. I stood. He
stood too in the polite way of
old men.
Signora. He said when I was
already at the door. For
whatever it's worth. He asked me
three weeks ago
to tear up that draft. I said,
I'd tear it. I didn't. I never
tear anything of the families
without a
written order. He knew I
wouldn't tear it. And he went
away satisfied all the same. I
stopped with my hand
on the knob. I didn't turn
around. I just nodded and left.
Narina's apartment was in
federal
hill. Three streets below my old
one. Bastion parked at the curb.
Leant his head against the seat.
Closed his eyes. I went up
alone. Rang the bell. She opened
wearing pajamas that must have
been
ten years old. Air pinned up
with a pencil. Glasses crooked.
Oh my God. She said,
she pulled me inside by the
elbow. You look like you saw
Christ come down off the cross.
Christ feels like too little.
She closed the door with her
foot. Took me to the couch.
Shove to pile of sheet music to
the floor. Sat beside me. The
apartment smelled of bad
coffee and old books. And I,
without meaning to, started to
cry. It wasn't a pretty cry.
It was the cry of someone who'd
held it in for two days. Narina
didn't say anything for a while.
She just ran her hand over my
back. The way her grandmother
must have run her hand over her
as a
child. Then she got up, went to
the kitchen, came back with a
mug of bad coffee and a piece of
dry orange cake. Eat. She said,
then talk. I ate. I talked. I
told her about the folder,
the claws, his handwriting, the
locked room, the cafe with the
waiter and the two cubes.
The draft in Faustos drawer. I
told all of it in the messy way
you tell your best friend,
out of order, with repetition,
with a pause to breathe. I told
her about the belly. Narina
stopped
the piece of cake fell into her
lap. She looked at me as if
seeing me for the first time in
three
days. I, Alanda, I know she
cried. Then laughed. Then cried
again. Hugged me tight enough to
hurt my
shoulder. You're not fighting
just for yourself, girl. She
said, still on my shoulder. This
changes the game.
I breathed deep inside her hug.
It really does change it. She
let me go. Wipe her face on
the
hand. That man wrote the claws
because he was scared. Fine.
Said and done. Now either he
destroys
the claws in front of his
mother-in-law, or I show up
there in person and he can deal
with it. Choose.
I laughed. It was a small laugh,
but it was a laugh. We'll see. I
said, she stood,
pulled me by the wrist. Before
anything you're going to the
doctor.
Nurt. To the doctor, Alanda. Not
tomorrow. Today. You look like
you haven't slept in three days.
And there's a little one in
there who needs a mother who's
whole. There was no arguing.
Nareena put shoes on me. Put a
person in my hand. Pushed me out
of the apartment.
Bastion lifted his head from the
seat when he saw me. Looked at
Nareena in the doorway. She came
down the stairs behind me. And
at a mug of coffee to bastion
through the car window. Take it.
It's awful.
But it's hot. Bastion accepted
it with that minimal nod of the
head. Nareena waited for me to
get in the
car. Patted the hood twice like
someone saying goodbye to a
horse. Went back up.
Bastion looked at the mug for
half a second before taking the
first sip. Miss Nareena. He
said,
low, more to himself than to me.
Has a heavy hand. With the
coffee or with life. Both. He
started the car.
The family's discreet clinic was
in a building with no sign.
Three floors above a jewelry
shop on
a quiet street. I went up in the
elevator with Bastion behind me.
A silent shadow. The doctor was
a woman
of around 50. Short gray hair. A
firm hand. She'd already treated
two generations of Karachi
Olos. She examined me carefully.
Ask questions without going
around anything. Marked
something
in a chart I didn't see. Then
she sat in the chair across from
me and crossed her hands. The
way
Fausto had crossed his hours
earlier. It must be a habit of
those who live around this
family.
Everything's fine with the
child. She said, but your blood
pressure is high. Higher than
I'd like
this stage. You need rest. You
need to sleep. And above all you
need to avoid any big shocks in
the coming
months. A big shock drops the
pressure. Dropped pressure drops
the child. I laughed awkwardly.
It was the kind of laugh that
isn't a laugh. The one that
comes out of your chest because
there's
nowhere else for it to come out.
Doctor, I said, I've had three
big shocks in the last 72 hours.
She didn't smile. She just
gripped the pen in her hand.
Then avoid the room. She gave me
vitamins.
A prescription. A sheet with
emergency numbers. Bastion paid
downstairs with an envelope that
appeared from his coat pocket as
if it had always been there. We
went back to the car. After noon
had already fallen. Home, I
said, Bastion nodded. The drive
back was long the way roads get
long
when your head is full. I looked
at the street without seeing it.
I went over everything. The
date in the corner of the draft.
Fausto's sentence. Narina's
gesture holding the piece of
cake in
her lap. The doctor gripping the
pen. And in the middle of it
all, something new. I wasn't
just
wounded anymore. I was planning.
We reached the mansion when it
was already night. Bastion
stopped
the car in the courtyard. Got
out. Open the door for me. I
climbed the three entrance steps
slowly.
The front door opened before I
touched it. Ludovico was at the
foot of the stairs. Exactly
where
he'd waited. Months ago, when
I'd tried to leave alone for the
first time and Renolfo had shown
up in the street behind the
market. The same place. The same
height. His hands at his sides.
His shoulders
straight. His mouth closed in a
line that couldn't hide that
he'd waited there for hours. I
stopped
in the middle of the hall. The
marble floor gave back the echo
of my heels. Where did you go?
He said,
it wasn't a question. It was
just his voice trying to reach
the edge of something. I
recognized
the place. I recognized the foot
of the stairs and the waiting.
And I let the recognition pass
across
my face without hiding it. After
you, I said, except you weren't
there. He closed his eyes half a
second. Open them. I'll land a.
Tomorrow will talk. I passed him
without touching. Climb the
stairs
slowly. One hand on my belly
under the coat, the other on the
railing. He didn't follow. He
stayed
where he was. The way men stay
when they've learned too late
that grabbing doesn't hold. I
lay
down in the old contract room.
The bed was still cold, but I
slept. Not much, but I slept.
It was the small hours that woke
me. A muffled sound. Downstairs.
The kind the mansion shouldn't
make at that hour. I sat up on
the bed with my eyes closed for
a second. Tuning my ear. Light
footsteps in the downstairs
corridor. A door opening slowly.
And a voice. A table. On the
phone.
Speaking Italian too fast. The
way someone does when they don't
want to be understood. I got up.
Pressed my ear to the crack of
the door frame. The mansion's
high ceilings carried sound
upward
as if designed for it. And I
caught three words in the
current of hers. Enough. Air.
Sarah Vall. I stayed there.
Pressed against the wood.
Without breathing. My hand went
back to my
belly without me telling it too.
And I understood. Without
needing another word. That the
witch
wasn't scheming alone. She'd
arranged the next step with the
enemy Ludovico thought was
contained.
I went back to bed slowly. I
didn't lie down. I sat leaning
against the headboard. I's open
in the
dark. Waiting for dawn.
Tomorrow. Ludovico was going to
hear me out tomorrow. I knew
she'd come down.
I'd been in the library since
before dawn. The way I always
had been when the house demanded
something I didn't yet know how
to give. A low fire in the half.
The coal eating itself slowly
from within. With that dry
crackle that filled the silence
without truly filling it. An
untouched
glass beside the arm of the
chair. The glass of a man who
pours out of habit and doesn't
drink.
The morning light still had that
grey tone of the small hours
that hasn't decided between
dark and day. And I waited
without waiting. My eyes fixed
on the embers. As if they might
tell me
something I still didn't have
the courage to tell myself. I
heard her step on the stairs
before I
recognized it by the weight. The
heels she wore inside the house.
Later than the ones for the
street.
A second slower than usual
because her body now carried a
secret that tired her more than
she
admitted. She came in through
the library's arch door and
stopped half a second at the
frame.
Her hand still on the wooden
frame. She was in a loose
blouse. Her pinned up. No
make-up. I'd
never seen her like this in the
morning. Even with anger written
into every muscle of her face,
she was the most alive thing in
that room full of dead books.
She looked at the empty arm
chair
beside me. Mine. She sat in it
anyway, with that deliberate
calm of someone who knows
exactly
what she's doing and wants you
to see. She crossed her legs
slowly. She held my gaze without
blinking. Explain it to me now,
she said. Without cutting
anything out. I breathed deep.
The air
was warm near the hearth and
cold on the opposite side, and I
felt both at the same time. If
there's
something I've learned about
speaking, I've learned that the
truth only fits in your mouth
when you accept losing something
by saying it. I'd accepted it
since Friday morning. When I
leaned my forehead against the
door of the room where she was
locked and admitted to the word
that the clause was mine and the
price of it was too. The first
time I wanted to tell you this
story I began was in the
kitchen. He lifted her chin half
a millimeter. She knew which
kitchen.
You'd been in the house a week,
I continued. I'd agreed with
myself that I wouldn't speak to
you in the corridors. Formal
greeting cold-look public dinner
contract, that was the
arrangement.
You cried in the small hours
alone at the counter and the
light you'd left on made me come
down.
I was going to leave without
going in. You heard me, turned
around, and fired off a sentence
I
still hear when I have nothing
to do. She stayed quiet. Her
hands rested in her lap,
with a stillness I recognized as
effort. I don't need an audience
to cry, thank you.
I repeated it without trying to
imitate her. No one had ever
spoken to me like that. Not a
man,
not a woman, not my father. In
that moment I understood two
things I didn't want to
understand.
The first, that you wouldn't fit
into the contract I'd written,
the second that I was going to
fall,
and I fell right there. That
night, with the glass of milk,
still in your hand. She pressed
the
pack of the armchair with her
fingertips. She didn't interrupt
me. The second time was in the
rain,
I continued. Coming back from
Miljira Soli, you got into the
car beside me,
wet from the shoulder up, your
hair stuck to your neck. I took
off my coat before I thought
and covered you. I was without a
coat the rest of the way the
cold coming in through the
window.
What I didn't tell you is that I
got home not trusting my own
voice. I didn't open my mouth
until the sweet door. If I'd
spoken, I'd have said something
that couldn't yet be said,
and the clause, the voice came
quiet. But with a firmness
underneath that left no room for
a
vision. When, there I closed my
eyes a second. The cold popped
softly in the hearth. I opened
them.
In the week I discovered the set
of Alice Plan, I said, before I
called you to the cafe,
I was alone in my father's
study. I'd already decided to
buy the debt. I'd already
decided to get
Delmo out of the city. I'd
already decided on the contract.
And I drafted it all by hand at
that mahogany writing desk with
the window facing the winter
garden, each line in silence.
The only sound, the scratch of
the pen on paper. She didn't
look away. The final clause I
wrote last, I continued. After
everything, Fausto wasn't there.
No one was. I wrote it because
if one day you found out who I
really was and were left with no
choice, I wanted you to be
able to leave. Without having to
ask, without having to knock on
my door asking permission to go,
with money to start over in
whatever city you wanted,
without my name on your passport
if you
preferred it that way. Silence.
A log tapped lightly against the
iron grate of the hearth.
I alander, I said, and my voice
was no longer firm. I didn't
know how to love without leaving
a door
open. Writing that clause was
the only form of love I'd
learned, building the exit for
someone
I didn't think would stay. She
breathed deep. Her chest rose
and fell in a way I noticed,
and I hated myself for noticing
so clearly. Chapter 4. The
writing on the page, the voice
in the ear.
And afterward, she said, it
wasn't a question. It was an
order. Afterward, I loved you. I
said
simply. And I put it off. I
thought I'd have time. I asked
Fausto to tear up the draft
three weeks ago.
He said he'd tear it. I knew he
wouldn't tear it because a
conciliary doesn't tear paper
without a
written order. I came away
without demanding the written
order. Because inside, I still
didn't know
if I deserved to destroy the
door. She said nothing more for
a while. The silence between us
had
its own weight and temperature.
Then she stood. She walked to
the hearth with measured steps,
as if she needed something
concrete to look at. She stood
with her back to me, facing the
coal.
Her shoulders were slightly
slumped. The way someone carries
an invisible baby,
and too heavy a truth on the
same day. The reddish light of
the embers struck her profile
and stayed
there. Quiet. Long enough for me
to realize she was using that
silence to organize something
within herself. You put it off,
she said, without turning.
That's different from lying.
It is. I said, low. But it costs
the same. She turned. Her eyes
were red. But they didn't fall.
I don't forgive you today, she
said. But I understand for today
it's what I can manage.
I stood from the armchair
slowly. I didn't approach. I
learned late, but I learned.
Thank you,
I said. She nodded half a
millimeter with her head. She
passed me without touching.
Stopped at the doorframe her
hand in the same place where
she'd stopped coming in,
as if the frame were a border
she controlled alone. There's
another thing, she said.
But I'll tell you later, not
today, she left. I stayed
looking at the fire, the glass
remained
untouched. I left the library
without running. If I ran, he'd
come after me. And I still
hadn't
decided what to do with what was
inside me in that minute. The
anger that still burned and that
other thing deeper than anger.
The one that hurt in a different
way because it had no easy name.
I walked down the corridor to
his father's old study. The wood
of the floor was cold under my
heels. The smell of Carnoboax
and old paper marking each step.
Ludovico had shown me the key
once,
months before. In the casual way
of a man saying, this door is
yours too. I'd never gone in
alone.
I went in now. The study was
darker than Ludovico's. Heavy or
wood. The thick wool rug with a
burgundy diamond pattern that
muffled any sound. The smell of
old cigar that never fully left
the
walls no matter how they opened
the window. The writing desk sat
in the middle, facing the
closed window. I went straight
to the top drawer without
hesitating. Like someone who
knows what
she came to get. It wasn't
locked. He trusted the people
living with him too much.
Inside,
among folders and sealed
envelopes, I didn't even dare
touch. An old leather notebook
with a crumpled
corner. I opened it. Loose
sheets of drafts, some with
incorrections, and others with
edges
yellowed by time. I found it
without needing to search much.
The handwriting was
unmistakable.
The same one I'd already learned
to recognize in every note and
dedication in the house.
Date in the upper right corner.
A week before the day of the
cafe. It was all there. All by
hand,
with each clause numbered and
the last one written on the back
of the sheet. Separated from the
others by a simple horizontal
line. I folded the sheet in four
with the care of someone who
knows
old paper tears. I put it in the
pocket of my dress. At my hip. I
closed the drawer slowly,
with two fingers, without a
sound. I left. In the upstairs
corridor I stopped. Otevia's
voice rose
through the stairwell, with the
clarity that only the mansion
knew how to give. The ceiling
was
extremely high in that stretch.
And the salon of the formal
sitting room sat right below my
feet.
The same room where she'd opened
the folder three days before.
With that smile of someone who'd
kept
the card up her sleeve her whole
life. The salon door was a jar,
and the sound rose through the
gap,
as if someone had planted an
acoustic pipe between the
floors. She wasn't speaking low.
She never
spoke low when she thought only
elders were listening. I leaned
my hand on the railing. The iron
cold against my palm. I didn't
crouch. I just stood. My son has
stopped listening to the family.
She was saying. Bastetalion
mixed with English. The
syllables cutting the air with
the precision of
someone who'd practiced that
speech before. He let the woman
nurse his decision. And the
three of
stakequia as if the Donna hadn't
been chosen in this room for
three generations. A male voice
answered
low. Don Vittorio by the grave
deliberate timbre. I didn't
catch the words. Don't come to
me with
a Tavia. She cut in. You signed
the original contract with me.
The clause exists. It's
legitimate.
And I'm going to enforce it.
Another answer. Also low. Also
his. It only takes one night.
Matevia said. And their her
voice changed tone. Ruth inner.
Sharper. That quality of a knife
passing
over a wetstone. One night. If
the air doesn't arrive, the
clause stops mattering. My son
becomes
mine again. And the stranger
goes back to the street she came
from. The railing went ice cold
under my fingers.
The cerevaules she continued.
Already know about the
pregnancy. I sent word
yesterday.
Renolfo accepted the job for the
price I offered. It won't be at
the mansion. It'll be on the
way out when she thinks she's
safe. And the three of you will
pretend you didn't know. And
after
word you'll pretend you're
sorry. And my son will pretend
for a month that he's lost
something
important. Then he'll go back to
being what he was. Silence. The
kind of silence three old men
make
when none want to be the first
to speak. Then one of the elders
spoke. And this time I caught
the
whole sentence. It was Don
Sisto. The youngest of the three
old men. The one with the lowest
voice.
This is an attempt against
Caratiollo blood Otevia. This is
an attempt against a bot
bride. She spat back without
pausing. Caratiollo blood is
decided in this room. I didn't
wait
for the rest. I went down the
stairs far too slowly. Gripping
the railing with both hands,
feeling the ice cold iron under
my fingers as if it were the
only solid thing in that moment.
With the hand written draft warm
in my pocket and my free hand
firm on my belly,
I crossed the service corridor,
passed the winter garden without
looking at the plants. All the
way to
the back veranda. The one where
I'd cried alone weeks before. On
the day, Lutavico had told me
the first
half of the truth. And I still
didn't know there was a second
half. I leaned my hip against
the stone
ballastrade. I breathed three
times. Deep, slow, counting the
seconds of each breath. The
doctor had
said on Monday's late afternoon
that a big shock dropped the
pressure and dropped pressure
dropped
the child. I wouldn't give the
witch that satisfaction. I
wouldn't run. I wouldn't scream.
I would tell Lutavico before
Otevia made her next move.
Before Renolfo went out into the
street
with the agreed price in his
pocket. The clause had become a
small piece of her game. The big
piece
was me, alive, walking out the
door. I couldn't let her move
first. I ran my hand over my
face.
It was steady. Good. I turned to
go back into the house, and I
saw. At the back wall,
where the garden met the narrow
street that wrapped around the
mansion, leaning against a stone
as if he'd been waiting since
the beginning of the world. A
man, light gray suit. One hand
in his pocket.
The other arm loose and
unhurried. A shark's smile I'd
seen once before. Months ago, in
the street
behind the old market, when he'd
gotten too close to Il Jira
Sole. And Lutavico had made him
a treat with a look alone.
Renolfo Saravala. He raised his
free hand. Slowly. With that
calm of someone
who has all the time in the
world and knows it. Like a man
greeting an old acquaintance in
the middle
of the street on a Sunday. He
held the gesture half a second
in the air. His eyes fixed on
mine
across the garden. Then he took
half a step back, entered the
shadow of the wall, and
vanished.
I stood there with my hand on my
belly, without moving. Counting
my breath until I reached
10, the witch wasn't waiting for
the next move. She'd already
made it. Chapter 5,
the night she chose to stay. The
blast entered my sleep before
the sound itself did. It was a
dry
crack, far off at the back wall,
and then a second one closer
against the stone of the wall.
I sat up on the bed in the old
contract room with my hand
already on my belly. As if my
body had
learned the gesture before I
did. The clock on the wall read
320 in the morning. I heard
fastened in the corridor
shouting orders at two men I
didn't know. I heard footsteps
running
up the service stairs. I heard
Donakirah calling my name from
somewhere far off. My bedroom
door
opened with a shove. Ludovico
was there in the gap, wearing
his coat over an open shirt.
I recognized the coat before I
recognized his face. It was the
same one from the rainy night,
months ago. The same heavy
fabric he'd put over my
shoulders without saying a word.
He never
knew I'd kept that detail.
Neither did I, until I saw it
there again. Get up. He said,
slowly. I got up too fast. The
dizziness came at once. A wave
of heat rising up my neck and
the room
spinning half a degree. He
caught me by the elbow before I
could hit the corner of the
nightstand.
Slowly, he repeated, lower. We
went down. In the hall,
Donakirah was crouched behind
the sofa
with Narina, who'd shown up at
the mansion without my knowing
when. Bastion was at the door.
Gun in hand. His face without a
single line more than usual. One
of the pains in the formal
sitting room had shattered on
the floor in long shards. One of
them caught my arm when I passed
too close. The cut was a graze.
Short. More shock than blood.
Ludovico saw the red line
rise on my white skin before I
felt it. We're leaving here. He
said, now. Bastion drove. I sat
in the
exit with Ludovico holding a
folded cloth against my forearm.
He pressed with the firmness of
a
man who'd done this more times
than any man should. The lights
of Providence passed by the
window
in yellow smears. No one spoke
for three kilometers. I had a
secret that could no longer
sleep in my
pocket. Ludovico. He turned his
face toward me without letting
go of the cloth. I'm pregnant.
I said, and your mother has
already sold that information.
He closed his eyes for half a
second.
That was all. No start. No
shout. No idiotic question. When
he opened his eyes,
they were those of the man the
city feared. But turned only
toward the inside of the car. I
know
what to do. Bastion took a
narrow road climbing into the
hills. I vaguely recognized the
curve.
Without knowing why. Ludovico
didn't tell me where we were
going. Nor did I ask. The house
was at
the end of a packed dirt path
surrounded by tall pines. Dark
stone facade. Windows shut for
years. Tiles covered in dry
needles. Bastion stopped the car
near the entrance and got out
first.
He stood at the door. Gun
resting on his thigh. His eyes
on the road we'd come by. It was
my
father's. Ludovico said, opening
the door for me. No one here was
ever happy. But no one knows
of this house outside of three
people. I went in. The smell of
shut up wood. Dust from more
than one
winter. A distant trace of dried
lavender in some piece of
furniture. You lit the hearth
without yet
taking off his coat. The fire
caught fast. Hungry for the old
paper he stacked beneath the
kindling. He knelt with me
before the hearth. A thick rug
cushioning our knees. From the
small
kit Bastion had thrown into the
car. He took a clean bandage, a
dark bottle, and cotton. It'll
sting.
He said, I've had worse sting.
He almost laughed. He didn't. He
ran the antiseptic over my arm
with the patience of a man who'd
been taught to kill and was
learning, right there, to heal.
His hand paused a second longer
than it needed to over the skin.
A small second. Nothing.
My chest registered it as if it
were a whole minute. I almost
believed it. I said, looking at
the fire.
These two days. I almost
believed you'd planned it all to
lose me. He didn't stop the
gesture.
He just answered in the same low
tone. I planned to lose you
because I didn't know I could
stay.
The silence after that was
thick. The hearth crackled.
Outside the wind passed through
the
pines with a sound like
breathing. He wrapped the
bandage around my arm with a
firm not on one side.
There. He said. I didn't stand.
Neither did he. He lifted his
hand from my elbow to my face.
Slowly, giving me time to pull
back if I wanted. I didn't pull
back. His thumb stopped on my
jaw.
I leaned my forehead against
his. It was the gesture we'd
invented in the bedroom corridor
months ago.
The one I'd kept is if it were a
password only hours. If I touch
you now,
you murmured. It's like
choosing. Again, good. He kissed
me as if he were apologizing and
promising at
the same time. It wasn't the
kiss of a man who thinks he's
one. It was the kiss of a man
who'd
finally stopped losing on
purpose. The heat of the hearth
struck my back. The fabric of
his coat was
rough beneath my fingers. I
smelled the fire, the antiseptic
him. I thought in a flash too
quick to
hold that I'd waited weeks to
breathe this close again. I
thought I was still afraid. I
thought the
fear now was of something else.
He laid me down on the rug
slowly. He slid his arm under
the
nape of my neck. Before letting
my weight rest on the floor. As
if my body were the most
delicate
thing he'd ever carried. His
hand moved down the side of my
hip and stopped. Open. Over the
still
invisible curve of my belly. It
stayed there. He looked at my
belly like a man looking at a
secret
that had become a promise.
Hours. He said, low, my eyes
stung. I didn't let them fall.
Mine.
I answered.
And my voice came out firmer
than I expected. In yours, he
pulled the coat off his
shoulders,
took off his shirt, and stood
there in the orange light of the
hearth with the old marks of his
life
on display. A long scar on his
left shoulder, a smaller one
near his ribs. The outline of a
small
tattoo on his chest I'd never
seen up close. I touched each of
them with my fingertips.
Slowly. Like someone reading a
story in Braille. He closed his
eyes. You tremble when I touch
you.
I said, only you. I pulled his
face to mine. This time the kiss
was deeper, slower, with a kind
of
hunger and no hurry at all. His
weight on my chest was dense and
alive. The rug beneath my back
was rough
and just the right measure. He
undid the strap of my night gown
with a patience that almost
irritated
me. Slighting the thin fabric
off my shoulders until it
exposed my breasts to the heat
of the
earth. His large hands cupped
each of them with reverence. His
thumbs tracing slow circles
around
the nipples that hardened under
his touch, pressing with enough
delicacy to draw a trembling
sigh from my lips. Ludovico.
Slowly. He answered, his mouth
at my neck. We have time now.
His
lips moved down my chest and
warm wet kisses, savoring every
inch of skin as if he wanted to
memorize
the taste. His tongue circled a
nipple, sucking it into his
mouth with a firm, steady
pressure.
While his free hand caressed the
other breast, squeezing and
releasing in sync, my body
arched involuntarily against
him. My hands buried in his dark
hair, pulling him closer. He
switched
sides, giving the same attention
to the other breast. His teeth
grazing the sensitive skin
lightly,
sending waves of intense
pleasure spreading through my
belly. My hands explored the
firm muscles
of his back, moving down to the
waistband of his pants. He let
me undress him completely,
revealing the member already
rigid and pulsing. The skin hot
and smooth under my fingers.
I caressed him slowly, feeling
the thickness, the vein that
throbbed at my touch, moving up
and
down in long passionate strokes.
He groaned low against my skin,
the sound vibrating in my chest.
He moved lower, kissing the
curve of my belly with infinite
tenderness. His hands parting my
legs
gently. His mouth found the wet,
hot center between my thighs.
His tongue tracing slow,
precise lines along the swollen
folds, circling the sensitive
point at the top with
dedication.
He sucked softly. Then with more
intensity, alternating broad
licks and circular movements
that made me tremble. Two of his
fingers entered me slowly,
curving to reach the inner
point that made me clench around
them. While his mouth never
stopped devouring me with tender
hunger.
I pulled him up, turning our
bodies on the soft rug until he
lay on his back. I mounted him.
My body facing his, and took his
member in my hand before
bringing it to my mouth. My lips
wrapped around the swollen head,
sliding down slowly, tasting the
salty clean flavor of him.
My tongue swirled around the
thick length as I rose and fell.
One hand massaging the base and
the
exbloring his firm thighs. He
groaned. His hands holding my
hips and pulled my sex back to
his mouth,
returning it with the same
intensity. Our mouths worked in
unison. The reciprocal oral sex
turning the air into muffled
size and horse groans. His
tongue penetrated deeper into me
while I
sucked him with devotion. His
hips moving subtly to meet the
rhythm of my lips. The pleasure
was mutual, electric. Each
caress of his tongue sending
shocks that made me suck harder
around his
pulsing member. The heat rose in
spirals inside us, but he turned
me carefully, positioning me
beneath
him again. His eyes met mine.
Full of desire and protection.
He went slowly. He was
meticulous.
He was a man who knew that one
wrong pressure could hurt a
wounded arm and a secret inside
me.
And he chose each movement, like
a man choosing a word that can't
be taken back. His breathing
slowed near my ear when he
finally positioned himself. He
raised himself on his arms to
distribute
his own weight. And I saw the
effort in the muscles of his
shoulders. The deliberate care.
He
fit into me in one long,
restrained movement. His eyes on
mine the whole time. I held my
breath.
He stopped right after. forehead
pressed to mine. Waiting for my
body to remember him. His
member filled me completely,
stretching the inner walls with
a delicious warm pressure. Each
inch
entering slowly until our bodies
were joined entirely. Stay with
me. You whispered. I'm here.
The rhythm came slowly. Deep. He
kept one hand flat on my belly,
protecting what was inside
without stopping the way he
moved me. His other hand tangled
in the nape of my neck. I heard
the
hearth. He heard the wind in the
pines. He heard his breath
breaking against my cheek. He
heard the
low sound coming from my own
throat that I didn't recognize
his mind. Each thrust was
deliberate.
His hips pulling back almost
completely before advancing
again. His member sliding in and
out with
perfect friction that grazed
every sensitive point. His
testicles struck softly against
me with
each deep thrust. The rhythm
gradually building as sweat
glistened on his skin in the
firelight.
I thought, between one movement
and another, that this man had
written a clause to let me
leave.
I thought that now he was
building with his own body, the
reason for me never to leave.
The heat rose. His sentences
grew shorter. Mine became only
his name.
Ludovico. Here. Ludovico. I'm
here. He sped up slightly
without
losing his focus.
And each movement began to hit a
spot that made me arch my hip
against his. My fingers sank
into his back.
I felt the heat of the hearth
and the heat of him confused.
Indistinguishable. One single
thing.
He murmured something in Italian
into my hair that I didn't
understand and didn't need to
the tone was clear. His member
swelled even more inside me. The
deep rhythmic thrusts
carrying me to the edge of the
abyss. My body clenched around
him. The inner muscles pulsing.
And the intense pleasure
exploded in powerful waves. A
strong orgasm that made me
scream his name
as spasms of ecstasy ran through
every nerve. He followed right
after. His body tensing in one
last deep movement. His member
pulsing as the warm release
surged inside me in intense
bursts,
filling me completely. A horse
sound escaped his throat against
my neck. We stayed like that
a long time. His hand went back
to my belly. It stayed open
there. Quiet. I put my hand over
his hand.
I closed my eyes and let the
rest of the fear drain away. I
thought, with a remnant of me
that
hadn't yet surrendered
everything. Whether that had
been a real choice or just the
relief of
still being alive after the
blast. I found no answer. I
found his gesture. His hand over
my belly.
His breathing slowing. It was
answer enough for today. I fell
asleep there on the rug, with
his
coat over the two of us. I woke
before her in the house in the
hills. The fire had died to
embers. The morning light came
through the cracks in the window
in grey bands. I land a slept
with
her hand over mine. My hand
still on her belly. I stayed
looking at her face for a time I
didn't measure.
There was a decision I'd put off
for three months that would stop
being postponable the moment she
opened her eyes. I'd written
that clause alone in my father's
study, a week before sitting at
the
cafe Vecca Roma across from her.
I wrote it because I didn't
believe a woman could stay with
me for
anything other than fear or
debt. I wrote it because I
wanted to leave an exit door
open for her.
I wrote it because the only love
I'd learned to give was
permission to leave. I spent
three
whole months knowing that she'd
still existed. I put off
destroying it. I thought I'd
have time.
I thought erasing it later would
count the same as never having
written it. It didn't. As long
as that clause was in the world,
I would keep being the man who'd
needed it, and not the man who
chose her. She deserved the
second. The first had cost her
two days locked in a room she
thought was
her place once again. I ran my
finger over her shoulder, very
slowly without waking her.
You're going to be Donna. The
way one is named, I said. So low
that only the fire heard.
She nod the way one is bought. I
opened the door carefully so as
not to wake her.
Vastian was outside, gun on his
thigh, eyes on the road. He
turned his face when he heard
me.
Go back to the mansion, I said.
Gather all the elders and my
mother in the main room tonight.
Fausto witnesses. You witness.
Say it's from my own hand.
Vastian looked inside.
At the rug. At her. And back at
me. He nodded half a degree,
left. I stayed there until she
woke.
When she opened her eyes and
looked at me, I knew I'd never
write another door again.
We stayed in the house in the
hills the rest of Friday. I
slept twice more.
Eight what Bastion brought from
the car. Let Ludovico tend the
dressing on my arm one more
time.
He spent the afternoon on the
phone with Fausto, arranging the
following night.
We went back to the mansion at
the start of Saturday evening.
I had the handwritten draft in
the pocket of my dress. I gave
it back to him before going into
the
main room. Neither of us said
anything about it. It was agreed
without words. The main room was
full.
Don Vittorio, Don Emiliano, and
Don Cisto seated in the high
chairs at the back.
Octavia and a sidearm chair,
spine straight, hands crossed
over her lap.
With the same polite contempt of
the first day I set foot in that
house.
Fausto standing near the hearth,
Bastion leaning against the wall
by the door.
I came in without taking
Ludovico's coat off my
shoulders. He'd covered me again
in the car, without saying
anything, and I hadn't given it
back.
I pulled my part of the contract
from my pocket. The copy
Donacira had brought back to me
in the
old room on the first day of
morning. I tore it in two in
front of them. I didn't shout.
I let the pieces fall on the
rug. I'm not leaving with any
fortune, I said.
Nor with any child under my arm,
I'm staying, not for the door,
for the house.
Vitavia opened her mouth, closed
it. I stared at her without
blinking.
Ludovico took a step forward. He
took the handwritten draft from
the inner pocket of his jacket.
He looked at his mother first,
then each of the three elders.
The clause was mine. He said.
The power it gave me over her
was mine. Now it belongs to no
one. He held the sheet out
toward the
earth. The paper caught fire at
the edge with an almost
impatient haste, as if it too
had waited too
long. He held it until the last
safe instant, then let go. The
ashes fell over the stones of
the
heart. He turned to me, not to
them. You are my equal of my
family. The Donah of the
Karachio Lose.
Don Amelia no, the eldest, was
the first to move his head. Half
a degree. It was only half a
degree.
But it was him. Don Vittorio
followed. Don Cisto last, with
an almost imperceptible delay.
Latvia didn't move at all. She
stayed where she was. Hand still
crossed.
Looking at her son the way one
looks at a polite stranger.
Latvia had lost. And she knew
it.
Ludovico took my hand on the way
out of the room. He pulled me
into the corridor, away from the
eyes.
And only then let out the air
he'd been holding the whole
time. And the Sarah Valls, I
asked
he raised my hand to his mouth.
Pressed his lips to my wrist.
And looked at me over my own
hand.
Tomorrow I deal with the Sarah
Valls. Today I'm your chapter
six. Beneath flowers. And after
his weeping.
Bastion stood near the window of
the breakfast room with the
newspaper folded under his arm
and his usual
face, which meant something had
happened. I learned that early.
When his face had no expression
at all,
it was because he was holding
one. Two days had passed since
the night of the elders.
The mansion breathed the
different air. When I was still
learning to recognize, Dona
Kiara
served coffee with her chin
higher. The corridors, which had
always seemed too empty.
Now had people who greeted me by
the name the family had
reluctantly accepted. And there
was a
small but real difference in the
way that greeting arrived. Less
ceremony, more person.
Ludovico raised his eyes from
the newspaper. Providence? He
asked. Boston.
Bastion answered. South dock.
Renolfo Saravale. Found this
morning with problems.
Problems of what order? The
order that doesn't ask for a
second visit, sir. Ludovico
turned his
eyes back to the newspaper as if
Bastion had commented on the
weather. He turned the page with
a calm,
I no longer found cold. I found
it deliberate. There was a
difference. I picked up my cup
with both hands.
felt the warmth enter my fingers
and asked nothing more. Someone
in Providence would no longer
send word with dead flowers.
That was all I needed to know.
The rest I left with him.
Nareena appeared in the doorway
carrying a white box wrapped in
green ribbon.
Cake. She announced. In that way
she had of turning every
entrance into an act.
Before anyone asks why. Bastion
got up and pulled a chair for
her. Without a word.
Without taking his eyes off the
window. Nareena looked at the
chair.
Looked at him. Sat. Arranging
the boxes ribbon on the table as
if she'd seen nothing.
You know that stone face turned
out kind of handsome after the
coffee. She said,
loud enough for Donna Kiarra to
hear from the kitchen. Bastion
coughed into a hand.
Change the subject by asking
Donna Kiarra for another plate.
I filed it away somewhere inside
me.
The chair pulled out and the
evirted look and the cough that
wasn't a cough. And I didn't
comment.
There were stories that weren't
mine yet. Seven weeks later, the
garden was covered in flowers.
I didn't wear a veil. I chose a
simple dress, cut at the waist,
no train and no adornment I'd
need to carry.
The bouquet was of chameleas.
The same ones I'd been watering
since the start of that spring
and pot scattered along the
corridor window. A small routine
that had become mine without my
noticing the exact moment.
Nareena had helped me tie the
white ribbon around the stems
the night before.
Crying while she laughed at
herself, which was exactly her
way of being happy for someone.
I walked to the altar alone.
There was no one to give me
away. And even if there had
been,
I wouldn't have accepted. No one
gives away a woman who has
already given herself.
The morning sun came in slanted
between the rows of chairs. And
the shadows of the rose stems
on the arch fell in long streaks
over the stone path. I heard my
own footsteps. They were the
only ones.
Ludovico waited beneath the arch
with his father's old watch on
his wrist and his arms at his
sides.
Not crossed, hiding nothing
behind them. He was in a dark
suit. No tie. When he saw me
arrive, he swallowed.
I saw the movement in his
throat. I also saw the effort he
made not to let more than that
show.
And I saw that the effort wasn't
enough. Nareena cried,
prettyly, seated in the front
row, with Donna Kiarra's hand
over hers. Donna Kiarra cried in
an ugly
way, an embroidered handkerchief
pressed to her nose. Her
shoulders shaking in generous
silence.
Bastion was in a tie as few
times as I'd ever seen him. A
dark gray tie, meticulously
nodded.
The only sign that that morning
was different from all the
others. Nareena turned to the
nearest
person and said it loud enough
to reach the altar. If he
blinked twice in a row, she
said,
it's a smile. Bastion blinked
twice in a row, without turning
his face. I saw it.
Atavia was in the front row on
the right side, in a dark blue
wool dress, and the bearing of
someone who came because she
needed to be seen. She was
invited. She accepted out of
politics.
I didn't look at her once, and
when the priest began to speak,
I realized I also wouldn't need
to. The priest said short
things. Ludovico said his vow so
low that the chameleas barely
heard it,
but I heard it. He said he'd
learned, too late, that love
isn't guaranteed with a clause,
that he'd spend the rest of his
life without writing any exit
door for me. That if one day I
wanted to leave, it would have
to be me walking, because he'd
no longer build the exit with
his own hands.
I said my vow looking at him. I
chose to stay. I'll keep
choosing every day. He kissed me
with
no contract between us. No door.
With the morning sun on my back
in the smell of Camilla in the
air,
and his hands on both sides of
my face, as if I were the only
stable thing in a world he'd
spent his whole life trying to
control. Winter came heavy in
Providence. Enrico was born on a
late January dawn, with snow
falling outside the window and
thick quiet pieces. No wind, as
if time
had decided to be gentle at that
hour. Labor was long. Ludovico
didn't leave the room once. He
held my hand through every
contraction. His forehead
pressed to mine. murmuring
things in
Italian that I'd begun to
understand because of how much
he murmured near me in hours
without witnesses.
Outside, Narina waited with
Donna Kiarra, and an absurd
basket with enough sandwiches to
feed a whole battalion, because
that was her way of enduring the
weight. Bastion stood in the
corridor
with the gun hidden under his
jacket, protecting something
that had no enemy that dawn.
Enrico came
into the world with a strong
cry. The size the family had
waited for over three
generations.
The obstetrician placed him on
my chest first. He stopped
crying almost at once,
as if he recognized the place. I
stayed looking at him. That tiny
piece of a person with wet
black lashes and hands closed
into small fists, and I found no
word sufficient for what I felt.
I didn't try. Ludovico took him
afterward. He held his son in
his arms with both hands open.
The small body lost in his large
arms, and stayed motionless for
a few seconds just looking.
And that was when he wept. He
didn't hide it. He didn't turn
his face. He didn't run his hand
over his eyes as if wiping away
something else. He wept looking
at his son. His chin trembling
and the tears running down the
line of his jaw without him
making any gesture to stop them.
With a stillness that was only
his, and that I'd never seen in
any of the faces he used in the
nose. He said low to me when he
found his voice. Poor thing. I
answered. He laughed in the
middle
of the weeping. He leaned his
forehead against mine. That
gesture that had become our
private language.
Then he leaned his forehead
against in Riko's too, closing
the triangle among the three of
us.
And we stayed like that for a
time I couldn't measure. In
Riko, he said, you were right.
I'd suggested the name weeks
before. On an ordinary night
while we waited for the snow to
stop outside.
And Riko, in honor of his
brother, the one who died at 19
in a story he told me only once.
Slowly, without a dormant.
Lutaviko had looked at me for a
long time when I said it.
Without saying yes or no, as if
he needed to carry the name a
little before giving his answer.
Only now, with his son and his
arms and the weeping he didn't
hide, was he saying yes.
Six months after the birth, the
morning in the suite was one of
the calmest the mansion had ever
seen.
And Riko slept in the crib in
the room next door. And the
monitor beside my side of the
bed,
purred with his breathing. That
sound that had become the
soundtrack of my small hours.
The June light came through the
cracks and the shutters and wide
warm bands.
Lutaviko came in carrying a tray
with two cups, bear foot, no
jacket, in the previous day's
shirt.
He sat on the edge of the bed
and handed me mine. Two sugar
cubes, a drop of milk.
I laughed softly. The way one
laughs at an old joke that keeps
working out of love for what it
means.
Do you remember? I asked. That I
told you once months ago, my
mother's dream. He already knew
which question it was. I saw it
in the way he held his own cup.
Unhurried. He let me finish
anyway.
A library I continued. In
federal hill, free books for the
neighborhood children.
She never had money to put a
book in my hand that wasn't
borrowed from the school or from
someone
who owed a favor. I bought the
building three months ago. He
answered, looking at his cup.
The work began last Monday. I
didn't tell you because I wanted
it to be a surprise when the
sign went up. It was going up
next week. I stayed quiet. The
band of sun crossed the sheet
slowly.
The sign. I asked softly. What's
it going to say? Marcecano
Community Library. Your mother's
maiden name.
You told me one dinner night and
passing. The way one tells
something without expecting
anyone to keep it.
I kept it. I set the cup on the
nightstand before I could spill
the coffee over the sheet.
I leaned my forehead against
his. We stayed like that a good
while,
without either of us finding a
word worth more than the
silence. In Rico woke shortly
after.
I nursed him. Changed him.
Handed him to Ludovico so he
could make the baby laugh with
that stone
face that no longer fooled
anyone. At the end of the
morning we went down to the
winter garden.
I took in Rico in my arm so he
could see the chameleas. The
same ones that had become my
bouquet.
And that I still watered now
with him on my hip, showing him
the flowers as if he knew what
they were.
Maybe he did. Ludovico sat
beside me on the stone bench
with the coffee he'd brought
down from upstairs.
Still warm. The June sun came
through the glass panes at a low
angle, warming the stone without
burning.
Do you remember the morning? He
said in a low tone. When I
received an envelope and put it
in the drawer,
I remembered at once. The
morning after the night
everything had shifted sides. On
the other side
of months, and of all that came
after. The old envelope sealed
with the crest of the lion with
the broken
crown. He'd put it away unopened
in front of me and hugged me too
tight for an ordinary Saturday
morning.
I remember. I answered. You
hugged me too tight for it to be
nothing. He ran his hand slowly
over
Rico's hair, who slept against
my shoulder with his mouth
slightly open. It really was
nothing.
Just the beginning. I stayed
looking at him. The winter
garden was in a good silence.
The kind
that asks for no filling. In
Rico breathe deep against my
neck. Ludovico's hand was open
over mine
between the two bodies in the
middle of the stone bench,
without grip, without weight.
Just there.
I thought of the islanda who'd
waited at the altar of the
church and providence in a white
dress
with a bell-tolling 12 times to
say what the whole city already
knew. She was another person.
She was me, but she was another
person. The one who didn't yet
know that humiliation can be the
first
step of a path worth walking.
Ludovico raised my hand and
kissed my wrist. Slowly, without
announcement.
In Rico let out a small sigh on
my shoulder. Outside, the white
chameleas swayed lightly with
the wind
coming through the gap in the
garden door. The butt wife of
Providence had a price. No one,
not even he knew it was this, to
stay.