Chapter 1. The morning before the folder.
I  woke  before  her  like  always.  The  thin  July  light
slipped  through  the  half  open  curtain,
and  fell  in  a  slanted  stripe  across  Islander's  bear  shoulder.
I  stayed  still,
propped  on  my  elbow,  watching  her  face  as  she  slept.
A  mouth  slightly  potted.  Her  dark  hair
spread  across  the  pillow  on  my  side  of  the  bed.  One  hand
curled  near  her  chin  like  a  child's.
The  air  conditioner  hummed  low  almost  imperceptible,  and
there  was  a  scent  of  jasmine  coming
from  the  window.  She'd  insisted  on  planting  jasmine  on
the  balcony,  and  I'd  let  it  happen
without  arguing,  which  said  a  lot  about  what  she'd  done  to
me.  There  was  a  time  when  I  couldn't
sleep  in  that  suite.  Now  it  was  the  opposite.  I
couldn't  leave  it  without  first  making  sure  she  was
still  there.  I  admitted  inwardly,  something  I
still  felt  embarrassed  to  say  out  loud.  I  was  happy.
The  words  sounded  strange  in  my  head.  Almost  indecent  for
a  man  like  me.  Happy.  I  got  up  slowly,
pulled  the  sheet  over  her  shoulder  so  the  AC  wouldn't  hit  her
skin  directly,
and went down barefoot. The cold marble of the staircase under my feet was the same as always,
but even that seemed different on the mornings she was upstairs. The mansions kitchen at that hour was
mine alone. Donakyara was still in the back garden cutting rosemary. I could hear from far off the
sound of her scissors against the thick stems. The dogs slept piled up near the service door.
My father's old clock kept the slow rhythm of 620. I grabbed the coffee tin,
measured it into the mocha pot the way I landed her taught me without realizing she was teaching.
Two sugar cubes, a drop of milk, never two. Bastion came in through the service door with his
planner under his arm, and stopped talking before he even started. He looked at me, looked at the
cup in my hand, looked back at me. Good morning, he said dry. Good morning, he said the planner on
counter, with the ceremony of a man delivering an official document. O second of silence. Two ticks of
the clock. Should I build a household for the dawn becoming a barista? I didn't answer. The corner
of my mouth betrayed half an intention of a smile, and I corrected it before he noticed. He noticed.
Pretended not to. That's how he'd worked for ten years. What's on the schedule?
Fausto asked for half an hour this afternoon. The elders sent word about the dock, and Donak
Tavia. He paused, chose the word, requested a family meeting at noon. Formal sitting room.
I looked at him. Did she request a meeting or announce one?
Announced. I filed the information in the place where I store the things I haven't yet decided
what to do with. My mother had come back from Naples two weeks earlier than planned without
warning and without explanation, and I'd expected her to arrive with her temper sharpened,
with a list of grievances, with that silence of hers that cuts deeper than any shout.
I hadn't expected her to request the formal room. The formal room was for weddings, funerals,
and contract executions. By mother knew very well what each setting said before a single word was spoken.
Teller will be there. I'll ander and I. Bastion nodded. Brief. Anything else? I raised the cup.
Take this up before it gets cold. Set it beside the bed. Don't say anything. She hates being
and she's not talking to her. She's not talking to her. She's not talking to her.
She's not talking to her. She's not talking to her. She's not talking to her.
She's  not  talking  to  her.  She's  not  talking  to  her.  She's  not
talking
to  her.
The flash from the neighborhood papers photographer had caught her face at the exact moment
the bell told for the last time and none of the guests knew how to look at her properly. I did.
I saw in the photo the exact moment her face understood that Adelma wasn't coming
and I saw that she decided right there that she wouldn't cry in front of those people.
That day I decided two things and I'm still keeping both to get her out of the trap.
The Sarah Valls had set for her and to never tell her that I'd seen her cry in a white dress.
I heard light footsteps on the stairs. The fourth step always creaked and the sound reached me with
the punctuality of an agreed upon signal. I came back to the present. I left the kitchen,
crossed the high ceiling to corridor and passed through the hall to the garden. She'd be by the
chamelears. She was always by the chamelears before eight said it was the hour when the flower is breathed.
She was, in a long night gown, hair pinned at the nape, watering can in her hands.
The morning still had that damp July light that makes everything seem slightly unreal
and she moved among the plants with the ease of someone born there. Though I knew that three
months ago she barely knew the chamelears name. I came up behind her without a sound and kissed her
neck right where I'd learned she shivers slightly. She shivered. You shouldn't do that when I'm
you. If you soak the chamelears and me along with them, I won't be offended. She laughed
softly and turned her face until she tucked her chin against my shoulder. Her hair smelled of rosemary,
probably because of Donna Kiyara, who insisted on leaving dried sprigs in every room of the house
as if that were protection enough against anything. Your mother is up to something.
My mother is always up to something. No. Today, she's up to something. I looked at her profile
against the morning light. She'd learned to read the house the way one reads the Bible,
word by word skipping nothing. If she said my mother was up to something, my mother was up to
something. Formal sitting room noon, I said, we go together. Together, it was just one word,
and it landed there like a signature at the bottom. I took the watering can from her hand,
set it on the ground and pulled her to me by the waist. Beneath the cotton of the night gown,
there was a small secret only the two of us knew, and I could count on my fingers the people
outside that house who also knew. Iolanda, me, the doctor, Donna Kiyara suspected, but Donna Kiyara
suspects everything and is rarely wrong. Do we tell them today? She asked against my chest.
My mother, your mother, I thought a second. After the meeting, we'll read the room. She agreed
without speaking. I felt her hair against my mouth and decided that this was the last morning
I'd put anything off. After lunch, I'd tell Fausto to pull the old contract out of the draw
and destroy it with me in front of me at my signature. There was a clause in it that I'd written
with my own hand in another life, and I'd carried the postponement of that clause, the way a man
carries a small stone in his shoe, not annoying enough to make him stop, but always hurting.
Today I was taking out the stone. Come, I said, eat something before you face the matriarch.
She laughed again. She laughed more since she'd been mine. I'd learned to listen to her laugh the
way one learns a language he never cared to learn and ended up in love with its sound. We went inside,
and the garden door closed behind us with the soft sound of old wood settling into its frame.
Four hours until noon, a whole lifetime until noon. The formal sitting room was the only room in
mansion where I'd never felt whole. Sealing too high, mahogany shelves with books no one read,
two sofas of dried blood-colored velvet, and a rug so pale it felt cruel to step on.
The air in there had that specific smell of a shut up room you only open on occasion.
Moth balls mixed with old varnish, and something floral trying to mask the other two.
Butavia liked that room because the room made an impression. That's why she chose it.
She sat with her back to the window, and the noon light came in behind her, and turned her into a
dark silhouette against the gold, a staging choice, the choice of someone who knows how to stage.
Bousto stood behind her, leaning against the shelves. His head lowered in a way I'd never seen in
the conceliary. Don Vittorio, Don Emilliano, and Don Sisto stood. The three of them with that old
bearing of men who'd learned to stand for hours at wakes for friends they themselves had ordered
killed. I came in hand in hand with Ludovico. I felt his finger squeeze mine for half a second,
almost involuntary, and let go. He read the room before I did. Mother, son, Otevia moved her head
a centimeter in my direction. Ealanda, I sat on the sofa across from them, him at my side. I crossed
my hands over my knee. There was a dark leather folder on the little table between us, and the folder
was closed, and the folder had the crest of the lion with the broken crown blind embossed on the
cover. My stomach sank half an inch. I recognized that crest. It was the same as the letter that
had arrived months ago. On a night when I still didn't understand much of what I was living.
The one Ludovico had put in the drawer without explanation. Otevia opened the folder with the
slowness of someone who knows no one will interrupt. She took out a sheet. Just one. Before my son
carries you twice. She said, without looking at me yet, I thought it better you know the whole
contract. She pushed the sheet with two fingers to my edge of the table. I didn't move. Ludovico
moved half a second to late. I felt his hand hesitate on my knee and settle there. I looked at the
sheet. It was paper yellowed at the edges. Family letterhead. My signature at the bottom. That shaky
signature I'd learned to make at the registry office months ago with my head spinning from hunger
and humiliation. And above my signature, in the third clause at the bottom, there was a paragraph
written by hand, by hand, not typed, by hand. In the writing I knew from notes in the corners of
library books, from messages left at my bedroom door in the first month, from the dedication he'd
written in a pavice novel and pretended hadn't been him. I read it once. On the day the air is born,
the marriage is dissolved. The wife leaves with a fortune corresponding to half the dawn's
net worth, alone. Without the child, full custody remains with the Karachiolo family. I read it again.
The words didn't change. I raised my eyes to his profile. He was looking at the sheet, not at me,
at the sheet, and his mouth opened, and his mouth closed. He didn't say no. The tavia smiled without
smiling. Keep your word son. It's written in your own hand. I heard my own name sound inside my head
as if called from far away. Iolanda. Iolanda, listen. That writing is his. That paragraph was him.
That paragraph had been there the whole time. Beneath everything, while I learned his coffee,
while he pulled the sheet over my shoulder, while we stood in the garden with our hands inside
each others as if that were real. He finally turned to me. His eyes were the exact color of the
Himelia garden. And in that color, there was now a terror I'd never seen on his face, not in the
small hours of the library, not on the night of the attack in the street. Iolanda. No. I stood.
My legs answered. It was the mornings only luck. I smoothed my skirt with both hands as if that
mattered. And I looked at the three elders, one by one, and then atotavia. And lastly, very lightly,
at Ludovico. You two fit together. I said, the both of you. My voice didn't shake.
To this day I don't know how. I walked out of the room, though everything in me wanted to run.
My heels struck the marble of the hall as if they belonged to another woman, and the other woman
climbed  the  stairs  far  too  slowly.  One  step,  two,  three.  And  on  the  13th
I  had  to  put  my  hand  on  the
palm. I focused on that. Only on that. In the bedroom corridor, I didn't go to the sweet I'd
been sharing with him for three months. I went to the door at the end. The door I hadn't opened
since we'd decided to sleep together. The white paint around the knob was slightly faded.
I'd noticed that detail on the first day, and completely forgotten it afterward. The old contract room.
I turned the knob. The air inside was still warm, with the smell of old wood, and the dust that
gathers in places no one enters anymore. The bed made as on the day I'd left. The lamp on the
night stand with its bulb off. The straw chair and the corner where I'd sat on the night of the storm
thinking that was the worst that would ever happen to me. I closed the door behind me, and the click of
the latch sounded loud through the whole house. I sat on the edge of the bed. The mattress was cold.
I laid my hand flat over the belly no one yet new existed, and for the first time in three months,
I said quietly, to no one, and to him, we're going to be okay. It was the first lie I told my child,
chapter two, the closed door and the man outside. The afternoon fell over the old contract room
without me moving from the edge of the bed. I watched the sunlight cross the floor in a long rectangle.
Shrink,  stretch,  shrink,  vanish,  the  room  turned  blue,  then  gray,  then
black.  I  didn't  turn  on  the
light. There was a sound I'd learned to ignore over the past months. The sound of the house itself
breathing, pipes, wood expanding. Donna kiaa's distant footsteps in the pantry. I listened to all of
it with a new attention, like someone arriving at a place for the first time. The smell of cold wax
on the floor. The creek of a window at the end of the corridor. The whole house sounding like a
living organism that didn't know I was falling apart inside it. Maybe it was the first time.
I started doing something I didn't want to do and did anyway. I started rereading the last few
months backward, each gesture of his, and fitting them into the shape of that handwritten paragraph.
The coffee, two cubes, a drop of milk. He'd noted it on the first day.
Adbastion noted, kept the order alive in the mansion's kitchen and at the cafe vekiae Roma.
I thought it was the small tenderness of a man who doesn't know how to say the big things,
and what if it was just care of an investment? A man tens his cattle with the same constancy,
but the same cold, calculated attention, no affection, only foresight. The coat over my shoulders on the
rainy night. I'd kept that coat at the back of the closet in the first week. The way one keeps a relic.
The dark, heavy fabric, with his scent mixed with the wet cold of the street,
and what if it had been the calculation of a man who knows an elegant gesture buys cheap loyalty?
The small hours of the library. Him broken in the armchair. The untouched glass.
Talk about his dead brother. And what if every sentence of that had been rehearsed to soften a woman
who still thought she was merchandise? And the handwritten paragraph proved she was?
I listened to that voice until I almost believed it. Then, I listened to another. The newer voice.
The one three months old. The one saying I wasn't an idiot. I'm not an idiot. I'd seen his face in
that room and I saw terror. Not a game. I saw a man who didn't know what to do with his own hands while
his mother slid the paper across the table. I stayed between the two voices until my mouth was too
dry to talk to myself. He knocked on the door for the first time near nine at night. Three short
knocks his way without pleading. I, Alanda, I didn't answer. I'm not coming in. I just want to know
if you've eaten. I didn't answer. He stayed there. I heard his breathing on the other side of the wood.
Held back, controlled. The way he controlled everything. Except the things that truly mattered.
I heard him let out the air like a man giving up on a sentence before saying it. I heard the
footsteps drawing away far too slowly. As if he wanted to give me time to change my mind,
I slept dressed on top of the comforter. I dreamed of the church in Providence. In the dream,
the bell wouldn't stop tolling. I woke with the sun on my face and my body heavy. I got up,
went to the adjoining bathroom, washed my face with cold water until my cheeks stung. In the mirror
I looked at the woman with swollen eyes and didn't recognize her at first glance. Second glance I did.
It was still me, just more tired. He knocked twice on Friday. In the morning,
in the voice of a man who decided not to impose. In the afternoon, in a horse or voice,
as if the hours had scraped something loose inside. Both times he said the same thing. I'm here.
Both times I didn't open. Donna Kira came up with a train near noon. She didn't knock.
She left the tray on the floor against the door with a note under the plate. I waited for
her footsteps to fade and opened the door the smallest crack. I pulled the tray inside.
Soup, bread, a pair. The note had three words in her round motherly hand. Eat for the little one.
She knew. Of course she knew. Donna Kira knew everything in that house. I ate the whole bowl of
soup without tasting it. I ate the bread. I ate the pair down to the core. It was the first thing I did for
the little one. And the second thing I did for myself. In Arena called near five, I answered because it was
her. Are you alive? I am. Are you eating? Now I am. You want me to come over? I thought a second.
The idea of having someone in the room felt too big to bear. Like a strong light in an eye used to the
dark. Not today. Tomorrow. Tomorrow I'll say. She was silent long enough for me to know. She was thinking
about not hanging up. And then she said her thing. If you need wine and a butter knife,
you know where I live. I laughed. It was half-laf, half-sob, but it was. It was the first time in
24 hours that my face made a movement. It wasn't pain. I know. I answered. I hung up. Lay down again.
And this time I managed to cry without being angry at myself for crying. I spent all of Friday
outside that door. Not the whole time. There was a chair in the corridor, a moss-coloured velvet armchair
one had used in years, and I sat in it when my legs got tired of standing. I came back to
knock when I thought she might hear. I never left the floor. Bastion came up twice with office
questions and went down with short answers. Fausto asked to speak with me over the intercom.
I sent word that not today. I leaned my forehead against the door's wood near the end of the
afternoon, and spoke low without calling her name. The wood was cold. I let it stay that way.
I wrote that before you existed in my life. I stopped. Before I knew you'd exist in my life,
I stopped again. That doesn't fix anything I know. On the other side her silence had wait.
I could tell her silence is a part. There was her thoughtful silence, her wounded silence,
her sleeping silence. That was a new silence, a silence that was weighing on me in return.
I didn't ask to come in. I didn't have the right. The clause I'd written with my own hand,
in the week I decided to buy her from the Sarah Valls, was the only piece of my history with her
that she didn't know. And that's why it was the only piece in which she could still believe I'd
plan to lose her from the start. If I forced that door now, I wouldn't be opening a door.
I'd be confirming the paragraph. I went back to the study at eight. I called Bastion.
You know this house. I do. Find every copy of that contract. My mother's Fausto's the one I
peep in the safe. The one the registry sent to the secretary at a never came back. All of them.
Bring them to me. He stood still half a second, enough to register that I wasn't asking.
And left without a single question. I opened the drawer of my father's study and took out
something that had sat there for three months. The handwritten draft of the clause.
Yellowed paper, black ink, my writing. I set it on the desk and looked at it the way one looks at
a dead animal he hadn't the courage to bury when he should have. There was a promise I'd made
my own conscience three months ago. On the morning I Orlando had agreed to sleep at my side without
a contract. I promised myself I'd erase that clause one day. I'd put it off. I'd thought I'd
have time. I'd put it off like a man putting off a doctor with chest pain. And now the pain had
come for her not for me. And that was what truly hurt in the whole story. I put the draft under the
blotter. It wouldn't burn alone. It would burn in front of the person who needed to see it.
I went up again. I leaned my forehead against the door one last time that night. Good night,
I'll under. On the other side, a second. Two. And a whisper so low I could have invented it. Good
night. I didn't invent it. She said it. Saturday was born gray with a pale light striking sideways
at the shutters and streaking the floor with opaque bands. I got up before the heat pressed in.
Took a long bath, chose a light dress, pinned my hair up with the two hands that no longer
trembled so much. I opened the door of the old contract room and stepped out for the first time in
almost 40 hours. I didn't go looking for him. I knew that at nine he'd be with Fausto in the downstairs
office. I went down the opposite side of the staircase and headed to the winter garden where Dona
Kiarra's brameleads caught the light through the glass and everything seemed quieter than the rest
of the house. Dona Kiarra appeared with a tray before I asked. Camo-Mail-T, a small piece of bread
with butter, an orange peeled into segments. She set the tray on the wicker table. Still to second.
Dried her hands on her apron. She didn't look at me straight on. He loves you dear. She said,
looking at the bromeliads. Men like him are stupid about the things they love. I didn't answer.
She didn't wait for an answer either. She went back inside. I drank the tea slowly,
feeling the warmth of the cup in my palms. I ate the whole piece of bread. I ate the orange.
And as I ate, I understood something that had taken 40 hours to reach me. If he wouldn't tell it,
I'd go after it. I'd done this before. Once ago I'd gone to find the truth about a delmo with my own hands
and the truth gave me back everything. Maybe the truth about that handwritten paragraph was also
stored somewhere in the city, in an archive, in someone's head, in his writing on some other paper.
Fausto probably knew. The cafe Vecchia Roma, where everything had begun, held the beginning.
And if there was a beginning, I still hadn't fully understood. It was mine. I took the phone
from my pocket and messageed bastion, car tomorrow morning. Early, just the two of us. He answered
in less than a minute. Yes, he didn't ask where to. He didn't warn the boss. Bastion was bastion.
I spent the rest of the morning in the winter garden. Lutavico didn't come looking for me.
I knew he knew I was there. On the other side of the glass. I knew he was waiting for a signal
for me. And I knew he wouldn't force one. There was something new in that silence that I'd
learned to read in the coming days, and that something was respect. He was letting me choose the distance.
At the end of the afternoon I went up again. I passed the door of his study. The door was a jar.
A threat of yellow light leaking through the gap. He was sitting at the desk. No tie.
The shirt rolled to the elbows. A pile of folders on the right. And a pile of folders on the left.
As if the work had come back to fill every hour I was away. He was reading a sheet with an
attention that hurt to look at. He raised his eyes and saw me. He didn't move. He didn't smile.
Just looked. The way he looked when he was holding something too big to fit into a sentence.
Good night. I said, good night. That was all. I continued down the corridor. I went to the
suite that was hours and didn't go in. I went to the old contract room. I laid dressed on the
comforter and on my belly, staring at the white ceiling until it stopped spinning. I closed my eyes.
If there was anyone who'd learned to hunt her own truth in the past months, it was me. To
borrow, I'd begin. Chapter 3. What his handwriting never said. Day began cold. The way Providence
knows how to be cold even in summer. The light came through the window of the old contract room in
a hard way, without generosity. I'd slept little. My hand stayed open over my belly. The way it
had already become habit these past two days. And I wondered, in the second before waking fully,
whether my child already knew that his mother had made a plan with no one for a hunt. I got
slowly. Put on dark pants, a turtleneck, black shoes, nothing that suggested Donna. Nothing that
suggested bride. Just a woman with an address in her head and a question that would no longer fit
inside her. Bastion waited in the car, outside. He didn't ask a question. He just opened the rear door
and kept looking straight ahead while I got in. The radio was low, an old Italian song I knew
without remembering from where. Cafe Vecchi Aroma, I said, buckling the belt, then the runnyeri office.
Then an address I'll give you later. He nodded half a millimeter with his head. Started the car.
The drive to the old neighborhood took long enough for me to count my breaths. We passed the
intersection where, months before, a collector had shown up at my apartment door with a Manila envelope
and a face that didn't ask permission. I was another person that day. Or maybe I was the same,
just not knowing yet. The dawn called three times. Bastion said, watching the rear view mirror.
His voice was always the same. Dry is dry stone. Asked where you'd gone. And you said,
that I didn't rightly know. I smiled for a second. It didn't last. The cafe Vecchi Aroma sat
on a corner that time had forgotten to renovate. Green onning. Peeling sign. The smell of good coffee
escaping through the door. I went in slowly. Half a dozen tables taken. Old men playing cards in the
back. A white-haired woman reading a newspaper. I sat at the window table. The table. The one where he'd
sat on the late afternoon of a Thursday that now seemed to belong to another life. His chair was
empty across for me. And even empty, it seemed occupied. The waiter came slowly. He was a thin man,
clean apron. With that look of someone who'd worked in an old cafe since he was 15 and would never
stop. Coffee, please. I said. He paused half a second. Looked at me the way one checks a password.
Two cubes, a drop of milk. The question landed between us. Quiet. I held my breath until it
heard in my chest. How do you know? My voice came out lower than I wanted. The waiter shrugged
with the kind of ease you only learned with time. Old order. Mr. Caracciolo asked a few months back
that if you ever came in, this was how you were to be served. Never came up. Today it did. He left
before I could answer. I stayed staring at the wood of the table, breathing through my mouth.
Ludovico had left a standing order at some ordinary cafe. Months ago. Without telling me. Without
asking for anything in return. Without collecting. Like a man leaving a piece of home on every
corner of the city in case I needed to come back. I really wanted to be angry. Anger was
easier to carry. The coffee came. I drank it slowly. It was exactly the way I liked it. And the
taste came along with a new scar. I paid. Left. Fausto Ranieri's office was on the second floor
of a dark brick building. Three blocks ahead. Bastion parked. Stayed in the car. I went up the stairs
alone. The wooden door had his name and discreet gold letters. The kind of discretion that costs a lot.
The secretary tried to stop me. I walked straight past. With the politeness of someone who no
longer asks permission. Fausto was behind the desk. Glasses at the tip of his nose. A paper
open in front of him. He raised his head slowly when he saw me. He didn't seem surprised. He seemed
tired. He knew what I could at Chiolo. He said, Marcicano. I corrected. Sitting in the chair
on the other side of the desk. For now, he closed the paper slowly. Crossed his hands. How can I help you?
When he wrote that clause. Fausto breathed through his nose. Took off his glasses. Put them in his
jacket pocket. Sinyora. I am the family's conciliate. My job is to advise. Not to betray. I'm not asking
you to betray. I said without raising my voice. I'm asking you to tell me when. That's all. The date.
He was silent for a while. Then he opened the drawer beneath the desk. Took out two bundles of paper
tied within twine. Set the first in front of me and untied it. Original draft. He said,
dated. By hand. You know the handwriting. I did. His writing was one of those you recognize from far off.
firm. A little old fashioned. With the careful capitals of a man educated by priests. The
date in the upper right corner was a week before the day he'd called me to the cafe for the first time.
A week before I existed in his life in full. He drafted it alone. Fausto continued.
Looking at the sheet and not at me. Locked in his father's study. Didn't let me read it before I
witnessed the signature. Just called me to certify the mark. I asked if he was sure. He didn't answer.
Why? Fausto raised his eyes. He had the kind of gaze a conciliary learns. It doesn't judge.
But it doesn't spare either. He didn't write this to bind you. He wrote it to be sure he could let
you go. I gripped the edge of the desk. The wood was cold. Good to hold. That doesn't excuse it.
I said, low. It doesn't excuse it. Fausto tied the twine again. Put it away. It only explains it.
I stayed another minute. I had no more questions. I stood. He stood too in the polite way of old men.
Signora. He said when I was already at the door. For whatever it's worth. He asked me three weeks ago
to tear up that draft. I said, I'd tear it. I didn't. I never tear anything of the families without a
written order. He knew I wouldn't tear it. And he went away satisfied all the same. I stopped with my hand
on the knob. I didn't turn around. I just nodded and left. Narina's apartment was in federal
hill. Three streets below my old one. Bastion parked at the curb. Leant his head against the seat.
Closed his eyes. I went up alone. Rang the bell. She opened wearing pajamas that must have been
ten years old. Air pinned up with a pencil. Glasses crooked. Oh my God. She said,
she pulled me inside by the elbow. You look like you saw Christ come down off the cross.
Christ feels like too little. She closed the door with her foot. Took me to the couch.
Shove to pile of sheet music to the floor. Sat beside me. The apartment smelled of bad
coffee and old books. And I, without meaning to, started to cry. It wasn't a pretty cry.
It was the cry of someone who'd held it in for two days. Narina didn't say anything for a while.
She just ran her hand over my back. The way her grandmother must have run her hand over her as a
child. Then she got up, went to the kitchen, came back with a mug of bad coffee and a piece of
dry orange cake. Eat. She said, then talk. I ate. I talked. I told her about the folder,
the claws, his handwriting, the locked room, the cafe with the waiter and the two cubes.
The draft in Faustos drawer. I told all of it in the messy way you tell your best friend,
out of order, with repetition, with a pause to breathe. I told her about the belly. Narina stopped
the piece of cake fell into her lap. She looked at me as if seeing me for the first time in three
days. I, Alanda, I know she cried. Then laughed. Then cried again. Hugged me tight enough to hurt my
shoulder. You're not fighting just for yourself, girl. She said, still on my shoulder. This changes the game.
I  breathed  deep  inside  her  hug.  It  really  does  change  it.  She  let  me  go.  Wipe  her  face  on
the
hand. That man wrote the claws because he was scared. Fine. Said and done. Now either he destroys
the claws in front of his mother-in-law, or I show up there in person and he can deal with it. Choose.
I laughed. It was a small laugh, but it was a laugh. We'll see. I said, she stood,
pulled me by the wrist. Before anything you're going to the doctor.
Nurt. To the doctor, Alanda. Not tomorrow. Today. You look like you haven't slept in three days.
And there's a little one in there who needs a mother who's whole. There was no arguing.
Nareena put shoes on me. Put a person in my hand. Pushed me out of the apartment.
Bastion lifted his head from the seat when he saw me. Looked at Nareena in the doorway. She came
down the stairs behind me. And at a mug of coffee to bastion through the car window. Take it. It's awful.
But it's hot. Bastion accepted it with that minimal nod of the head. Nareena waited for me to get in the
car. Patted the hood twice like someone saying goodbye to a horse. Went back up.
Bastion looked at the mug for half a second before taking the first sip. Miss Nareena. He said,
low, more to himself than to me. Has a heavy hand. With the coffee or with life. Both. He started the car.
The family's discreet clinic was in a building with no sign. Three floors above a jewelry shop on
a quiet street. I went up in the elevator with Bastion behind me. A silent shadow. The doctor was a woman
of around 50. Short gray hair. A firm hand. She'd already treated two generations of Karachi
Olos. She examined me carefully. Ask questions without going around anything. Marked something
in a chart I didn't see. Then she sat in the chair across from me and crossed her hands. The way
Fausto had crossed his hours earlier. It must be a habit of those who live around this family.
Everything's fine with the child. She said, but your blood pressure is high. Higher than I'd like
this stage. You need rest. You need to sleep. And above all you need to avoid any big shocks in the coming
months. A big shock drops the pressure. Dropped pressure drops the child. I laughed awkwardly.
It was the kind of laugh that isn't a laugh. The one that comes out of your chest because there's
nowhere else for it to come out. Doctor, I said, I've had three big shocks in the last 72 hours.
She didn't smile. She just gripped the pen in her hand. Then avoid the room. She gave me vitamins.
A prescription. A sheet with emergency numbers. Bastion paid downstairs with an envelope that
appeared from his coat pocket as if it had always been there. We went back to the car. After noon
had already fallen. Home, I said, Bastion nodded. The drive back was long the way roads get long
when your head is full. I looked at the street without seeing it. I went over everything. The
date in the corner of the draft. Fausto's sentence. Narina's gesture holding the piece of cake in
her lap. The doctor gripping the pen. And in the middle of it all, something new. I wasn't just
wounded anymore. I was planning. We reached the mansion when it was already night. Bastion stopped
the car in the courtyard. Got out. Open the door for me. I climbed the three entrance steps slowly.
The front door opened before I touched it. Ludovico was at the foot of the stairs. Exactly where
he'd waited. Months ago, when I'd tried to leave alone for the first time and Renolfo had shown
up in the street behind the market. The same place. The same height. His hands at his sides. His shoulders
straight. His mouth closed in a line that couldn't hide that he'd waited there for hours. I stopped
in the middle of the hall. The marble floor gave back the echo of my heels. Where did you go? He said,
it wasn't a question. It was just his voice trying to reach the edge of something. I recognized
the place. I recognized the foot of the stairs and the waiting. And I let the recognition pass across
my face without hiding it. After you, I said, except you weren't there. He closed his eyes half a
second. Open them. I'll land a. Tomorrow will talk. I passed him without touching. Climb the stairs
slowly. One hand on my belly under the coat, the other on the railing. He didn't follow. He stayed
where he was. The way men stay when they've learned too late that grabbing doesn't hold. I lay
down in the old contract room. The bed was still cold, but I slept. Not much, but I slept.
It was the small hours that woke me. A muffled sound. Downstairs. The kind the mansion shouldn't
make at that hour. I sat up on the bed with my eyes closed for a second. Tuning my ear. Light
footsteps in the downstairs corridor. A door opening slowly. And a voice. A table. On the phone.
Speaking Italian too fast. The way someone does when they don't want to be understood. I got up.
Pressed my ear to the crack of the door frame. The mansion's high ceilings carried sound upward
as if designed for it. And I caught three words in the current of hers. Enough. Air.
Sarah Vall. I stayed there. Pressed against the wood. Without breathing. My hand went back to my
belly without me telling it too. And I understood. Without needing another word. That the witch
wasn't scheming alone. She'd arranged the next step with the enemy Ludovico thought was contained.
I went back to bed slowly. I didn't lie down. I sat leaning against the headboard. I's open in the
dark. Waiting for dawn. Tomorrow. Ludovico was going to hear me out tomorrow. I knew she'd come down.
I'd been in the library since before dawn. The way I always had been when the house demanded
something I didn't yet know how to give. A low fire in the half. The coal eating itself slowly
from within. With that dry crackle that filled the silence without truly filling it. An untouched
glass beside the arm of the chair. The glass of a man who pours out of habit and doesn't drink.
The morning light still had that grey tone of the small hours that hasn't decided between
dark and day. And I waited without waiting. My eyes fixed on the embers. As if they might tell me
something I still didn't have the courage to tell myself. I heard her step on the stairs before I
recognized it by the weight. The heels she wore inside the house. Later than the ones for the street.
A second slower than usual because her body now carried a secret that tired her more than she
admitted. She came in through the library's arch door and stopped half a second at the frame.
Her hand still on the wooden frame. She was in a loose blouse. Her pinned up. No make-up. I'd
never seen her like this in the morning. Even with anger written into every muscle of her face,
she was the most alive thing in that room full of dead books. She looked at the empty arm chair
beside me. Mine. She sat in it anyway, with that deliberate calm of someone who knows exactly
what she's doing and wants you to see. She crossed her legs slowly. She held my gaze without
blinking. Explain it to me now, she said. Without cutting anything out. I breathed deep. The air
was warm near the hearth and cold on the opposite side, and I felt both at the same time. If there's
something I've learned about speaking, I've learned that the truth only fits in your mouth
when you accept losing something by saying it. I'd accepted it since Friday morning. When I
leaned my forehead against the door of the room where she was locked and admitted to the word
that the clause was mine and the price of it was too. The first time I wanted to tell you this
story I began was in the kitchen. He lifted her chin half a millimeter. She knew which kitchen.
You'd been in the house a week, I continued. I'd agreed with myself that I wouldn't speak to
you in the corridors. Formal greeting cold-look public dinner contract, that was the arrangement.
You cried in the small hours alone at the counter and the light you'd left on made me come down.
I was going to leave without going in. You heard me, turned around, and fired off a sentence I
still hear when I have nothing to do. She stayed quiet. Her hands rested in her lap,
with a stillness I recognized as effort. I don't need an audience to cry, thank you.
I repeated it without trying to imitate her. No one had ever spoken to me like that. Not a man,
not a woman, not my father. In that moment I understood two things I didn't want to understand.
The first, that you wouldn't fit into the contract I'd written, the second that I was going to fall,
and I fell right there. That night, with the glass of milk, still in your hand. She pressed the
pack of the armchair with her fingertips. She didn't interrupt me. The second time was in the rain,
I continued. Coming back from Miljira Soli, you got into the car beside me,
wet from the shoulder up, your hair stuck to your neck. I took off my coat before I thought
and covered you. I was without a coat the rest of the way the cold coming in through the window.
What I didn't tell you is that I got home not trusting my own voice. I didn't open my mouth
until the sweet door. If I'd spoken, I'd have said something that couldn't yet be said,
and the clause, the voice came quiet. But with a firmness underneath that left no room for a
vision. When, there I closed my eyes a second. The cold popped softly in the hearth. I opened them.
In the week I discovered the set of Alice Plan, I said, before I called you to the cafe,
I was alone in my father's study. I'd already decided to buy the debt. I'd already decided to get
Delmo out of the city. I'd already decided on the contract. And I drafted it all by hand at
that mahogany writing desk with the window facing the winter garden, each line in silence.
The only sound, the scratch of the pen on paper. She didn't look away. The final clause I
wrote last, I continued. After everything, Fausto wasn't there. No one was. I wrote it because
if one day you found out who I really was and were left with no choice, I wanted you to be
able to leave. Without having to ask, without having to knock on my door asking permission to go,
with money to start over in whatever city you wanted, without my name on your passport if you
preferred it that way. Silence. A log tapped lightly against the iron grate of the hearth.
I alander, I said, and my voice was no longer firm. I didn't know how to love without leaving a door
open. Writing that clause was the only form of love I'd learned, building the exit for someone
I didn't think would stay. She breathed deep. Her chest rose and fell in a way I noticed,
and I hated myself for noticing so clearly. Chapter 4. The writing on the page, the voice in the ear.
And afterward, she said, it wasn't a question. It was an order. Afterward, I loved you. I said
simply. And I put it off. I thought I'd have time. I asked Fausto to tear up the draft three weeks ago.
He said he'd tear it. I knew he wouldn't tear it because a conciliary doesn't tear paper without a
written order. I came away without demanding the written order. Because inside, I still didn't know
if I deserved to destroy the door. She said nothing more for a while. The silence between us had
its own weight and temperature. Then she stood. She walked to the hearth with measured steps,
as if she needed something concrete to look at. She stood with her back to me, facing the coal.
Her shoulders were slightly slumped. The way someone carries an invisible baby,
and too heavy a truth on the same day. The reddish light of the embers struck her profile and stayed
there. Quiet. Long enough for me to realize she was using that silence to organize something
within herself. You put it off, she said, without turning. That's different from lying.
It is. I said, low. But it costs the same. She turned. Her eyes were red. But they didn't fall.
I don't forgive you today, she said. But I understand for today it's what I can manage.
I stood from the armchair slowly. I didn't approach. I learned late, but I learned. Thank you,
I said. She nodded half a millimeter with her head. She passed me without touching.
Stopped at the doorframe her hand in the same place where she'd stopped coming in,
as if the frame were a border she controlled alone. There's another thing, she said.
But I'll tell you later, not today, she left. I stayed looking at the fire, the glass remained
untouched. I left the library without running. If I ran, he'd come after me. And I still hadn't
decided what to do with what was inside me in that minute. The anger that still burned and that
other thing deeper than anger. The one that hurt in a different way because it had no easy name.
I walked down the corridor to his father's old study. The wood of the floor was cold under my
heels. The smell of Carnoboax and old paper marking each step. Ludovico had shown me the key once,
months before. In the casual way of a man saying, this door is yours too. I'd never gone in alone.
I went in now. The study was darker than Ludovico's. Heavy or wood. The thick wool rug with a
burgundy diamond pattern that muffled any sound. The smell of old cigar that never fully left the
walls no matter how they opened the window. The writing desk sat in the middle, facing the
closed window. I went straight to the top drawer without hesitating. Like someone who knows what
she came to get. It wasn't locked. He trusted the people living with him too much. Inside,
among folders and sealed envelopes, I didn't even dare touch. An old leather notebook with a crumpled
corner. I opened it. Loose sheets of drafts, some with incorrections, and others with edges
yellowed by time. I found it without needing to search much. The handwriting was unmistakable.
The same one I'd already learned to recognize in every note and dedication in the house.
Date in the upper right corner. A week before the day of the cafe. It was all there. All by hand,
with each clause numbered and the last one written on the back of the sheet. Separated from the
others by a simple horizontal line. I folded the sheet in four with the care of someone who knows
old paper tears. I put it in the pocket of my dress. At my hip. I closed the drawer slowly,
with two fingers, without a sound. I left. In the upstairs corridor I stopped. Otevia's voice rose
through the stairwell, with the clarity that only the mansion knew how to give. The ceiling was
extremely high in that stretch. And the salon of the formal sitting room sat right below my feet.
The same room where she'd opened the folder three days before. With that smile of someone who'd kept
the card up her sleeve her whole life. The salon door was a jar, and the sound rose through the gap,
as if someone had planted an acoustic pipe between the floors. She wasn't speaking low. She never
spoke low when she thought only elders were listening. I leaned my hand on the railing. The iron
cold against my palm. I didn't crouch. I just stood. My son has stopped listening to the family.
She was saying. Bastetalion mixed with English. The syllables cutting the air with the precision of
someone who'd practiced that speech before. He let the woman nurse his decision. And the three of
stakequia as if the Donna hadn't been chosen in this room for three generations. A male voice answered
low. Don Vittorio by the grave deliberate timbre. I didn't catch the words. Don't come to me with
a Tavia. She cut in. You signed the original contract with me. The clause exists. It's legitimate.
And I'm going to enforce it. Another answer. Also low. Also his. It only takes one night.
Matevia said. And their her voice changed tone. Ruth inner. Sharper. That quality of a knife passing
over a wetstone. One night. If the air doesn't arrive, the clause stops mattering. My son becomes
mine again. And the stranger goes back to the street she came from. The railing went ice cold under my fingers.
The cerevaules she continued. Already know about the pregnancy. I sent word yesterday.
Renolfo accepted the job for the price I offered. It won't be at the mansion. It'll be on the
way out when she thinks she's safe. And the three of you will pretend you didn't know. And after
word you'll pretend you're sorry. And my son will pretend for a month that he's lost something
important. Then he'll go back to being what he was. Silence. The kind of silence three old men make
when none want to be the first to speak. Then one of the elders spoke. And this time I caught the
whole sentence. It was Don Sisto. The youngest of the three old men. The one with the lowest voice.
This is an attempt against Caratiollo blood Otevia. This is an attempt against a bot
bride. She spat back without pausing. Caratiollo blood is decided in this room. I didn't wait
for the rest. I went down the stairs far too slowly. Gripping the railing with both hands,
feeling the ice cold iron under my fingers as if it were the only solid thing in that moment.
With the hand written draft warm in my pocket and my free hand firm on my belly,
I crossed the service corridor, passed the winter garden without looking at the plants. All the way to
the back veranda. The one where I'd cried alone weeks before. On the day, Lutavico had told me the first
half of the truth. And I still didn't know there was a second half. I leaned my hip against the stone
ballastrade. I breathed three times. Deep, slow, counting the seconds of each breath. The doctor had
said on Monday's late afternoon that a big shock dropped the pressure and dropped pressure dropped
the child. I wouldn't give the witch that satisfaction. I wouldn't run. I wouldn't scream.
I would tell Lutavico before Otevia made her next move. Before Renolfo went out into the street
with the agreed price in his pocket. The clause had become a small piece of her game. The big piece
was me, alive, walking out the door. I couldn't let her move first. I ran my hand over my face.
It was steady. Good. I turned to go back into the house, and I saw. At the back wall,
where the garden met the narrow street that wrapped around the mansion, leaning against a stone
as if he'd been waiting since the beginning of the world. A man, light gray suit. One hand in his pocket.
The other arm loose and unhurried. A shark's smile I'd seen once before. Months ago, in the street
behind the old market, when he'd gotten too close to Il Jira Sole. And Lutavico had made him
a treat with a look alone. Renolfo Saravala. He raised his free hand. Slowly. With that calm of someone
who has all the time in the world and knows it. Like a man greeting an old acquaintance in the middle
of the street on a Sunday. He held the gesture half a second in the air. His eyes fixed on mine
across the garden. Then he took half a step back, entered the shadow of the wall, and vanished.
I stood there with my hand on my belly, without moving. Counting my breath until I reached
10, the witch wasn't waiting for the next move. She'd already made it. Chapter 5,
the night she chose to stay. The blast entered my sleep before the sound itself did. It was a dry
crack, far off at the back wall, and then a second one closer against the stone of the wall.
I sat up on the bed in the old contract room with my hand already on my belly. As if my body had
learned the gesture before I did. The clock on the wall read 320 in the morning. I heard
fastened in the corridor shouting orders at two men I didn't know. I heard footsteps running
up the service stairs. I heard Donakirah calling my name from somewhere far off. My bedroom door
opened with a shove. Ludovico was there in the gap, wearing his coat over an open shirt.
I recognized the coat before I recognized his face. It was the same one from the rainy night,
months ago. The same heavy fabric he'd put over my shoulders without saying a word. He never
knew I'd kept that detail. Neither did I, until I saw it there again. Get up. He said,
slowly. I got up too fast. The dizziness came at once. A wave of heat rising up my neck and the room
spinning half a degree. He caught me by the elbow before I could hit the corner of the nightstand.
Slowly, he repeated, lower. We went down. In the hall, Donakirah was crouched behind the sofa
with Narina, who'd shown up at the mansion without my knowing when. Bastion was at the door.
Gun in hand. His face without a single line more than usual. One of the pains in the formal
sitting room had shattered on the floor in long shards. One of them caught my arm when I passed
too close. The cut was a graze. Short. More shock than blood. Ludovico saw the red line
rise on my white skin before I felt it. We're leaving here. He said, now. Bastion drove. I sat in the
exit with Ludovico holding a folded cloth against my forearm. He pressed with the firmness of a
man who'd done this more times than any man should. The lights of Providence passed by the window
in yellow smears. No one spoke for three kilometers. I had a secret that could no longer sleep in my
pocket. Ludovico. He turned his face toward me without letting go of the cloth. I'm pregnant.
I said, and your mother has already sold that information. He closed his eyes for half a second.
That was all. No start. No shout. No idiotic question. When he opened his eyes,
they were those of the man the city feared. But turned only toward the inside of the car. I know
what to do. Bastion took a narrow road climbing into the hills. I vaguely recognized the curve.
Without knowing why. Ludovico didn't tell me where we were going. Nor did I ask. The house was at
the end of a packed dirt path surrounded by tall pines. Dark stone facade. Windows shut for
years. Tiles covered in dry needles. Bastion stopped the car near the entrance and got out first.
He stood at the door. Gun resting on his thigh. His eyes on the road we'd come by. It was my
father's. Ludovico said, opening the door for me. No one here was ever happy. But no one knows
of this house outside of three people. I went in. The smell of shut up wood. Dust from more than one
winter. A distant trace of dried lavender in some piece of furniture. You lit the hearth without yet
taking off his coat. The fire caught fast. Hungry for the old paper he stacked beneath the
kindling. He knelt with me before the hearth. A thick rug cushioning our knees. From the small
kit Bastion had thrown into the car. He took a clean bandage, a dark bottle, and cotton. It'll sting.
He said, I've had worse sting. He almost laughed. He didn't. He ran the antiseptic over my arm
with the patience of a man who'd been taught to kill and was learning, right there, to heal.
His hand paused a second longer than it needed to over the skin. A small second. Nothing.
My chest registered it as if it were a whole minute. I almost believed it. I said, looking at the fire.
These two days. I almost believed you'd planned it all to lose me. He didn't stop the gesture.
He just answered in the same low tone. I planned to lose you because I didn't know I could stay.
The silence after that was thick. The hearth crackled. Outside the wind passed through the
pines with a sound like breathing. He wrapped the bandage around my arm with a firm not on one side.
There. He said. I didn't stand. Neither did he. He lifted his hand from my elbow to my face.
Slowly, giving me time to pull back if I wanted. I didn't pull back. His thumb stopped on my jaw.
I leaned my forehead against his. It was the gesture we'd invented in the bedroom corridor months ago.
The one I'd kept is if it were a password only hours. If I touch you now,
you murmured. It's like choosing. Again, good. He kissed me as if he were apologizing and promising at
the same time. It wasn't the kiss of a man who thinks he's one. It was the kiss of a man who'd
finally stopped losing on purpose. The heat of the hearth struck my back. The fabric of his coat was
rough beneath my fingers. I smelled the fire, the antiseptic him. I thought in a flash too quick to
hold that I'd waited weeks to breathe this close again. I thought I was still afraid. I thought the
fear now was of something else. He laid me down on the rug slowly. He slid his arm under the
nape of my neck. Before letting my weight rest on the floor. As if my body were the most delicate
thing he'd ever carried. His hand moved down the side of my hip and stopped. Open. Over the still
invisible curve of my belly. It stayed there. He looked at my belly like a man looking at a secret
that  had  become  a  promise.  Hours.  He  said,  low,  my  eyes  stung.  I  didn't  let  them  fall.  Mine.
I  answered.
And my voice came out firmer than I expected. In yours, he pulled the coat off his shoulders,
took off his shirt, and stood there in the orange light of the hearth with the old marks of his life
on display. A long scar on his left shoulder, a smaller one near his ribs. The outline of a small
tattoo on his chest I'd never seen up close. I touched each of them with my fingertips.
Slowly. Like someone reading a story in Braille. He closed his eyes. You tremble when I touch you.
I said, only you. I pulled his face to mine. This time the kiss was deeper, slower, with a kind of
hunger and no hurry at all. His weight on my chest was dense and alive. The rug beneath my back was rough
and just the right measure. He undid the strap of my night gown with a patience that almost irritated
me. Slighting the thin fabric off my shoulders until it exposed my breasts to the heat of the
earth. His large hands cupped each of them with reverence. His thumbs tracing slow circles around
the nipples that hardened under his touch, pressing with enough delicacy to draw a trembling
sigh from my lips. Ludovico. Slowly. He answered, his mouth at my neck. We have time now. His
lips moved down my chest and warm wet kisses, savoring every inch of skin as if he wanted to memorize
the taste. His tongue circled a nipple, sucking it into his mouth with a firm, steady pressure.
While his free hand caressed the other breast, squeezing and releasing in sync, my body
arched involuntarily against him. My hands buried in his dark hair, pulling him closer. He switched
sides, giving the same attention to the other breast. His teeth grazing the sensitive skin lightly,
sending waves of intense pleasure spreading through my belly. My hands explored the firm muscles
of his back, moving down to the waistband of his pants. He let me undress him completely,
revealing the member already rigid and pulsing. The skin hot and smooth under my fingers.
I caressed him slowly, feeling the thickness, the vein that throbbed at my touch, moving up and
down in long passionate strokes. He groaned low against my skin, the sound vibrating in my chest.
He moved lower, kissing the curve of my belly with infinite tenderness. His hands parting my legs
gently. His mouth found the wet, hot center between my thighs. His tongue tracing slow,
precise lines along the swollen folds, circling the sensitive point at the top with dedication.
He sucked softly. Then with more intensity, alternating broad licks and circular movements
that made me tremble. Two of his fingers entered me slowly, curving to reach the inner
point that made me clench around them. While his mouth never stopped devouring me with tender hunger.
I pulled him up, turning our bodies on the soft rug until he lay on his back. I mounted him.
My body facing his, and took his member in my hand before bringing it to my mouth. My lips
wrapped around the swollen head, sliding down slowly, tasting the salty clean flavor of him.
My tongue swirled around the thick length as I rose and fell. One hand massaging the base and the
exbloring his firm thighs. He groaned. His hands holding my hips and pulled my sex back to his mouth,
returning it with the same intensity. Our mouths worked in unison. The reciprocal oral sex
turning the air into muffled size and horse groans. His tongue penetrated deeper into me while I
sucked him with devotion. His hips moving subtly to meet the rhythm of my lips. The pleasure
was mutual, electric. Each caress of his tongue sending shocks that made me suck harder around his
pulsing member. The heat rose in spirals inside us, but he turned me carefully, positioning me beneath
him again. His eyes met mine. Full of desire and protection. He went slowly. He was meticulous.
He was a man who knew that one wrong pressure could hurt a wounded arm and a secret inside me.
And he chose each movement, like a man choosing a word that can't be taken back. His breathing
slowed near my ear when he finally positioned himself. He raised himself on his arms to distribute
his own weight. And I saw the effort in the muscles of his shoulders. The deliberate care. He
fit into me in one long, restrained movement. His eyes on mine the whole time. I held my breath.
He stopped right after. forehead pressed to mine. Waiting for my body to remember him. His
member filled me completely, stretching the inner walls with a delicious warm pressure. Each inch
entering slowly until our bodies were joined entirely. Stay with me. You whispered. I'm here.
The rhythm came slowly. Deep. He kept one hand flat on my belly, protecting what was inside
without stopping the way he moved me. His other hand tangled in the nape of my neck. I heard the
hearth. He heard the wind in the pines. He heard his breath breaking against my cheek. He heard the
low sound coming from my own throat that I didn't recognize his mind. Each thrust was deliberate.
His hips pulling back almost completely before advancing again. His member sliding in and out with
perfect friction that grazed every sensitive point. His testicles struck softly against me with
each deep thrust. The rhythm gradually building as sweat glistened on his skin in the firelight.
I thought, between one movement and another, that this man had written a clause to let me leave.
I thought that now he was building with his own body, the reason for me never to leave.
The heat rose. His sentences grew shorter. Mine became only his name.
Ludovico.  Here.  Ludovico.  I'm  here.  He  sped  up  slightly  without
losing  his  focus.
And each movement began to hit a spot that made me arch my hip against his. My fingers sank into his back.
I felt the heat of the hearth and the heat of him confused. Indistinguishable. One single thing.
He murmured something in Italian into my hair that I didn't understand and didn't need to
the tone was clear. His member swelled even more inside me. The deep rhythmic thrusts
carrying me to the edge of the abyss. My body clenched around him. The inner muscles pulsing.
And the intense pleasure exploded in powerful waves. A strong orgasm that made me scream his name
as spasms of ecstasy ran through every nerve. He followed right after. His body tensing in one
last deep movement. His member pulsing as the warm release surged inside me in intense bursts,
filling me completely. A horse sound escaped his throat against my neck. We stayed like that
a long time. His hand went back to my belly. It stayed open there. Quiet. I put my hand over his hand.
I closed my eyes and let the rest of the fear drain away. I thought, with a remnant of me that
hadn't yet surrendered everything. Whether that had been a real choice or just the relief of
still being alive after the blast. I found no answer. I found his gesture. His hand over my belly.
His breathing slowing. It was answer enough for today. I fell asleep there on the rug, with his
coat over the two of us. I woke before her in the house in the hills. The fire had died to
embers. The morning light came through the cracks in the window in grey bands. I land a slept with
her hand over mine. My hand still on her belly. I stayed looking at her face for a time I didn't measure.
There was a decision I'd put off for three months that would stop being postponable the moment she
opened her eyes. I'd written that clause alone in my father's study, a week before sitting at the
cafe Vecca Roma across from her. I wrote it because I didn't believe a woman could stay with me for
anything other than fear or debt. I wrote it because I wanted to leave an exit door open for her.
I wrote it because the only love I'd learned to give was permission to leave. I spent three
whole months knowing that she'd still existed. I put off destroying it. I thought I'd have time.
I thought erasing it later would count the same as never having written it. It didn't. As long
as that clause was in the world, I would keep being the man who'd needed it, and not the man who
chose her. She deserved the second. The first had cost her two days locked in a room she thought was
her place once again. I ran my finger over her shoulder, very slowly without waking her.
You're going to be Donna. The way one is named, I said. So low that only the fire heard.
She nod the way one is bought. I opened the door carefully so as not to wake her.
Vastian was outside, gun on his thigh, eyes on the road. He turned his face when he heard me.
Go back to the mansion, I said. Gather all the elders and my mother in the main room tonight.
Fausto witnesses. You witness. Say it's from my own hand. Vastian looked inside.
At the rug. At her. And back at me. He nodded half a degree, left. I stayed there until she woke.
When she opened her eyes and looked at me, I knew I'd never write another door again.
We stayed in the house in the hills the rest of Friday. I slept twice more.
Eight what Bastion brought from the car. Let Ludovico tend the dressing on my arm one more time.
He spent the afternoon on the phone with Fausto, arranging the following night.
We went back to the mansion at the start of Saturday evening.
I had the handwritten draft in the pocket of my dress. I gave it back to him before going into the
main room. Neither of us said anything about it. It was agreed without words. The main room was full.
Don Vittorio, Don Emiliano, and Don Cisto seated in the high chairs at the back.
Octavia and a sidearm chair, spine straight, hands crossed over her lap.
With the same polite contempt of the first day I set foot in that house.
Fausto standing near the hearth, Bastion leaning against the wall by the door.
I came in without taking Ludovico's coat off my shoulders. He'd covered me again
in the car, without saying anything, and I hadn't given it back.
I pulled my part of the contract from my pocket. The copy Donacira had brought back to me in the
old room on the first day of morning. I tore it in two in front of them. I didn't shout.
I let the pieces fall on the rug. I'm not leaving with any fortune, I said.
Nor with any child under my arm, I'm staying, not for the door, for the house.
Vitavia opened her mouth, closed it. I stared at her without blinking.
Ludovico took a step forward. He took the handwritten draft from the inner pocket of his jacket.
He looked at his mother first, then each of the three elders. The clause was mine. He said.
The power it gave me over her was mine. Now it belongs to no one. He held the sheet out toward the
earth. The paper caught fire at the edge with an almost impatient haste, as if it too had waited too
long. He held it until the last safe instant, then let go. The ashes fell over the stones of the
heart. He turned to me, not to them. You are my equal of my family. The Donah of the Karachio Lose.
Don Amelia no, the eldest, was the first to move his head. Half a degree. It was only half a degree.
But it was him. Don Vittorio followed. Don Cisto last, with an almost imperceptible delay.
Latvia didn't move at all. She stayed where she was. Hand still crossed.
Looking at her son the way one looks at a polite stranger. Latvia had lost. And she knew it.
Ludovico took my hand on the way out of the room. He pulled me into the corridor, away from the eyes.
And only then let out the air he'd been holding the whole time. And the Sarah Valls, I asked
he raised my hand to his mouth. Pressed his lips to my wrist. And looked at me over my own hand.
Tomorrow I deal with the Sarah Valls. Today I'm your chapter six. Beneath flowers. And after his weeping.
Bastion stood near the window of the breakfast room with the newspaper folded under his arm and his usual
face, which meant something had happened. I learned that early. When his face had no expression at all,
it was because he was holding one. Two days had passed since the night of the elders.
The mansion breathed the different air. When I was still learning to recognize, Dona Kiara
served coffee with her chin higher. The corridors, which had always seemed too empty.
Now had people who greeted me by the name the family had reluctantly accepted. And there was a
small but real difference in the way that greeting arrived. Less ceremony, more person.
Ludovico raised his eyes from the newspaper. Providence? He asked. Boston.
Bastion answered. South dock. Renolfo Saravale. Found this morning with problems.
Problems of what order? The order that doesn't ask for a second visit, sir. Ludovico turned his
eyes back to the newspaper as if Bastion had commented on the weather. He turned the page with a calm,
I no longer found cold. I found it deliberate. There was a difference. I picked up my cup with both hands.
felt the warmth enter my fingers and asked nothing more. Someone in Providence would no longer
send word with dead flowers. That was all I needed to know. The rest I left with him.
Nareena appeared in the doorway carrying a white box wrapped in green ribbon.
Cake. She announced. In that way she had of turning every entrance into an act.
Before anyone asks why. Bastion got up and pulled a chair for her. Without a word.
Without taking his eyes off the window. Nareena looked at the chair.
Looked at him. Sat. Arranging the boxes ribbon on the table as if she'd seen nothing.
You know that stone face turned out kind of handsome after the coffee. She said,
loud enough for Donna Kiarra to hear from the kitchen. Bastion coughed into a hand.
Change the subject by asking Donna Kiarra for another plate. I filed it away somewhere inside me.
The chair pulled out and the evirted look and the cough that wasn't a cough. And I didn't comment.
There were stories that weren't mine yet. Seven weeks later, the garden was covered in flowers.
I didn't wear a veil. I chose a simple dress, cut at the waist, no train and no adornment I'd need to carry.
The bouquet was of chameleas. The same ones I'd been watering since the start of that spring
and pot scattered along the corridor window. A small routine that had become mine without my
noticing the exact moment. Nareena had helped me tie the white ribbon around the stems the night before.
Crying while she laughed at herself, which was exactly her way of being happy for someone.
I walked to the altar alone. There was no one to give me away. And even if there had been,
I wouldn't have accepted. No one gives away a woman who has already given herself.
The morning sun came in slanted between the rows of chairs. And the shadows of the rose stems
on the arch fell in long streaks over the stone path. I heard my own footsteps. They were the only ones.
Ludovico waited beneath the arch with his father's old watch on his wrist and his arms at his sides.
Not crossed, hiding nothing behind them. He was in a dark suit. No tie. When he saw me arrive, he swallowed.
I saw the movement in his throat. I also saw the effort he made not to let more than that show.
And I saw that the effort wasn't enough. Nareena cried,
prettyly, seated in the front row, with Donna Kiarra's hand over hers. Donna Kiarra cried in an ugly
way, an embroidered handkerchief pressed to her nose. Her shoulders shaking in generous silence.
Bastion was in a tie as few times as I'd ever seen him. A dark gray tie, meticulously nodded.
The only sign that that morning was different from all the others. Nareena turned to the nearest
person and said it loud enough to reach the altar. If he blinked twice in a row, she said,
it's a smile. Bastion blinked twice in a row, without turning his face. I saw it.
Atavia was in the front row on the right side, in a dark blue wool dress, and the bearing of
someone who came because she needed to be seen. She was invited. She accepted out of politics.
I didn't look at her once, and when the priest began to speak, I realized I also wouldn't need
to. The priest said short things. Ludovico said his vow so low that the chameleas barely heard it,
but I heard it. He said he'd learned, too late, that love isn't guaranteed with a clause,
that he'd spend the rest of his life without writing any exit door for me. That if one day I
wanted to leave, it would have to be me walking, because he'd no longer build the exit with his own hands.
I said my vow looking at him. I chose to stay. I'll keep choosing every day. He kissed me with
no contract between us. No door. With the morning sun on my back in the smell of Camilla in the air,
and his hands on both sides of my face, as if I were the only stable thing in a world he'd
spent his whole life trying to control. Winter came heavy in Providence. Enrico was born on a
late January dawn, with snow falling outside the window and thick quiet pieces. No wind, as if time
had decided to be gentle at that hour. Labor was long. Ludovico didn't leave the room once. He
held my hand through every contraction. His forehead pressed to mine. murmuring things in
Italian that I'd begun to understand because of how much he murmured near me in hours without witnesses.
Outside, Narina waited with Donna Kiarra, and an absurd basket with enough sandwiches to
feed a whole battalion, because that was her way of enduring the weight. Bastion stood in the corridor
with the gun hidden under his jacket, protecting something that had no enemy that dawn. Enrico came
into the world with a strong cry. The size the family had waited for over three generations.
The obstetrician placed him on my chest first. He stopped crying almost at once,
as if he recognized the place. I stayed looking at him. That tiny piece of a person with wet
black lashes and hands closed into small fists, and I found no word sufficient for what I felt.
I didn't try. Ludovico took him afterward. He held his son in his arms with both hands open.
The small body lost in his large arms, and stayed motionless for a few seconds just looking.
And that was when he wept. He didn't hide it. He didn't turn his face. He didn't run his hand
over his eyes as if wiping away something else. He wept looking at his son. His chin trembling
and the tears running down the line of his jaw without him making any gesture to stop them.
With a stillness that was only his, and that I'd never seen in any of the faces he used in the
nose. He said low to me when he found his voice. Poor thing. I answered. He laughed in the middle
of the weeping. He leaned his forehead against mine. That gesture that had become our private language.
Then he leaned his forehead against in Riko's too, closing the triangle among the three of us.
And we stayed like that for a time I couldn't measure. In Riko, he said, you were right.
I'd suggested the name weeks before. On an ordinary night while we waited for the snow to stop outside.
And Riko, in honor of his brother, the one who died at 19 in a story he told me only once.
Slowly, without a dormant. Lutaviko had looked at me for a long time when I said it.
Without saying yes or no, as if he needed to carry the name a little before giving his answer.
Only now, with his son and his arms and the weeping he didn't hide, was he saying yes.
Six months after the birth, the morning in the suite was one of the calmest the mansion had ever seen.
And Riko slept in the crib in the room next door. And the monitor beside my side of the bed,
purred with his breathing. That sound that had become the soundtrack of my small hours.
The June light came through the cracks and the shutters and wide warm bands.
Lutaviko came in carrying a tray with two cups, bear foot, no jacket, in the previous day's shirt.
He sat on the edge of the bed and handed me mine. Two sugar cubes, a drop of milk.
I laughed softly. The way one laughs at an old joke that keeps working out of love for what it means.
Do you remember? I asked. That I told you once months ago, my mother's dream. He already knew
which question it was. I saw it in the way he held his own cup. Unhurried. He let me finish anyway.
A library I continued. In federal hill, free books for the neighborhood children.
She never had money to put a book in my hand that wasn't borrowed from the school or from someone
who owed a favor. I bought the building three months ago. He answered, looking at his cup.
The work began last Monday. I didn't tell you because I wanted it to be a surprise when the
sign went up. It was going up next week. I stayed quiet. The band of sun crossed the sheet slowly.
The sign. I asked softly. What's it going to say? Marcecano Community Library. Your mother's maiden name.
You told me one dinner night and passing. The way one tells something without expecting anyone to keep it.
I kept it. I set the cup on the nightstand before I could spill the coffee over the sheet.
I leaned my forehead against his. We stayed like that a good while,
without either of us finding a word worth more than the silence. In Rico woke shortly after.
I nursed him. Changed him. Handed him to Ludovico so he could make the baby laugh with that stone
face that no longer fooled anyone. At the end of the morning we went down to the winter garden.
I took in Rico in my arm so he could see the chameleas. The same ones that had become my bouquet.
And that I still watered now with him on my hip, showing him the flowers as if he knew what they were.
Maybe he did. Ludovico sat beside me on the stone bench with the coffee he'd brought down from upstairs.
Still warm. The June sun came through the glass panes at a low angle, warming the stone without burning.
Do you remember the morning? He said in a low tone. When I received an envelope and put it in the drawer,
I remembered at once. The morning after the night everything had shifted sides. On the other side
of months, and of all that came after. The old envelope sealed with the crest of the lion with the broken
crown. He'd put it away unopened in front of me and hugged me too tight for an ordinary Saturday morning.
I remember. I answered. You hugged me too tight for it to be nothing. He ran his hand slowly over
Rico's hair, who slept against my shoulder with his mouth slightly open. It really was nothing.
Just the beginning. I stayed looking at him. The winter garden was in a good silence. The kind
that asks for no filling. In Rico breathe deep against my neck. Ludovico's hand was open over mine
between the two bodies in the middle of the stone bench, without grip, without weight. Just there.
I thought of the islanda who'd waited at the altar of the church and providence in a white dress
with a bell-tolling 12 times to say what the whole city already knew. She was another person.
She was me, but she was another person. The one who didn't yet know that humiliation can be the first
step of a path worth walking. Ludovico raised my hand and kissed my wrist. Slowly, without announcement.
In Rico let out a small sigh on my shoulder. Outside, the white chameleas swayed lightly with the wind
coming through the gap in the garden door. The butt wife of Providence had a price. No one,
not even he knew it was this, to stay.