The house near the Savannah River woke up slowly.
The  way  old  houses  do,  carrying  the  habit  of  breathing  before
their  people.
The  light  of  dawn  came  through  the  crack  in  the  curtains  in  a  thin  strip
and  settled  on
her  shoulder,  and  Jago  Quint  stood  there  looking  at  that
shoulder  for  longer  than  was  reasonable.
Rowena  slept  on  her  side,  one  hand  opened  near  her
face,  like  someone  who  had  left  a
question half-assed and decided to finish asking at the next day.
The  sheet  had  slipped  down  to  her  waist,  and  the  light
caught  the  loose  strands  of  her  hair
which still smelled of the soap from the night before.
He got up without a sound.
His  body  knew  this  ritual,  getting  out  of  bed  without
waking  the  one  who  stayed.
There  was  a  calm  inside  him  that  still  scared  him,  six  months
after  she'd  moved  into  that  house.
That  was  love  he'd  discovered,  and  at  the  same  time  it  was  something
else  a  small  dread,
almost  decorative  that  lived  beneath  his  rib  cage  and  beat  along
with  his  heart.
He thought he knew how to handle it.
A  man  who  survived  what  he'd  survived,  learns  to
tame  his  own  fear.
He went down the stairs stepping on the side of the wood that didn't creak.
The kitchen was still cold, with that stale air of June mornings that hadn't decided whether
they were warm or not.
He turned on the kettle, measured out her coffee like someone writing a sentence he already knew
by heart.
Two scoops of grounds, water that hadn't fully boiled, a little less than the usual ratio,
because Roenah liked her coffee milder at the start of the day, as if the morning needed
to ask permission before coming in.
The smell rose slowly through the kitchen.
There was something in it he could never quite name.
It wasn't the coffee itself.
It was what the smell stood for.
She was still there and she'd come down.
There was a thought he avoided at that hour, and the thought showed up anyway.
If she ever vanished from there the smell of coffee would tear him apart with devastating
efficiency.
He stirred the spoon slowly and brushed the thought aside with the same gesture you'd
use to wave off a polite fly.
Not today.
The male came early.
Feline, the personal assistant, delivered the envelope at the side door with the discrete
punctuality J. Gopei dearly for.
There were three letters from the office.
One from the management of one of the properties, and a cream-coloured envelope.
No return address.
Address to Roenah Pike in the impersonal handwriting of a secretary at some respectable
institution.
He recognized the letterhead in the upper corner before he even looked properly.
He stood there for a second with the envelope between his fingers, feeling the specific
weight of quality paper.
I'll take this one.
He said, low.
He tucked the envelope into the inside pocket of his jacket, as if he were putting away
an important document he'd remember to hand over later.
In New He wouldn't remember.
He'd already decided not to remember before he even finished the gesture.
The worst part was that his hand had made the move without consulting him, with an old
efficiency he recognized as his own, and didn't like recognizing.
Feline saw it.
Feline said nothing.
The two exchanged a brief greeting, and the assistant left the same way he'd come in,
is steps muffled by the runner in the hallway.
When Roenah came down, coffee was served in two cups.
She appeared in the kitchen doorway, in a long night gown.
A hair loosely pinned up, rubbing her eye with a closed fist like a child.
The morning sun was coming in now through the side window, and drew a golden square on
the wooden floor between them.
He looked up and the small decorative dread settled back beneath his ribcage quiet.
You got up early?
She remarked, her voice still thick with sleep.
I couldn't sleep with you breathing so beautifully like that, J. Go answered, and his mouth
almost smiled.
She laughed.
It was a short, slightly husky laugh, the kind he collected inside without admitting
he collected them.
She sat on the stool at the kitchen island, took the cup with both hands, and smelled
it before drinking the way she did every day.
Her eyes closing for half a second over the steam, a gesture so hers that he already knew
it by heart.
He watched without seeming to watch.
Are you expecting anything today?
He asked, and the tone was casual in that practiced way.
Rowena thought for a second her eyes still on the cup, and answer, she said, maybe.
That conversation I told you about last week, she looked up.
You remember?
I remember, he answered.
He remembered.
In his pocket he had exactly the answer she was waiting for, and the answer was generous.
And the answer would take her out of that house for six months.
The pocket weighed on him in a specific way.
He drank his own coffee and said nothing more.
Rowena looked at him for a second longer than her usual.
Then she looked at her own coffee, and the rest of the morning ran along beautifully,
the way their mornings usually ran.
At noon, Silas Ashford was waiting for Jago at the office in downtown Savannah.
The lawyer had a way of sitting in chairs that didn't belong to him as if they did.
Legs crossed, one finger resting against his temple.
The expressionless face he wore when he brought bad news.
The air conditioning in the room was set too high, and the artificial chill clashed
with the heat coming in through the wide windows overlooking the square.
Short lunch.
Silas announced when Jago walked in.
Short why?
Because what I've got to tell you doesn't go well with dessert.
Jago closed the door behind him.
He sat down on the other side of the desk.
The two had no need to other long enough to skip the run around.
Someone's asking questions.
Silas said without raising his voice.
Again in three different places.
Discrete questions.
The kind of trained person asks.
And the questions come too close to what we agreed to never let anyone get close to.
Jago didn't move.
Inside the decorative dread grew an inch.
Name?
He asked.
Not yet.
But they pay well, and they pay with money that leaves no trail.
That interest me more than the name.
Jago looked at the desk.
There was a line of silence the two of them respected.
The kind built over years of loyalty.
Silas waited.
He always waited with that stone patience he charged dearly for by the hour.
Double the security at the house.
Jago said finally.
Quietly.
Rowina can't know.
Silas kept looking at him a second longer than necessary.
Jago.
She can't know Silas.
The lawyer ran his tongue along the inside corner of his cheek.
A small gesture he made when he wanted to say something and chose not to.
Then he nodded in that short dry way of his.
And that envelope, Silas asked.
Did the answer come?
Jago didn't answer right away.
He tapped his thumb lightly on the tabletop once twice.
It came.
Are you going to deliver it?
I am.
Jago looked up.
There was something in his eyes that Silas had known long before this conversation.
The same thing that lived in that gaze ten years ago.
And that Silas had hoped for a while had gotten better.
When I figure out how.
Silas nodded.
But his face didn't agree.
The two finished lunch in decent silence with the noise from the square coming in muffled
through the windows.
When Jago left the office, the cream envelope was still weighing in the inside pocket
of his jacket.
And he had for the first time in a long time a brief urge to tear it up.
Rowena spent the afternoon in the living room of the house near the river.
She was rereading some old work notes.
Things she kept in a hardcover folder that sat on a shelf in plain sight.
No hiding place at all.
She'd learned to value that transparency the way people do, who have already lost someone
by hiding too much.
The afternoon light came in slanted through the half open blinds and striped the rug in
golden bands.
Outside the river made its usual gentle sound, the living room phone rang at a little
past five.
Nieve had gone to the market with Feline.
Jago hadn't come back yet.
Rowena answered.
Quint residence.
She said.
The way she always answered.
Half joking with the formality.
On the other end, a full second of silence.
Then a man's voice horse with age and with something harder to name.
Good afternoon I need to speak with Mr. Quint.
He's not in at the moment.
Can I take a message?
Another silence.
She heard the man breathe as if he were weighing every word before letting it out.
Rowena, a well-trained journalist, began paying attention with her whole body.
Without yet knowing why.
There was something in that silence that wasn't in decision.
It was calculation.
It's the man coughed lightly.
It's about kit.
Tell him it's about kit.
He'll understand.
Rowena stopped breathing for a second.
Not because of the name.
The name still meant nothing to her.
She stopped because of the way the man said it.
Like someone handing over a password, he knows will open a door that's been locked for a long time.
Kit, she repeated slowly and her voice came out more neutral than she was feeling.
May I ask who's calling?
The man was already answering when the front door slammed.
Quick steps in the hallway.
Quicker than J. GO step usually was at the end of the day.
He walked into the room with his meeting posture still in his body.
And stopped walking when he saw the phone in her hand.
She watched the colour drain from his face in real time.
It was something she'd never seen before in that man.
No anger, no practice, surprise.
Just a physical animal whiteness.
Rising from his chin to his forehead in seconds, as if someone had flipped a switch.
The was it?
He asked.
His voice too low for the size of the question.
Roena didn't answer.
She held out the receiver.
J. GO took it, brought it to his ear, listened for two seconds.
Close his eyes once. A single blink longer than normal.
The kind of gesture that isn't reflex its decision.
And then said just one sentence.
Don't call this number.
He hung up.
He kept his hand on the phone for a length of time she counted inside her own chest.
Be it by beat.
Roena looked at him.
She knew that man in her body.
In his smell.
In the way he ran his thumb under his eye when he was tired.
She'd never seen him white like that.
She'd never seen him need support just to stay standing.
J. GO.
He didn't answer right away.
Who was it?
She asked.
With the trained calm her profession had given her as a gift.
He looked up.
And that was when she saw it.
For the first time since the two of them had met,
she saw him decide to lie.
It wasn't a quick decision.
She saw the moment before it.
The instant when he could still choose the other path.
An old employee, J. GO said,
drunk probably got the wrong number.
She kept looking at him.
He held her gaze with the composure of someone who'd spent his whole life holding
gayses.
He couldn't afford to lose.
He knew inside that she knew.
Still, he wanted her to let it go.
He said a name, Roena said,
and her voice came out very low almost gentle,
which was the way she used when the question wasn't gentle.
J. GO swallowed.
What name?
Kid.
He didn't blink.
He carried his body to the sideboard next to the sofa,
rested his hand on the wood as if he needed something solid.
And spoke looking at the river through the window, his back to her.
I don't know him.
Roena stood where she was.
On the other side of the room near the big window there was a chair.
Just like the one in the mansion's main hall,
brought here when they moved in.
She had now six months of looking at that chair without understanding why no one ever sat in it.
Why the seat was always turned slightly toward the river,
as if waiting for someone who knew where they'd arrived from.
She looked at the chair, looked at J. GO's back,
looked at the chair again,
and the chair for the first time had a sound.
The name was short, short, and old.
It had only three letters, and it slipped down the phone line like a poorly tied secret,
spoken by a horse voice.
Kid.
She didn't repeat it out loud.
She kept it.
She was very good at that.
That night Roena didn't sleep.
She lay looking at the bedroom ceiling,
listening to his breathing beside her.
That breathing she knew better than her own,
that she could tell when it was real sleep,
and when it was faked.
That night for the first time she couldn't read it.
Outside, the river ran with its usual soft sound,
indifferent to what was happening inside that beautiful house.
Inside her chest, an empty chair had begun to creak.
The sun came into the bedroom in the morning as if nothing had happened,
and Jago moved in bed the way he always did.
His hand seeking her waist beneath the sheet,
his face pressing into the nape of her neck,
the short kiss at the spot where her hair began.
Roena lay still, eyes closed, and received it all with her skin.
His warmth was real.
The weight of his arm was real.
It was easier to stay quiet a second longer,
and let her body believe in what her mind hadn't yet resolved.
Then she turned over.
Jago.
The call yesterday.
He opened his eyes with a staged laziness.
She saw the staging.
It was quick, almost imperceptible, but she saw it.
She'd learn to see the small things in him before she'd learn their names.
I already told you my love, it was nobody.
You went white.
Jago smiled with half his mouth.
That small smile he reserved for diffusing
difficult situations in boardrooms.
He raised his hand and tucked a strand of her hair behind her ear,
with a calculated lightness.
A gesture that had always worked before.
One she herself had loved in those first months,
when she still couldn't tell genuine tenderness
from the tenderness that served as a curtain.
I didn't, he said, his voice low and firm,
you were against the light.
She looked at him in silence.
A pause of three, four seconds,
enough for any guilty person to fill the emptiness with more words.
He didn't fill it, he was too good for that.
He leaned in, kissed the corner of her mouth with a tenderness
that was real and at the same time evasive about everything,
and spoke against her skin.
Let's have coffee.
Rowena let it go.
She kissed him back.
Short, got up, went to shower alone.
And while the water fell too hot on her shoulders,
she thought for the first time in plain terms,
a sentence that bothered her a great deal.
Tenderness and truth are not the same thing.
She stayed under the water longer than she needed to.
The bathroom smelled of the citrus soap Jago had started buying for her,
when he noticed which one she liked.
One more detail he memorized,
one more gesture she no longer knew how to receive.
She came down dressed to go out.
Linin pants, a light-colored blouse.
A small bag she used when she went downtown.
Jago was in the kitchen reading something on the tablet,
with a cup of coffee in front of him that must have been half-loop warm by now.
He looked at her with that gaze that crossed the room without needing distance.
Where are you going?
She founded him using, not the question.
The tone.
It was his old tone.
The one she thought had been left behind since they'd gotten themselves organized,
six months earlier, to live together there near the river.
Downtown, by a couple things.
Marlo arrives today, remember?
I remember.
He set down the tablet.
Taking the car?
I'm driving myself.
He nodded as if he were accepting it.
He reached out.
Took a hand on the cold marble counter,
squeezed it lightly.
His fingers wrapping around hers with the ease of someone
who already knew every knuckle.
Be careful.
She went out the side door.
She walked along the stone hallway to the garage,
took the keys off the hook.
The air outside smelled of the river's dampness,
and of some neighbouring garden that must have had Jasmine.
It was early enough that Savannah's heat hadn't yet weighed down.
When she opened the electric gate,
two men in suits were standing outside next to a dark car she didn't recognize.
They didn't seem like a threat.
They seemed like scenery.
The scenery of another kind of house,
not hers.
One of them approached with a smile that was too polite.
Mrs. Pike, good morning, will be going with you.
Rowena blinked.
Going with me, where?
Wherever you go.
House orders.
Security.
She looked at the man.
Looked at the other one.
Neither of them seemed embarrassed.
Neither of them seemed to expect her to argue.
That more than anything else was what bothered her,
that they derived ready for the normalcy of a situation she hadn't authorized.
I didn't ask for security.
She said, with a calm that wasn't easy to maintain.
You don't need to ask, Mom, it's already been arranged.
She stood for a second on the stone pavement.
Inside the house, behind her, Jago knew.
Jago was on the tablet with the lukewarm cup, and he knew.
It given the order the day before at the downtown office,
and he knew the exact second she'd meet those two men at the gate.
At that very moment, sitting in the kitchen,
he swallowed some coffee that was too cold to cover his own nerves.
His hand pressing lightly on the tablet for no reason at all.
Rowena didn't make a scene.
She simply said, All right, she got into her car.
Let their car follow behind.
She drove to downtown Savannah with both hands on the wheel,
and the silence inside the car so vast,
that she turned on the radio.
Found it unbearable.
Turned it off.
Bahan stayed on the leather of the wheel,
and she looked out the window at the old Magnolia's lining the avenue.
White and heavy from so much blooming,
and thought that some beautiful things were also suffocating.
Marlo Trent showed up on time at the old cafe in the historic district,
with a bag too big for anything she could possibly need there,
and an expression Rowena recognized from far off.
The expression of someone who'd flown three hours
to give a dose of reality to someone she loved very much,
and who was in need of hearing it.
Row, Marlo,
they hugged the way they'd hugged for years,
tight without ceremony.
Marlo rubbing her hand twice on her back with that energy of someone who
arrived to fix something.
The cafe smelled of cinnamon and burnt coffee from an old machine,
and the dark wooden tables had marks from years of cups.
They sat near the window.
Marlo ordered black coffee,
Rowena a cappuccino.
Across the street, the dark car parked with professional discretion.
Those two yours, Marlo pointed with her chin,
no filter at all.
They're the houses,
the houses.
Yeah, Marlo raised a eyebrow.
Marlo had an eyebrow that asked whole questions on its own
without needing anything more.
Row, don't start.
Row, love doesn't treat you like a hostage.
Rowena loved.
It was a short laugh a little awkward but honest,
and she felt along with it a good pang.
The pang of someone being reminded of herself
by someone who'd known her before all of this.
They talked for an hour.
Marlo talked about the newsroom,
about the new editor who'd reorganized everything.
About the people who still asked about Rowena now and then with that mix of curiosity and respect
that comes just before being forgotten.
Rowena listened and wanted to feel a clean kind of longing,
uncomplicated, but the longing that arrived had an uneven edge.
At some point, out of old reflex,
she took the recorder from her bag.
A small, silver recorder that she carried out of a habit of more than six years,
always in the side pocket.
She looked at the device in the palm of her hand
as if she weren't sure when it had ended up there.
She put it back without pressing a single button.
Marlo saw it.
Marlo saw everything always had.
Who are you now journalist?
She asked, with the corner of her mouth croaked in a way that was both a question and a fiction,
Rowena laughed for real this time, a bigger laugh that arrived without warning.
A woman waiting for an answer that never comes.
What answer?
A proposal?
A job offer?
They sent it last week.
I still haven't gotten any reply.
Marlo kept looking at her.
She held the cup with both hands and waited a second longer before speaking.
That second rowing a new.
The second that came before the sentences that stayed.
Row.
What?
Are you sure it didn't come?
Rowena stopped the cappuccino midway.
The cup hung suspended.
The heat rising to her face.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
Marlo deflected and looked at the dark car across the street with an expression that was nothing.
Never mind.
But the sentence stayed.
Marlo knew how to put sentences in the air the way they'd hang suspended.
And this one stayed the rest of the coffee.
The rest of the way back.
The rest of the whole afternoon.
Rowena returned to the house near the river in the late afternoon,
with savanna's golden light striking the paving stones from the side.
And a thin mist rising from the river as it always did when the heat began to give way.
The two men followed behind in professional silence.
Jago was still at the downtown office.
The house was quiet.
Only neither in the kitchen.
Cutting something with that silent precision of hers.
And the smell of rosemary coming from some pot that had been on the stove for a while.
Rowena went into Jago's private study,
with an excuse she'd prepared for herself while still in the car.
She needed that old contract from the house renovation work.
The carpenter had asked for a copy of the original specification.
It was a polite lie.
The kind you tell yourself before doing what you were going to do anyway.
She opened the first drawer.
Office papers all in order, labelled with the precision of a man who tolerated chaos on no surface.
Second drawer.
Contracts.
Thin folders with dates and numbers.
Third drawer.
A cream-coloured envelope.
No return address.
With her name in the center in the impersonal, type-written handwriting.
Let her head in the upper right corner.
Winslow foundation for independent journalism.
The envelope was open.
She stood still.
The study itself went still around her.
The dark shelves, the books lined up by size.
The narrow window that looked out onto the side garden with the moss on the stones.
Her hands went strangely quiet.
She took the envelope.
She pulled out the contents carefully,
as if the paper might confirm something she already knew.
But didn't yet want to name.
Two sheets.
The first was the formal invitation.
A job offer.
A series of long investigative reports, full grant, complete autonomy over the topics.
An offer that would bring her career back to life from scratch.
At the exact point where she'd left off before Savannah.
Before the ball.
Before everything.
The second sheet was a carbon copy.
A reply.
Dated 10 days ago.
Dear Serz.
We thank you for your generous consideration.
At this time, Miss Pike is not available to take on new professional
commitments.
We renew our thanks.
A signature at the bottom in hand writing.
The same handwriting that appeared in the notes he left her in the kitchen in the morning.
The same as the contract she signed alongside him.
The same one she'd learned to recognize before even reading what was written.
His hand writing.
Ruinna kept looking at the sheet for a length of time she couldn't measure.
Her body didn't tremble.
Her body went very still.
And the stillness was heavier than any tremor.
Ruinna put the envelope back in the drawer.
Closed it with the same care she'd opened it.
She left the private study without taking the carpenters contract.
She didn't need the contract.
She never had.
She went to the living room.
She sat on the sofa.
Without turning on the light.
The afternoon had closed into that dark blue of early night that came fast in Savannah's summer.
And the room filled with a warm dimness.
On the other side next to the big window.
The empty chair was in its usual place.
With the last light of day reaching only the backrest.
She looked at the chair for a long time.
Two stories she thought.
One of them has a short old name that no one pronounces inside this house.
The other has his handwriting on a sheet that answered for her without her knowing.
The phone rang.
It was Jago.
Love.
I'm not going to make it home yet.
Don't stay hungry.
Eat without me.
She closed her eyes.
She held her voice in the right place.
That exact place where the voice stops trembling and becomes just an answer.
Okay.
I love you.
You too.
She hung up.
She kept the phone in her hand.
The heat of the device against her palm.
Outside the river ran with that low constant sound she'd learned to find calming
and that now sounded different.
The empty chair waited.
And for the first time in six months,
Rowena Pike felt inside her own chest.
The low firm creek of a decision beginning to be made.
The cream envelope sat on the table between them as if it weighed more than the wood holding it up.
Rowena had waited all day to set it down there.
At the exact spot where he usually left his keys.
She chose the dining room table because it was the only room where Jago couldn't lean on a
work object.
No paper, no pen, no phone.
Just him, her and his handwriting betraying his handwriting.
Jago came in after eight.
He took off his jacket with the slowness of someone who already knew what he'd find.
The house near the Savannah River smelled of Jasmine from the garden outside.
An out of season's sweetness that only worsened the sensation that the air was breathing on its own.
He saw the envelope.
He didn't ask what it was.
Inside he felt a lying sentence form before he could stop it.
I was going to tell you and in the same instant, new it was false.
He wasn't going to.
If she hadn't found it, that paper would have died at the bottom of that drawer.
Rowena, his voice came out too controlled to be sincere.
It's not what it looks like.
She crossed her arms over her linen dress.
She didn't sit.
The yellow light of the chandelier fell between them like a border.
It's exactly what it looks like Jago.
He breathed in deep.
The cold panic settled between one rib and another.
That old cold he knew from another night, 10 years ago.
He swallowed twice before he managed to speak.
I wanted to protect you.
From a job offer.
From an offer that was going to take you away from Savannah for six months.
Rowena smiled without joy.
And the decision to go or stay was yours.
He opened his mouth and found no answer.
She continued lower because the low voice hurt more.
You answered for me.
You said, thank you for me.
You declined for me.
Each sentence fell like a small stone into the bottom of a glass.
And then you brought me breakfast.
Rowena.
No.
She raised her hand.
And her hand was trembling and she hated that.
You're not going to ask me for time.
Time is the one thing you shouldn't ask for today.
You had six months.
He took a step toward her.
She took a step back.
It was a small movement.
But he felt as if he'd been shoved against the opposite wall of the room.
Inside something in him.
The part that was always certain began to crack.
He watched her mouth pronounce the next sentence before he heard it.
Who is kit?
The name fell to the dining room floor and stayed there gleaming.
Jego looked at the envelope.
looked at her.
looked at the window that faced the dark river outside.
He said nothing.
And his silence was the first real confession.
Good night, Jego.
She went up the stairs slowly.
He stood beside the table for too long listening to her footsteps disappear into the upstairs
hallway.
Then he sat in the nearest chair elbows on his knees and stared at his own envelope as if the
paper were capable of answering for him.
Rowena didn't sleep.
She spent the small hours with her eyes open at the ceiling of the guest room.
That room she'd never entered before and where the sheets smelled of forgotten lavender.
She mentally repeated the list of things she knew.
The name, the chair, the terrace.
Udora's remark about a laugh that wasn't hers.
The payments she hadn't yet traced.
The envelope answered in his handwriting.
There were two stories being hidden.
She needed to unravel both.
In the morning before the sun rose fully, she called a taxi from the street.
She didn't ask for a house car.
She didn't tell Filan.
She put on the plane as close she had and went out the side door and no guard saw her.
Because no guard expected her to leave before six in the morning.
Silas Ashford's office was in downtown Savannah in an old townhouse with tall windows and a
permanent smell of coffee and old paper.
The sun hadn't yet warm the sidewalk when she climbed the steps.
Silas answered the door himself.
He didn't even ask what she wanted.
He just pointed to the chair in front of the desk.
You already know why I'm here.
I'm pretty sure I do.
Silas poured two coffees without asking.
And I'm pretty sure I shouldn't open my mouth.
Roena accepted the coffee and didn't drink it.
Silas, her voice came out firmer than she expected.
Your his friend, I know that.
But you were also the only one who looked me in the eye that night at the ball and didn't pretend
not to see what you were seeing.
I need to know who kit is.
Silas let the coffee rest between his hands.
He stared at the tabletop for long enough that Roena understood the answer would hurt him too.
Kit was his brother.
He said it last.
Younger.
Was.
That's what they say in Savannah.
And what do you say?
Silas raised his eyes.
There was a new caution in them.
The caution of someone crossing a line and knowing it.
I say there was a boating accident 10 years ago
that the boat was found destroyed, that the family buried a closed casket.
He paused and that Jego never believed it.
Roena felt her own chest drop.
Why did he never believe it?
Silas shook his head slowly.
Roena, not today, not this.
This isn't mine to tell.
Silas.
I've already said more than I should.
He looked at the door.
Go home ask him.
He won't answer me.
Then come back here when he doesn't.
She got up.
At the door she stopped.
She didn't look back when she said.
Thank you.
Silas didn't answer.
He kept looking at her coffee that hadn't been drunk.
And for the first time in 10 years,
he felt he might be betraying the right friend.
Back at the house near the river.
Roena found Neeve in the kitchen,
arranging sprigs of basil in a glass jar.
The old housekeeper had her hair pinned up in a loose bun
and wore the same grey apron as always.
Roena stopped in the doorway for a second before going in.
Neeve belonged to that house more than Jego belonged to it.
If anyone knew, it was her.
Neeve.
The woman looked up.
She smiled with that small smile she kept for Roena.
Good morning dear.
Shall I make some tea?
Neeve.
Who is Kitt?
The smile disappeared so fast
that Roena almost doubted it had existed.
Neeve's hands gripped the jar too hard.
One of the sprigs slipped and fell into the sink.
Oh dear.
Please.
Neeve looked at the door leading to the hallway.
She looked at the window that faced the garden,
where the morning Jasmine was still closed.
She looked at the counter as if the answer might be printed on the marble.
It's not my place.
I know it isn't.
Roena took a step closer,
but I've been sleeping in this house for six months.
And I can't pretend anymore that I don't see.
He avoids the terrace.
You avoid answering.
Mrs. Udora has never said that name near me.
And last night I asked my husband,
the word slipped out before she could choose another.
And he went silent.
Neeve closed her eyes.
He avoids the terrace.
Her voice came out broken almost inaudible.
Because that's where the boat set out that night.
Roena didn't move.
What night, Neeve?
The night.
Neeve wiped her hands on her apron,
a mechanical gesture,
the only night.
The one this family could never buried properly.
She turned her face aside.
Don't ask me for the rest dear.
Please.
Roena swallowed hard.
Mr. Kitt,
Neeve continued.
And now she was speaking to the basil, not to her.
At a way of laughing loud.
Mrs. Udora used to say he'd wake the whole house when he was a child.
A small smile crossed her face and vanished.
It was a beautiful laugh, too full for that mouth.
You have his laugh.
Roena had to grip the counter.
The air went out of her slowly.
Her hand pressed on the cold marble.
The certainty assembling inside her ribs like an old building rising from the dark.
Whose laugh it was.
Where the sentence came from.
Why Udora had looked at her that way,
as she left that night at the ball.
Thank you, Neeve.
Dear, the housekeeper held her arm for a second.
Her fingers were firm and dry.
He suffered.
Don't let anger make you forget that.
I won't forget.
The weekend passed in a silence of war.
Jego didn't try to enter the guest room.
Roena didn't come down from meals.
Feeling carried trays in silence.
Left them outside the door.
Collected them untouched.
On Saturday afternoon,
Roena wrote in her planner.
The list of everything she needed to trace.
Payments.
Names.
Cities.
Dates.
She started with the public library in downtown Savannah.
Where the old newspapers were kept on microfilm.
She spent hours hunched over a reader that hummed softly.
The smell of dry paper and old air conditioning filling the small room.
She found the headline she knew existed.
Quint Air Missing After Coastal Storm.
The photo was small, grainy.
A young man smiling with his mouth open.
His teeth a little crooked.
His hair touseled by the wind.
She looked at the face for a long time.
There was something of Jego in it.
In the shape of the eyes in the line of the jaw.
There was also that Frank Lough,
Nive had described.
Two wide for a newspaper portrait, impossible to contain.
On Sunday, she cross-referenced information.
She asked feeling for old statements with some excuse.
And the assistant, who already liked her more than he should,
gave in without asking.
She found regular payments going out of a parallel account of Jego's.
Monthly.
Always the same rounded amount.
Always to the office of a lawyer with no recognizable family name.
She found receipts from a pharmacy in a small town she'd never heard of.
She found, among the clippings, Nive kept in an old envelope in the kitchen cabinet.
A photo where a teenage kid appeared beside an older man.
The same face she'd recognized in the more recent records.
Marlo called at three in the morning on Monday.
Rowena answered on the second ring.
Row I had the strange feeling that you needed to laugh.
Marlo.
Seriously, I was asleep.
woke up out of nowhere, looked at the ceiling and thought,
this woman needs to laugh right now.
Rowena laughed.
She laughed for real mouth open in the middle of the silent guest room.
Then she started to cry and kept laughing and Marlo on the other end stayed quiet,
waiting for the hurricane to pass.
I found out the name, Rowena said when she was able.
The kid guy, he was his brother.
Was.
That's what Silas said.
Marlo breathed in deep and do you believe it?
I believe nobody pays for a pharmacy for a dead man.
Silas on the other end.
Then, Row.
Marlo's voice was serious now.
Are you sure you want to go down this hole?
I already have.
Then hold on tight.
Rowena looked at the planner open on the mattress and a dress had appeared twice in the
receipts, a small town a few hours by train from Savannah.
A name that matched the man from the old photo.
She circled everything in red pen and underlined the address three times.
The pressure of the pen leaving a groove on the paper below.
On the other side of the house, Jago was sitting in the study with a glass of whiskey he hadn't
touched in hours.
He'd heard the taxi arrive in the morning.
He'd heard the taxi leave.
He'd heard Rowena ask feeling for the statements.
With an excuse he knew because he himself was the one.
Who'd used that excuse decades ago.
He knew she was piecing it together.
He knew she was going to find it.
And for the first time in 10 years he couldn't tell whether he was afraid of what she'd
discover or afraid of what he'd feel when she knew.
He ran his hand over his forehead.
His hand was trembling.
In the guest room Rowena closed the planner.
A name.
An address.
A small town.
Everything that had come before.
The old story, the charade at the ball, the coffee without a recorder, had been
training for this decision.
She turned off the light.
And in the dark, she heard clearly the sound the empty chair made
inside her now.
It was no longer a creek.
It was a whole name.
Silas gave in on Tuesday morning.
And he gave in because Rowena stopped asking.
She walked into his office without knocking.
She placed the open planner on his desk.
The address circled in red.
The name of the man from the old photo written beside it.
She said nothing.
Silas read it.
Lean back against the chair and closed his eyes for a moment.
Like someone who knew this moment would come sooner or later and had chosen too late.
You got to this on your own.
I get to almost everything on my own Silas.
The open his eyes.
There was guilt in them now.
An old guilty no longer tried to disguise beneath the efficiency of the faithful assistant.
If I complete the picture.
Jago will kill me.
Jago is already dying inside Silas.
She said, what do you want?
To bury both of them.
Silas kept looking at her for a length of time that seemed to stretch beyond how long silence
usually lasts.
Then he opened a desk drawer and took out a small card no letterhead.
With a name written by hand on one side and an address on the other.
He slid it across the desk with two fingers.
Like someone handing something over.
And at the same time apologizing for having taken so long.
The man who carries the money is this one.
His voice came out low, almost horse.
He lives between Savannah and the town.
He makes the trip by train once a month.
Always on the first Saturday.
He tapped the card lightly.
Kid lives in that town under another name.
I'm not going to tell you which.
That he'll have to tell you himself.
Roenah took the card.
She felt the paper way more than it should.
More than any paper card should weigh.
Thank you.
Roenah Silas leaned forward his elbows on the desk.
If he doesn't want to come back, don't force it.
He has that right.
I won't force it.
And please.
His voice nearly broke before reaching the end of the sentence.
Take care of Jago when you come back.
She tucked the card into the inside pocket of her bag.
She stood up.
She was almost at the door when he spoke again.
Roenah.
Yes.
By now, why did you tell me now?
He took a while to answer.
When he answered, he looked at the window.
Not at her.
At the street below where Savannah went on ahead, knowing nothing.
Because I watched Jago spend 10 years dying slowly.
And I watched you arrive and him start to live again.
And I can't watch him lose you thinking he's protecting you.
He turned his gaze back to her.
Someone needs to break this cycle.
You're the only one with the courage to break it.
Roenah nodded once.
She left.
Outside Savannah's air had that humid mid-afternoon heat.
Dense and green.
With the smell of wet earth mixed with the distant salt of the estuary.
She walked to the station without hurry,
feeling the uneven paving under her shoes.
The sounds of the city around her.
The streetcar passing by.
A child shouting in some backyard.
The clinking of glasses in a corner cafe.
She bought a one-way ticket for the four-a-clock train.
And called Marlo from the payphone.
I'm going.
Alone?
Marlo paused for a long time.
The kind that contains questions one decides not to ask.
Do you want me to call someone if you don't come back in 24 hours?
Call Silas.
Done.
Before boarding.
Roenah stopped at the house near the river.
She came in through the side door.
Went up to the guest room through some clothes into a small suit
with the objectivity of someone who knows that thinking too much
is a luxury that doesn't fit in the luggage.
She went down to the kitchen, where the afternoon light came in slanted through the shutters.
And Ruth in stripes across the stone floor.
And wrote a short letter on a piece of writing paper.
The letter had a single line.
I'll come back when I bring what he couldn't bring on his own.
She left the letter on top of the day's newspaper.
She left.
Feel and saw her come down the stairs with the suitcase
and ask nothing.
She asked him to call a taxi.
He called one.
Before the taxi door closed, the assistant said quietly almost to himself,
have a good trip miss.
She didn't correct him.
The train left Savannah at four o'clock sharp.
Roenah chose a seat by the window and rested her forehead against the cold glass.
And for a long time thought about nothing.
She passed low houses, flooded fields, a smaller town with a rusty water tower in the center.
A river that wasn't the Savannah.
A line of Cyprus's cutting into the copper-colored sky of the late afternoon.
The sun began to set slowly,
tinting the landscape and orange that looked like a painting.
She opened the planner and re-read the address three times
as if she could forget it.
And she knew she couldn't.
On the other side at the house near the river,
Jago arrived at seven at night and felt that something was missing before he looked in any direction.
It was as if the house had changed weight,
not temperature, not sound,
weight.
He passed through the living room the kitchen,
saw the letter on top of the newspaper.
He read it.
He read it again.
And something in him collapsed with the same silent precision of a structure
that gives way from within with no visible warning.
It was the same old night returning to his nostrils,
the smell of the sea after the storm,
the taste of metal in his mouth,
the physical animal certainty that he had lost again
and that this time the punishment was proportional to the size of the mistake.
He let the letter drop.
He sat on the kitchen floor.
He truly sat.
His back against the door of the low cabinet
and his hands open on his knees as if he didn't know what to do with them.
He stayed there too long for it to be dignity.
Scytler showed up half an hour later.
He hadn't been called, he simply knew.
He came in through the side door,
found Jago on the floor,
knelt beside him without hesitation.
I told her.
Jago raised his face slowly.
There was something in his eyes that wasn't anger.
It was an exhaustion so deep,
it passed beneath the anger
and reached a place the anger no longer reached.
You told her what?
The name, the address.
The man who carries the money.
Jago closed his eyes.
It took him a full second to breathe again.
I'm going to hit you, Scytler.
Hit me.
Jago didn't hit him.
He clenched his fist, raised it and the fist stopped in the air before touching anything.
He lowered his hand slowly, rested it on his knee
and stared at his own fingers as if he didn't recognize them.
As if that man sitting on the floor of his kitchen
belonged to someone else.
She went alone.
She did.
And if he doesn't take her in.
He'll take her in.
He can't say no to anyone, Jago.
He never could.
Jago swallowed twice.
And if he takes her in and doesn't want to come?
Scytler didn't answer.
There was no answer to that.
Jago squeezed his eyes shut.
Inside something in him was reconstructing the timeline
with a precision that hurt.
The train's schedule, the distance, the time she'd need to arrive.
The night she'd spend alone in a town he knew from a map and from receipts.
But never with his own eyes.
He'd never gone.
He'd never allowed himself to go.
And now she was going for him.
With the courage he'd traded for control.
And he was sitting on the kitchen floor because he no longer knew what to do with his own body.
Scytler.
Yes.
If she comes back, I'll fix it.
She'll come back.
If she comes back.
Silas rested his hand on his shoulder and left it there.
She'll come back, Jago.
In the small town the train arrived at 9.20 at night.
Rowing a got off with the small suitcase felt the asphalt different under her feet.
Piotr without Sivanor's constant noise and looked for a small hotel a block from the station,
with painted wooden windows and a ceiling fan that turned slowly.
She paid for one night.
Went up.
Didn't have dinner.
She sat on the edge of the bed until dawn,
with Silas's card in her hand and the address memorized.
In the morning she followed the map on foot.
The town was smaller than she'd expected.
A main street with five shops.
A central square with a bandstand painted white and peeling at the edges.
Low houses scattered along dirt roads where grass grew down the middle.
The address led her to a modest light blue house,
with an neglected front garden and a rocking chair sitting motionless on the porch.
She knocked on the door.
Once with her knuckle, firm.
A man opened it.
She recognized him before she looked properly.
She recognized him by the shape of the eyes.
By the line of the jaw.
By the way he stood in the doorway.
The same way Jago had a filling a threshold that presence that filled the space even in silence.
Except this man was thinner, harder.
With a small scar crossing his left eyebrow and lighter hair.
Sun bleached.
He had the slightly crooked teeth she remembered from the newspaper photo.
Kit.
He was paralyzed for a full second.
Then he stepped back half a step.
Who are you?
Rowena Pike.
She didn't move forward.
I've been with your brother for a while.
The silence that came after was dense and loaded.
Kit rested one hand on the door frame.
As if he needed the support.
His fingers gripping the painted wood.
You shouldn't be here.
I know.
He sent you.
He doesn't even know I came.
Kit looked at her for a long time.
The physical shock was still in him.
And the old anger rose automatically.
And the fear hidden beneath the anger too.
And there was something else.
Deeper.
That he could no longer name well.
Then he stepped aside.
Come in.
The living room was small and clean.
With that silence of a place where a person has lived alone for too long.
There was a dark wooden table.
Two chairs.
A sofa with warm fabric on the backrest.
A shelf with few books and no ornaments.
Kit pointed to one of the chairs.
Rowena sat.
He stayed standing leaning against the wall arms crossed.
Talk.
She talked.
She talked for a long time.
Without embellishing without crying.
She talked about the investigators J. Go had hired over the years.
About the money he left with lawyers who had no names.
About the medications paid for by third parties.
The debts settled before they became dangerous.
About the empty chair no one explained and no one removed from the living room.
She talked about Yudora.
About the way she never said his name.
About the way once on the porch she had murmured about a lost laugh.
She talked about the terrace J. Go avoided.
She talked about the envelope he'd hidden.
About the control he confused with love.
About the old fear he carried because he thought that if he let go,
he'd lose everything again.
Kit listened without interrupting.
When she finished he stayed silent for a while.
Then he laughed.
A short dry laugh.
Almost a grunt.
He spent 10 years looking for me.
He did.
Without stopping.
And he never came himself.
Rowena hesitated.
He thought you didn't want to be found by him.
Kit closed his eyes.
Inside something that had been hard for 10 years began to crack.
Slow and inevitable as a crack in stone.
He swallowed once.
Slow and again.
He wasn't wrong.
He was.
Rowena's voice came out lower.
He just didn't know he was.
Kit peeled himself off the wall.
He went to the window.
Looked at the neglected garden for a long time at the grass growing between the paving stones.
Then he turned around.
I'll make coffee.
They spent the afternoon and the night talking.
On the porch with cups that went cold twice and the sound of crickets filling the dark around them.
Kit spoke aloud for the first time about what he felt.
He said he'd fled because he thought he wasn't important to anyone.
But on that night, he'd asked his brother for help and his brother hadn't come.
And he understood in that instant that his world was worth less than a meeting.
That when the boat began to crack in the storm, he had two seconds to choose between swimming
or sinking.
And he chose to swim because the anger was greater than the exhaustion.
That when he came out the other side, on a stretch of beach he didn't even know where it was.
He made the decision to disappear because he thought no one would miss him enough to
really look.
And he looked, Kit said, looking at the bandstand in the square in the distance.
All these years, all these years.
Kit ran his hand over his eyes slowly.
He made a mistake out of fear, Kit.
Not out of choice.
Rowena spoke low, looking at the same point he was.
He's afraid of you all the time.
Of what happened and of what he didn't do.
Kit laughed again this time without the dryness of before, almost with affection.
And affection he clearly hadn't expected to feel.
You talk about him as if you knew him.
I know him.
You love him.
She didn't answer.
She didn't need to.
They stayed silent for a while.
With the warm wind passing through the branches of the old Magnolia,
growing in the corner of the garden.
Then Kit spoke, looking at his own hands.
If I come back, I come back once.
No promises.
If it doesn't work, I leave again.
And this time no one finds me.
Agreed.
And I don't know if I'll be able to look at him.
You don't need to know that now.
Kit nodded slowly, like someone making a deal with himself,
as much as with her.
In the morning he took a small suitcase.
Very small.
Rowena looked at that suitcase and understood the size of what he carried.
Not in what was inside, but in how little there was.
Before they left for the station, she sent a single message to Silas,
from the telegraph on the corner.
We arrived tomorrow.
Prepare you Dora.
While they waited for the train on the wooden bench of the town's only platform,
Kit looked at the horizon and said,
without turning his face.
Rowena.
Yes.
If you brought me here for him, he swallowed.
Thank you.
She didn't answer.
She simply rested her hand over his hand,
and his hand was cold, and hers was too.
The train whistled in the distance.
Jego didn't sleep.
The house near the Savannah River was so silent
that he could hear his own pulse in his throat.
Sitting on the study floor leaning against the shelf,
his suit rumbled and his tie loose since the small hours.
He counted time by the way the light came through the window.
First blue, then gray,
then a timid gold that arrived to insulting for the weight of the day.
Rowena's letter was still folded in his lap.
He no longer needed to reread it to know what was written.
I'll come back when I bring what he couldn't bring on his own.
Each word weighed more than the last.
Each word opened a door he'd kept closed for 10 years
and pushed him inside it with no choice, no warning,
without even letting him breathe first.
Inside, Jego had the cold certainty that the punishment had finally arrived,
not in the form of scandal, not in the form of death,
not in the form of a headline,
in the form of a woman with an ink scar in the Sunday paper,
going after what he hadn't had the courage to bring.
And in the most cowardly part of him,
a low voice said that this scar could open again,
that this time the woman too might not come back.
Silas came in at seven without knocking.
He brought coffee Jego hadn't asked for,
and a silenced Jego didn't want.
He stood in the door frame waiting with that lawyer's patience of someone who'd already seen too many
clients on the floor of his own office.
Talk, Jego said without looking up, she arrived, she's with him.
How do you know? She sent me a message.
Short, Silas hesitated, and at the bottom of that hesitation there was an old
lawyer had decided to carry in silence until now.
He held out the phone. Jego read the line on the screen
and took a full second to breathe again.
We arrived tomorrow.
Prepare you doorer. He closed his eyes.
He felt the room spin as if someone had flipped the floor.
There was a man inside him who wanted to yell at Silas for giving up the thread.
There was another deeper who wanted to kneel and give thanks.
The first one for half a second.
Jego stood up, grabbed Silas by the lapel, and stopped his fist in the air before it closed.
His hand trembled, it never trembled.
Don't hit, Silas said very low.
You're not a man who hits.
I'm not a man of anything right now, Jego answered,
and let go of the lapel like someone releasing a rope too hot to hold.
They stood still.
Outside a bird insisted on a whistle of three repeated notes without tiring, without mercy.
Jego looked at his own reflection in the glass of the picture frame.
And recognized neither the disheveled hair nor the civilized despair his eyes held.
Prepare her, he asked, and his voice didn't quite obey.
Prepare my mother.
I will.
Silas.
Jego swallowed.
Thank you.
Silas looked at him long.
He said nothing.
He left.
It was feeling who arrived first at the quint mentioned.
Udora was having tea in the small parlor.
The newspaper still untouched on the white linen napkin.
The matriarch looked up and read.
In the younger systems posture, that something was coming before the words.
She didn't ask.
She waited.
With that old skill of letting Silas do the work.
Mrs. Rowena asked that you come to the main hall at five.
Feline said, with the trained delicacy of someone delivering news he didn't understand.
And Mr. Jego as well.
Udora folded the newspaper carefully as if it might break.
A hand when it rested on the table had a strange lightness
for the weight of the day.
That's all?
She wanted to know.
That's all.
The matriarch didn't smile.
She didn't protest.
She nodded once and turned her gaze to the window.
Where the garden trees swade in a breeze no one inside could feel.
The trainer arrived at four.
Rowena got off on the savanna platform with the same small bag she'd left with.
And a thin man beside her who insisted on keeping three steps of distance.
Like someone still deciding whether to stay or turn around and disappear again.
Kit had his head down.
His cap pulled low.
His backpack held tight against his chest like a shield.
Every sudden noise in the station made his jaw clench.
He stopped twice on the way to the taxi.
And both times Rowena pretended not to see.
Continuing to walk at a pace that demanded nothing.
We can go back.
She said, at the third stop without pressure.
If you want to go back now, we go back.
I'll take you back and won't tell anyone you set foot in savanna.
Kit swallowed.
It's not that.
It's what then.
It's that I forgot what the smell is like.
Rowena looked at him.
There was an 18-year-old boy inside that thin man and the boy was blinking hard not to cry on the
sidewalk of a station full of strangers.
She didn't touch his arm.
She just stood there at the same height waiting.
The smell is the same, she answered.
Magnolia and old money.
Kit laughed.
A quick laugh almost a sob.
Ah.
So it's the same.
They got into the taxi.
Rowena told the driver to stop at the mansion.
Not at the house near the river.
Kit raised his face when the facade appeared.
That heavy iron gate he knew better than any other place in the world.
He stared at it for a long time.
A leaf came loose from one of the tall trees and fell on the hood of the car with a
lightness that seemed calculated.
No one said anything.
I don't know if I can.
Kit said, low.
You can make it to the door.
After that we decide.
And if they hate me, they don't hate you.
They don't know how to hate you.
Kit didn't answer.
The open the car door and got out slowly.
Like someone stepping onto a floor that might not hold his weight.
The main hall smelled of Magnolia and old money.
The afternoon came in through the tall windows in bands of golden light
that crossed the marble and stopped at the empty chair near the window
as if they knew exactly where to land.
Rowena went in first.
She deliberately chose that place.
Not the living room, not the library, not J. GO's study.
Where everything had begun to fall apart.
The hall.
The same room where one night, month earlier, a woman in a borrowed dress had held the face of a
silent man and kissed him in front of 300 people.
The smell was the same.
The light came in at the same angle.
The chair was still empty.
Rowena positioned herself exactly where she had stood on that other night.
As if she were marking a fixed point on a map.
Only she knew how to read.
Kit stayed one step behind, still in his cap,
still with his hand closed around the strap of the backpack.
Feeling opened the double doors.
Udora came in first.
The matriarch noticed Rowena, noticed the figure behind her.
And for a moment, tiny, almost invisible, her spine seemed to give way a millimeter.
She restrained it.
She kept her chin high.
She crossed the hall to the center and stopped, waiting.
J. GO came in after.
And his world stopped turning.
There was a thin man in the hall.
Then, with his cap pulled low, a small scar on his eyebrow.
His shoulders narrower than memory had drawn them.
A man who slowly lowered the cap, revealing his short hair, and looked up.
And it was the gaze of the 18-year-old boy, who had taken a boat out alone on a stormy night,
10 years before.
J. GO said nothing for a length of time no one there could measure.
He took a step than another.
Then he stopped.
Inside it was as if a dam had given way.
The old guilt, the anguish of the last two days.
The fear of losing Rowena, all mixing into a single hot point in the middle of his chest,
too hot to be born with composure.
He felt his throat tightened.
He felt his hands go cold.
He felt with brutal clarity that the punishment hadn't come.
That life, against any deserving, had given something back.
Kit, he said.
And his voice came out choked, ridiculous.
The voice of a big boy that didn't fit that man.
Kit, Kit dropped the backpack on the floor.
The thud was dry on the marble.
I ran away, he said, and his mouth trembled.
I ran away because I thought I wasn't important to anyone.
J. GO closed his eyes.
A tear fell before he could command his body to hold it back.
Then another.
He didn't wipe them.
I spent 10 years, he answered.
Trying to fix the worst choice of my life.
Kit shook his head incredulous.
And the shaking became a tremor.
And the tremor became a short dry sob.
J. GO crossed the rest of the hall in three strides,
and hugged his brother any which way.
A crooked hug without elegance,
without the composure all of Savannah knew.
A hug that had waited 10 years to happen,
and that now happened all at once, clumsy and urgent.
Kit was slow to return it.
When he did, he gripped J. GO's coat,
as if he were holding on so as not to fall.
J. GO's coat was not to fall.
My boy, she said,
and the knife-edged voice became a voice with no edge.
My boy,
get turned to his mother and couldn't speak.
He just rested his forehead on her shoulder.
J. GO's coat was not to fall. J. GO's coat was not to fall.
J. GO's coat was not to fall.
J.
GO's
coat
was  not  to  fall.
J. GO's coat was not to fall.
J.  GO's  coat
was  not  to  fall.
J. GO's coat was not to fall.
J.  GO's
coat
was  not  to  fall.
J. GO's coat was not to fall.
J.
GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.
J. GO's coat was not to fall.
J.  GO's  coat  was
not
to  fall.
J.  GO's
coat  was  not  to  fall.
J. GO's coat was not to fall.
J.  GO's  coat  was
not  to  fall.
J.  GO's  coat
was  not  to  fall.
J.  GO's
coat  was  not  to  fall.
J. GO's coat was not to fall.
J.  GO's  coat  was
not
to  fall.
J. GO's coat was not to fall.
J.  GO's  coat
was  not  to
fall.
J. GO's coat was not to fall.
J.  GO's  coat
was
not
to  fall.
J. GO's coat was not to fall.
J.  GO's  coat  was  not
to  fall.
J.  GO's  coat
was  not  to  fall.
J. GO's coat was not to fall.
J.  GO's
coat
was  not  to  fall.
J. GO's coat was not to fall.
J.  GO's  coat  was  not
to  fall.
J.  GO's  coat
was  not  to  fall.
J. GO's coat was not to fall.
J. GO's coat was not to fall. J. GO's coat was not to fall.
J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's
coat  was  not
to
fall.
J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat
was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat
was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's
coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not
to  fall.  J
GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.
GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat
was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.
GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was
not  to  fall.  J.  GO
J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was
not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's
coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to
fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J
GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat
was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's
coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not
to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not
to  fall.  J.  GO
Settysfied  desire  and  something  deeper  that  reaffirmed  itself  with  each  beat  of  the  heart.  Little  by  little  the  movement  slowed
to  lazy  touches.  Soft  kisses  on  shoulders  and  chins.  Glances  that  said  everything  the  words  hadn't  yet  reached.
The  connection  that  had  begun  with  the  recognition  in  the  kiss.  Now  sealed  itself  in  the  post -pleasure  stillness.  Where
each  shared  breath  reinforced  the  certainty  that  this  time  they  wouldn't  lose  each  other  again.  They  stayed  there.  Their
breathing  took  time  to  steady.  He  didn't  pull  a  wall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall
J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.
J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's
coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.
GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not
to  fall.  J
GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat
was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to
fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's
coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO
coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's
coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.
GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to
fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's
coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat
J.  GO's
coat
was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J
GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's
coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to
fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's
coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not
to  fall.  J.  GO
She  began  by  saying  she'd  be  brief  because  long  love  puts  you  to  sleep  and  drew  a  laugh  even  from  you  dora.  She
looked  at  Rowena  and  said,  you  were  the  best  journalist  in  this  city  when  I  met  you.  You  still  are.  Only  now  you  write  by
choice,  not  by  fright.  And  that's  the  only  thing  I've  wanted  for  you  since  the  very  first  pre -dorn  we  answered  the  phone  crying.  Rowena
laughed  with  a  runny  nose.  J.  GO's  squeezed  her  hand.  Silas  raised  his  glass  a  little  later.  And  mentioned  in  passing
that  a  certain  ares  had  gotten  engaged  to  a  swiss -possil.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to
J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.
GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's
coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not
to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J
GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's
coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's
coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.
GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO
GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.
J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's
coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.
GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.  GO's  coat  was  not  to  fall.  J.
GO
On  months  had  stayed  empty  without  anyone  explaining,  someone  was  sitting.  J.  GO  was  reading  the  newspaper  with  a  steaming
mug  beside  him.  His  hair  still  wet  from  the  shower.  His  feet  resting  on  the  stool.  He  felt  her  gaze,  looked
up,  smiled  with  just  one  corner  of  his  mouth.  He  went  back  to  the  newspaper.  J.  GO  looked  too.  He
stayed  there  a  second.  He  squeezed  Rowena's  hand  more  firmly  over  their  own  child.  The  winter  light  crossed  the  room  and  fell  on
J.  GO's  arm.  On  Rowena's  belly.  J.  GO's  arm.  On  Rowena's  belly.  J.  GO's  arm.  On  Rowena's  belly.  J.  GO's  arm.  On  Rowena's  belly.  J.  GO's  arm.  On  Rowena's  belly.  J.  GO's  arm.  On  Rowena's  belly.  J.  GO's  arm.  On  Rowena's  belly.  J.  GO's  arm.  On  Rowena's  belly.  J.  GO's  arm.  On  Rowena's  belly.  J.  J.  J.  J.  J.  J.
J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J. J